<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Technical | harkuchh]]></title>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/blog/categories/technical/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-16T08:19:12+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://harkuchh.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[harkuchh]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Firefox Plugins I Can't Live Without]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/5-firefox-plugins-i-cant-live-without/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-16T08:01:47+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/5-firefox-plugins-i-cant-live-without</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I use Firefox as my primary web browser. I have emotional attachments with Mozilla and their <a href="https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/mission/">mission</a>. I used Chrome for sometime, but I ditched it for some reasons. Firefox make me feel more like home. The philosophical bond of trust is a big thing for me.</p>

<p>Here&rsquo;s a list of top 5 Firefox addons I use daily. Whenever I switch to a new machine, installing these is generally the first thing I do.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h3><a href="https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/addon/fxchrome">FxChrome</a></h3>

<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/b7MQxEu.png" alt="FxChrome Firefox plugin" />
FxChrome is a Chrome like theme for Firefox. Firefox is cool, but it doesn&rsquo;t look that cool. By default I mean. This theme make Firefox look like Chrome, while keeping all Mozilla goodness.</p>

<h3><a href="https://wappalyzer.com/">Wappalyzer</a></h3>

<p>Wappalyzer is a browser extension that identifies the technologies used on websites. Whenever I see a good site, first thing that come to mind is what technologies are these guys using?</p>

<p>Wappalyzer save me a lot of work. It shows the technologies used by the sites in the address bar. So whenever I visit a website, it tells me things like they are using Wordpress, jQuery, Google Analytics and other technologies.</p>

<h3><a href="http://www.ghostery.com/">Ghostery</a></h3>

<p>Ghostery is for my paranoid self. It stop websites from tracking me. Ghostery detects and stop all sort of trackers used on websites, from analytics to social media widgets. I used to use AdBlock Plus as well earlier, but now I use Ghostery only.<br/>
After all ads are the reason why content on Internet is free. Ghostery protects my privacy while I am still able to support publishers.</p>

<h3><a href="http://trac.arantius.com/wiki/Extensions/Resurrect">Resurrect Pages</a></h3>

<p>Web pages go down all the time. It happen a lot with me that I visit some website and it&rsquo;s down. Resurrect pages help resurrecting the dead (pages) using various archiving sites of the web. Whenever I visit a dead page, it shows a list of archives, and I can choose to visit a snapshot of the page from there.</p>

<h3><a href="https://www.pushbullet.com">PushBullet</a></h3>

<p>You&rsquo;ll understand the value of PushBullet only if you use the PushBullet app on your Android phone. PushBullet help me share content between my phone and my browser. I send all sort of things with it to my phone, would it be the todo list of things I need to do when I go out of my home (that actually happen very rarely), or links to articles I want to read on phone when lying in bed or notes etc.</p>

<p>And for some reason my brain start producing awesome ideas when I am about to sleep, and there is no time to start my computer to note them. Then I just start my phone, and send those ideas to my computer as notes. It&rsquo;s a really useful app.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
