<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: INDIA | harkuchh]]></title>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/blog/categories/india/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-04T01:04:37+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://harkuchh.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[harkuchh]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corporate Society is Fraud, Bitch Please !]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/corporate-society-is-fraud-bitch-please/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-05T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/corporate-society-is-fraud-bitch-please</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>You might have heard about Corporate, The <b>Corporate Infocom Pvt. Ltd</b> or <b>Corporate Society</b>, and if you have heard <b>about</b> <b>Corporate Society</b> then there are two strong possibilities that you may heard it’s a great emerging <b>Indian networking company</b> originated from <b>capital of India</b>, Delhi or you may have heard that <b>Corporate society is fraud</b>, fake, cheater company who <b>make people especially youth fool by making fake promises</b> to them. I have no idea what exactly you have heard <b>about</b> <b>Corporate Infocom Pvt. Ltd</b> but I’m damn sure, whatever someone told you <b>about Corporate</b> will be something like that, well just give your sometime to this post and let me explain what is the truth behind Corporate Society.<!--more--></p>

<br><br>


<p><a href="http://harkuchh.com/corporate-society-is-fraud-bitch-please/corporate-is-fraud-or-not/" rel="attachment wp-att-8601"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-8601" alt="Corporate is Fraud or not" src="https://fbcdn-sphotos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-ash3/t1/1622048_620819387984253_705217368_n.jpg" width="580" height="213" /></a></p>

<br><br>


<p>I promise you whatever I’m going to tell you is absolutely truth and trusted because I also joined corporate and I know almost everything about it, I joined corporate and it changed my life completely, hold on ! don’t react too fast, first listen what I’m talking about, Yes this is true that my life got changed and corporate is responsible behind it.</p>

<br><br>


<p>Now I know, you wanted to know, How my life got changed because of Corporate Society ? it’s answer is, corporate gave me that platform on which I’m working right now and this platform have a glorious future ahead, it’s called Blogging. Actually before joining<strong> CIPL</strong> I had no Idea how to develop a complete website and run it on internet even after I was a engineering student from I.T trade, I knew how to create a webpage by using HTML and PHP but if we know how to create a webpage it doesn’t mean we can also make a website with that comfort for example creating a webpage by using HTML is like making a 5 second ad commercial and developing a website is something like making of Titanic and I don’t think I need to explain what is the difference between making these two.</p>

<br><br>


<p>In short, it was not possible for me to create even a 4-5 page static website and deploy it on Internet then you can easily think that how could I think of creating a website like Harkuchh, pay your attention, right now I’m just talking about creating a website not SEO, ranking, Backlinks, Ads, commercial emails, advertising, Social promotion, Database, My Sql, affiliate marketing  etc etc and etc but as you can see today I own a website with world rank near to 25k worldwide and around 2k in India and unbelievable fact is that the worth of my website is more than my dad’s property! and that all is live and true you know why ? because of corporate. Corporate told me I can do it, and I did.</p>

<br><br>


<p>Now let me tell you, if it’s true then why people says Corporate is fraud, fake, cheater and blaw&hellip; blaw&hellip; blaw :P</p>

<br><br>


<p>Well Corporate is actually a networking company, who sales it’s web hosting service by following a referral marketing strategy i.e Corporate gives web hosting for a website and chance to work in networking to it’s associates, and the real story begins here..</p>

<br><br>


<p>When a person is approached for a seminar or PPT (paper presentation) by a friend or any known, he/she’s told by the presenter that we’ll give you hosting to create your own website and tell you how to earn money through Google Adsense and other Ads and along with this, company will also give you some extra money as commission if someone join the company by your referral.<br><br>
After joining, some finds it more profitable to work in network marketing so they start working in it,else who wanted to create their website start working on their website, but when any problem arises to them they expect help from the seniors but their seniors won’t help them (I’m always present to help you) this is a bitter but truth, and this is the biggest reason people call the <b>Corporate is fraud</b> <b>company</b>, but point to pay the attention again is that it’s just a hurdle and if seniors not helping someone and they stop working then it’s neither the senior’s nor company’s it’s your fault. Because problem arise to everyone it doesn’t mean you can not proceed after that, there are so many examples who did it all without the help of any seniors, I’m also one of them.</p>

<br><br>


<p><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>&ldquo;</b></span><span style="color: #003366;"><em>If you need any kind of help in making website, increasing ranking, traffic, getting Adsense, earnings you can contact me any time, my contact details are given in Author Box in sidebar. If you want to create or develop a website only and not interested in Networking part then also you can contact me for the solution of your problem</em></span>.</p>

<br><br>


<h2><span style="font-family: georgia;"><b>Reviews About Corporate Society
</b></span></h2>


<p>Many people call it fraud, fake blaw&hellip;blaww&hellip; blaw&hellip;. and many people worship corporate, let me share some reviews from the person who are/were the part of Corporate Infocom Private Limited.</p>

<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>

<img class=" " alt="" src="https://fbcdn-profile-a.akamaihd.net/hprofile-ak-prn2/t1/p160x160/1545136_3867806511460_1004175759_n.jpg" width="112" height="112" /> <strong>Chandan Sanwal</strong>

&nbsp;</td>
<td>If your senior/upline is Good to you then CIPL is good for you, If not then you will be frustrated after some time and say it is fraud. But actually it is not. People working is CIPL make it fraud by not supporting their downline. Chandan Sanwal</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="text-align: left;">

<img alt="" src="https://fbcdn-profile-a.akamaihd.net/hprofile-ak-ash2/t1/c1.159.339.339/s160x160/1452253_3652895536633_757654845_n.jpg" width="112" height="112" /> <strong>Jatin Malik</strong>

&nbsp;</td>
<td style="text-align: left;">Failure will never blame himself for his failure , he will always blame the platform he opted..but from my according every platform is best , its just how you perform out there..by this reason people who blame the platform to be as FRAUD and having belief that somewhere it was the platform only which was responsible for their failure , i personally call those people A BIG FRAUD for being FRAUD to themselves and to those whom they are saying the platform they opted was FRAUD...in the end THANX Corporate Society for providing me those things which are priceless to me..love u always..</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>

<img alt="" src="https://fbcdn-profile-a.akamaihd.net/hprofile-ak-ash3/c50.50.621.621/s160x160/558613_4140712009991_2081007018_n.jpg" width="112" height="112" /> <strong>Vinod Krishna</strong></td>
<td>It is the duty of the upline to train their downline, this lack of training is the main reason why some people become negative. But there are also some people who expect a lot to earn but never atleast try to work. Such people are also one of the reason for such rumors.
But it is a proved fact that corporate has changed the lifestyle of many people..</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>


<br><br>


<p><strong>Conclusion </strong>: Corporate Society is not a fraud company, it’s all crap ! many people living their life happily on internet world because of Corporate Society, well yes it’s true that many people leaved and leaving corporate society and they doing their own business after leaving corporate but it’s also a fact that whatever they are today because of corporate Society, they are thinking they are king but they may forgot every king was once a child, in short if there would be <strong>no corporate Society</strong> then there would be no&hellip;&hellip;&hellip;&hellip;&hellip; , no&hellip;&hellip;&hellip;&hellip;&hellip; and even no&hellip;&hellip;&hellip;&hellip;&hellip;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Success Story ever, from an Indian Farm laborer to CEO of a Software Company in USA]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/biggest-success-story-ever-from-an-indian-farm-laborer-to-ceo-of-a-software-company-in-usa/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-16T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/biggest-success-story-ever-from-an-indian-farm-laborer-to-ceo-of-a-software-company-in-usa</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #000000;">You may have heard about many successful people who were nothing in the beginning and they became a famous person or personality later, but this story is greater than those all. It will be hard to believe on this but you have to believe on it, because<span style="color: #008000;"> <strong>this is a true Success story of an Indian lady who got married at the age of only 16, became a two child mother at the age of 18 who </strong><strong>worked as agricultural laborer for Rs. 5 per day and today she is the CEO of a Software company in USA.</strong></span></span></p>

<p><span style="color: #000000;"><!--more--> </span></p>

<p><span style="color: #000000;">her story is enough to explain that ‘Success is the result of a continuous hardworking with optimism ,overcoming all the barriers’.  This is the Incredible Success story of the most successful woman who started from Nothing, and didn&rsquo;t wait for the opportunity to knock but created the opportunity on her own, worked hard and made History<strong><em>, this is the complete success story of ‘Jyothi Reddy’</em></strong>.</span></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #3366ff;"><strong>Early Life, Education and Marriage</strong></span></h3>




<hr />


<p><span style="color: #000000;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/biggest-success-story-ever-from-an-indian-farm-laborer-to-ceo-of-a-software-company-in-usa/jyothi-reddy-youngage-pic/" rel="attachment wp-att-3489"><img class="alignleft  wp-image-3489" title="Jyothi Reddy youngage pic" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/Jyothi-Reddy-youngage-pic.jpg" width="166" height="237" /></a>Every success story has a humble beginning which proceeds through extraordinary events, and extreme life journeys. The story of <span style="color: #008000;"><strong>D. Anila Jyothi Reddy</strong></span> is one of them. She was born in Warangal District (Andhra Pradesh) as eldest of four children to a common peasant who lost his employment from Army because of his attachment with the family. It was very difficult for her poor father to run family, so he put Jyothi in a <em><span style="color: #333333;">government orphanage at Hanumakonda as a mother less child. From 5th class to 10th class Jyothi Reddy stayed in orphanage by having solitary life away from home.</span></em></span></p>

<p><span style="color: #000000;">She used to await if anyone would come and render some help. Particularly during winter season when she used to shiver like anything as her blankets were torn. Even during summer she never used to go to her village, she used to stay in warden’s house and did all the house hold work for which she was fed. She passed 10th class with good marks but could not continue her education. <em><strong><span style="color: #333333;">At the age of just 16 they performed her marriage with Mr. Sangi Reddy and by the age of 18, she became mother of two girls.</span></strong></em></span></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #3366ff;"><strong>Necessity made her Post Graduate Teacher</strong></span></h3>




<hr />


<p><span style="color: #000000;">To meet the basic requirements of her family, Jyothi started working as an agricultural laborer for 5 Rupees a day and continued working from 1986 to 1989. Jyothi would mostly work in the fields and struggled to find a job in off seasons. Her tumultuous life changed the day when Nehru Yuvak Kendra (NYK) founded a night school with the intention of providing basic education for the villagers. </span></p>

<p>[caption id=&ldquo;attachment_3490&rdquo; align=&ldquo;aligncenter&rdquo; width=&ldquo;460&rdquo;]<a href="http://harkuchh.com/biggest-success-story-ever-from-an-indian-farm-laborer-to-ceo-of-a-software-company-in-usa/jyothi-in-red-saree-with-white-chain-when-she-working-with-nehru-yuva-kendrawarangal-in-1990-91-year-and-salary-was-190-rupees-per-month/" rel="attachment wp-att-3490"><img class="size-large wp-image-3490 " title="Jyothi in Red Saree with white chain....When she working with Nehru Yuva kendra,Warangal...in 1990-91 Year and Salary was 190 Rupees per Month" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/Jyothi-in-Red-Saree-with-white-chain....When-she-working-with-Nehru-Yuva-kendraWarangal...in-1990-91-Year-and-Salary-was-190-Rupees-per-Month-460x460.jpg" width="460" height="460" /></a> Jyothi in Red Saree with white chain&hellip;.When she working with Nehru Yuva kendra,Warangal&hellip;in 1990-91 Year and Salary was 190 Rupees per Month[/caption]</p>

<p><span style="color: #000000;">She was the only educated girl in village so they appointed her as the volunteer to educate the adults after giving some training. It fetched her Rupees 150 per month. Her hard work and dedication impressed the Inspection authorities and they promoted her to Mandal Prerak of Hanumakonda. After being appointed there, Jyothi had to visit all the centres of the Warangal district and there she realized the importance of education. and she went on to completing her graduation and post graduation from Ambedkar Open University. Later, on completion of her B. Ed from Anna University, Jyothi Reddy became a government teacher. It was the initial stage that she successfully achieved through slow but steady steps.</span></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #3366ff;"><strong>Reason to Go Abroad</strong></span></h3>




<hr />


<p><span style="color: #000000;">If the story stopped here there would be nothing much to inspire others. Real Story begins here, Jyothi was working as inspector of schools, a relative of her who settled in America came to India, after meeting them on some occasions she realized how a completely different lifestyle they led. So for a bright future for her daughters, she dreamed of going abroad, as an old proverb says “Success is 1 percent inspiration and 99 percent perspiration.” She started learning computers and saving money for her passport and visa. Back in those days, getting US Visa wasn’t as easy as today she tried many times and failed but eventually after series of early failures she could get a visiting visa and flew to America having a very little amount.</span></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #3366ff;"><strong>First Work in USA</strong></span></h3>




<hr />


<p><span style="color: #000000;">There challenges did not stop, her relatives denied giving her shelter they refused to take her phone call and fortunately was finally accepted as a paying guest by a Gujarati family. As work Jyothi joined a video shop in New Jersey as a salesperson, While working an Indian from Warangal saw her and recommended her name to his brother who owned a company called “ CSAMERICA” and she was appointed as recruiter there after being trained. It was a climbing phase of her economic and career ladder. Several months later, a reputed company ICSA offered her a better position with better salary so she moved. Jyothi says about that time “It was a crucial time for me. I had to deal with Americans but did not know English very well”.</span></p>

<p><span style="color: #000000;">After working for some days again she became in trouble when the company asked her to resign for not owning a working Visa. She resigned and once again worked for just $5 an hour doing several offbeat jobs until the day she received her H1 Visa (h1 Visa allows US employers to temporarily employ foreign workers in specialty occupations).</span></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #3366ff;"><strong>Idea of establish entrepreneurship</strong></span></h3>




<hr />


<p><span style="color: #000000;">She went to Mexico for her VISA to be stamped. According to Jyothi ‘Getting the Visa Stamped, was one of the most painful and dreary experiences for her’, all the hardships of obtaining visa gave her an idea of establish her first entrepreneurship to assist the people to get their Visas. Jyothi came back to U.S in May 2000 and by September, 2001 she became entrepreneur with her own initiation, i.e.<span style="color: #008000;"><strong> Keys software solutions</strong></span> was initiated. It extended its services in developing software solutions and recruitment and other job providing areas. She made her cousin as partner and extended her business to become more profitable.</span></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #3366ff;"><strong>The Dream became True</strong></span></h3>




<hr />


<p><span style="color: #000000;">Her priority and dream was always giving her children that life which she didn’t lived, Her hard work, commitment and dedication towards her goal make all her dreams true. Her two daughters had finished higher education in America from prestigious universities and got married to well settled bridegrooms. She made enough money to take care of her children and herself with many other children living in Orphanages. She did perfectly what she dreamed for and proved ‘<em><strong>No condition is permanent</strong></em>’.</span></p>

<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/biggest-success-story-ever-from-an-indian-farm-laborer-to-ceo-of-a-software-company-in-usa/jyothi-reddy-story-of-success/" rel="attachment wp-att-3491"><img class="aligncenter  wp-image-3491" title="Jyothi Reddy story of Success" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/Jyothi-Reddy-story-of-Success.jpg" width="275" height="302" /></a></p>


<p><span style="color: #008000;">Mrs. Jyothi Reddy is now the owner of a million-dollar company, has customised homes in the US and India, owns a Toyota Camry (an earlier car was a BMW) and has “enough” jewellery which is generally any women’s biggest dream specially in India :).</span></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #3366ff;"><strong>Believe in Humanity</strong></span></h3>




<hr />


<p><span style="color: #000000;">Jyothi strongly believes the words of Mother Teresa… “ The worst disease in the world is neither poverty nor other, lack of feeling of belongingness, being unwanted is the worst ”. Whenever she visits the Orphanages in India she prefers to spend more time with the orphans. “ <em><strong>she is more than mother to me</strong></em>’’ says Ranjitha, an orphan who is being sponsored by Jyothi, she helps the children with all that they require among all the love and feeling of belongingness. She visits Women’s colleges too and empowers them with her life experience. She also helped many Indians to settle in America by providing initial shelter and guidance.</span></p>

<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/biggest-success-story-ever-from-an-indian-farm-laborer-to-ceo-of-a-software-company-in-usa/jyothi-reddy-with-orphan-children/" rel="attachment wp-att-3492"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-3492" title="Jyothi Reddy with orphan children" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/Jyothi-Reddy-with-orphan-children.jpg" width="320" height="210" /></a></p>


<p><span style="color: #000000;">Agricultural workers still remember her as friendly, keen to learn work, but often bemoaning her fate. “<em><strong>She used to walk around with an umbrella</strong></em>,” recalls one labourer with a laugh.</span></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h2 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #3366ff;"><strong>Conclusion</strong></span></h2>




<hr />


<p><span style="color: #000000;">She has proven that higher education is attainable by even very poor people against all odds. She proves that to be successful, what requires is aspiration, desperation, perseverance to accomplish, which most people think to be impossible. She is also a live example of ‘<em><strong>harder you work and luckier you get</strong></em>’.<span style="color: #333399;"> If you see many college students and people they keep on blaming their environment and parents when they fail to satisfy their wants. A sincere advice to them to visit any orphanage at least once in a year. You better understand the real pain of the life and appreciate what you really have.</span></span></p>

<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/biggest-success-story-ever-from-an-indian-farm-laborer-to-ceo-of-a-software-company-in-usa/jyothi-reddy-biggest-success-story-of-a-lady/" rel="attachment wp-att-3494"><img class="aligncenter  wp-image-3494" title="Jyothi reddy success story " alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/Jyothi-reddy-biggest-success-story-of-a-lady-580x318.jpg" width="580" height="318" /></a></p>


<p><span style="color: #000000;">A FEW BUT STILL TRUE LIFE ROLE MODELS. It’s so amazing for a girl from a BPL family particularly when her family was opposed to her climbing the ladder of distinction – all alone.</span></p>

<p><span style="color: #000000;">Hit like and share if you feel proud to be an Indian and if you think Jyothi Reddy’s story is Really inspiring. <span style="color: #808080;"><em><strong>Congratularion Mrs. Jyothi Reddy, May God bless you always, Long Live, Grand salute to you</strong></em></span>.</span></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
