<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Tools | harkuchh]]></title>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/blog/categories/tools/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-12T01:53:43+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://harkuchh.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[harkuchh]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strong Passwords, Weak Passwords: How to Generate Strongest Possible Passwords Which You Can Remember]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/strong-passwords-weak-passwords-how-to-generate-strongest-possible-passwords-which-you-can-remember/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-04T00:46:09+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/strong-passwords-weak-passwords-how-to-generate-strongest-possible-passwords-which-you-can-remember</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Passwords we know, the most common method used by almost all websites for authenticating users. But how good is this method? Well, the strength of this method partially depend on the strength of the password we choose.</p>

<h2>What&rsquo;s the strength of a password?</h2>

<p>Strength of a password is determined by a number of things.</p>

<!-- more -->


<ul>
<li><strong>Character set</strong><br/>
Most important thing which make a password strong is its character set. Character set of a password means which characters are used in the password, like lower case characters, upper case characters, numbers, symbols etc. A password which has all different type of characters is considered stronger.</li>
<li><strong>Length of the password</strong><br/>
Second most important thing about strong passwords is their length. Longer passwords are considered more secure.</li>
<li><p><strong>Guessability of the password</strong><br/>
Another thing which determine strength of password is of easy it is to guess a password. Easier to guess passwords are weak. A security researcher has said that <a href="http://www.troyhunt.com/2011/03/only-secure-password-is-one-you-cant.html">any password  you can remember is not safe enough</a>.</p>

<h2>The problem</h2>

So we have a problem here. They say any password we choose which we can remember is not safe enough. Most people choose easy, simple to remember password, which is perfectly reasonable. Why putting extra load on brain? But this laziness can cost more than you think.

<h2><a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">The Solution</a></h2>

<img src="http://i.imgur.com/Ujh8L6y.png" alt="Fireword password generator" /><br/>
So I wanted a system which will create passwords for me which I can remember, but which can&rsquo;t be guessed or cracked easily. One solution to this is passphrases. For example, instead of choosing a single word password like &ldquo;facebook123&rdquo;, I choose a sentence like &ldquo;facebookhasbluecolor&rdquo;. And even better, change some character with symbols and numbers, &ldquo;f@c3b00kh4sBlu3C0lOr&rdquo;. Awesome, right! But it still can be remembered. So according to our theory that any password which can be remembered is not safe enough. I want something simple to remember and type and still very strong and long.
So being a software developer, I made a system which do exactly this. I call it fireword.

<h2>What is fireword?</h2>

<p><a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a> is an application in which you enter a simple word or phrase, and it give you a very strong and impossible to guess password.</p></li>
<li><p><a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a> always generate same password for same word. So you remember your simple password, and generate a strong one with this site. And then when you need to login again, regenerate strong password with your simple one.</p></li>
<li><a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a> allow you to select the length of the password. You can choose from 8 to 128 character long password.</li>
<li>For example, just entering &lsquo;facebook&rsquo; become this &lsquo;bF2A37d5e8%{61?C]>3E[{(9{&rsquo;. Any password can be expanded to at most 128 character long complex password.

<h2>Recommended ways to use <a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a></h2>

<p>It&rsquo;s really simple. Instead of using you easy to remember but weak password for a website, change your password with the password generated by fireword.</p></li>
<li>Enter your simple password in <a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a>, get a strong one, and use it for logging in.</li>
<li>Do not copy-paste strong generated passwords on your hard-disk, it is very insecure. Instead, whenever you need to login again, just get back to the fireword, and generate password again. <a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a> will always generate same strong password for same simple password you enter.

<h2>How to choose passwords?</h2></li>
<li>Instead of choosing ridiculously stupid passwords like &lsquo;password&rsquo;, you should choose little smarter passwords. Even if you are hardening your passwords with fireword, try choosing a better password.</li>
<li>Choose different passwords for different sites following some pattern, like</li>
<li>Use the name of the website for which you are generating password and use some words in front and end of it. Like
<strong> For facebook choose bluefacebookaccount
</strong> For google choose greengoogleaccount
<strong> Come up with your own patterns. You can even use your phone number, your name and the site name in the combo.
</strong> Convert the pattern with fireword, and get strongest password possible.
Amazing. Isn&rsquo;t it!<br/>
<strong>NOTE: Firefox and Chrome extensions are on their way. With them you&rsquo;ll not even need to visit firewordgen.herokuapp.com.</strong></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
