<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[harkuchh]]></title>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-26T00:11:28+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://harkuchh.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[harkuchh]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Tutorial Day 0: Hello Python! Nice to Meet Yea!]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/python-tutorial-day-0-hello-python-nice-to-meet-yea/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-25T22:37:45+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/python-tutorial-day-0-hello-python-nice-to-meet-yea</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello friends,</p>

<p>As promised here we are starting a Python tutorial series. This will go 2 week long, including 14 tutorials. Can you learn Python only in 2 weeks? No you can&rsquo;t. Teaching you everything Python has to offer is not the objective of this series. I am aiming for those who are brand new to programming, and want to introduce programming to them gently. Please read the <a href="http://harkuchh.com/announcing-2-week-python-tutorial-series/">announcement</a> for more details about the series.</p>

<p>I deeply apologize for the delay in publishing this post. Many funny things are going on around me nowadays. They have started development work in harkuchh, I had my own projects I was bootstrapping and my relations with harkuchh are on shaky grounds. This series might be the last I write on this blog, but I will finish it before leaving.</p>

<p>Let&rsquo;s not waste time and start with our day 0 of learning Python. From the title you might have already guessed, there will be 15 tutorials in total. This one is meant for setting up the Python interpreter so that you can easily write and run Python programs on your own machine. We will also discus some basic terminology related to programming and there will of course be the traditional <code>hello world</code>. Don&rsquo;t skip on reading this one considering it a filler. If you are coming from the world of languages like PHP, C family languages or Java etc, there are some new things for you to grok.</p>

<h2>Installing Python</h2>

<p>You need to know about versions of Python before you install Python. Python has 2 major versions: 2.x (latest 2.7.6) and 3.x (latest 3.3.4). Those new to Python often get confused which one they should use. There are obvious benefits of Python 3.x over 2.x, but I recommend you to download and install 2.x. There are too many reasons to mention here. I am using 2.7 on my machine, so I recommend you to install a 2.x version (whichever is latest on the site) just to keep up with the programs we will write in this series.</p>

<h3>Windows</h3>

<p>It&rsquo;s very easy for MS Windows users to install Python on their machines. Since Windows is built as an idiot-proof operating system, there are click and install packages (aka setups) available. Follow these steps.</p>

<ul>
<li>Go to the <a href="http://www.python.org/download/releases/">official python download site</a></li>
<li>Download the latest 2.x package for windows from the site</li>
<li>It&rsquo;s a traditional windows installer which will guide you through the installation.</li>
<li>Just run the installer and go through &lsquo;next&rsquo; clicks to install</li>
<li>That&rsquo;s all you need for now</li>
</ul>


<h3>Linux</h3>

<p>If you are using some variant of Linux, cheer up as Python is most likely already installed on your system. Most Linux systems come preinstalled with a 2.x version of Python.</p>

<p>But there is one extra goodie packaged with Windows installed that is that is not installed in Linux by default. It&rsquo;s called IDLE. We&rsquo;ll talk about it in a minute. You can easily install it with the package manager of your distro.</p>

<h2>Running Python</h2>

<p>You most likely now have Python installed on your system which is ready to roll. Python has something new for those who code in more traditional languages. If you are using Windows, go to the Start Menu and search of <code>Python IDLE</code>. Idle is a simple GUI Python IDE which is meant for aiding new Python devs to get started quickly. If you are a Linux user and have not install Idle, you can just shoot out your terminal and enter <code>python</code>. A python shell will be spawned for you.</p>

<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/GSCB4bj.jpg" alt="Idle shell" /></p>

<p>What you are seeing in above snapshot is the Python Shell. Python provides a shell (also called REPL) to help making programs interactively. It&rsquo;s fun to use and you will use it for making almost every Python program for some time.</p>

<p>You can type in any valid Python statement in there, and press Enter. Python will execute that statement, prints the output and ask you for entering more. That&rsquo;s why it is called REPL (Read Eval Process Loop). The shell reads every single line you enter in there, it evaluate that line, process the task you give it, and Loops for more input.</p>

<p>At this moment we have not learned any Python code yet, but you can try basic calcualtions like <code>5+5</code> or anything. You can also write your name in <code>'</code> or <code>"</code>. It will simply evaluate it, print result and ask for more.</p>

<p><strong>print</strong> statement: This is the first thing generally taught to new programmers. I won&rsquo;t break the tradition. <code>print</code> statement in Python is used to print anything on the screen. Like if you want to print your name, just write <code>print "My name"</code>. Yes, for printing a sentence, it is required to put in inside <code>'</code> or <code>"</code>s.</p>

<p>Play around with repl more if you want.</p>

<h2><code>Hello world</code> program in Python</h2>

<p>We will close today&rsquo;s tutorial with the <code>hello world</code> program in Python. REPL allows us to execute statements interactively, but when writing actual programs, we need to save them in files for executing later. Traditionally, python programs are written in files with extension <code>.py</code>. We will talk about them some other day.</p>

<p>Let&rsquo;s quickly wrap up and write our &lsquo;hello world&rsquo; program.</p>

<p>I told you Idle is actually a simple IDE (Interactive Development Environment) for Python. It allows you to create Python programs, and run them from right inside the Idle. Open a new file in Idle:<br/>
* Go to <code>File</code> Menu
* Click <code>New File</code> (or whatever new option is there, sorry I am using Linux right now)</p>

<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/kFEuTAA.png?1" alt="Python Idle New File Hello world" /></p>

<p>It will open a new window. Note that this windows is not an interactive shell. You can write multiple statements in it and they will not automatically execute. We will write our <code>hello world</code> program in it.</p>

<p>You might have already guessed it. Our program is just one single statement.</p>

<figure class='code'><figcaption><span>hello_world.py </span></figcaption>
<div class="highlight"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre class="line-numbers"><span class='line-number'>1</span>
</pre></td><td class='code'><pre><code class='python'><span class='line'><span class="k">print</span> <span class="s">&quot;Hello world!&quot;</span>
</span></code></pre></td></tr></table></div></figure>


<p>Write above line in the window, and save it with any name and <code>.py</code> extension.</p>

<p><code>.py</code> files can be executed in Windows by simply double clicking on them. But we will execute this one from right inside the Idle. Just press <code>F5</code> key. The output of our program will be shown in the Python shell (the other window).</p>

<p>That&rsquo;s it for today.</p>

<p><em><strong>Note:</strong> I wrote this one in a sort of rush because I didn&rsquo;t want to delay it any further. There were readers coming back to harkuchh for this tutorial series and going back disappointed. If you don&rsquo;t understand anything, or find something hard to understand, or something doesn&rsquo;t work, or for any kind of queries, please leave a comment.</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing 2 Week Python Tutorial Series]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/announcing-2-week-python-tutorial-series/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-20T16:33:03+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/announcing-2-week-python-tutorial-series</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Few days back we shared our experience about how we utilize the Python programming language in our work at harkuchh blogging valley. We got very positive interest about it and readers requested tutorials about the Python programming language.</p>

<p>So here I am with the announcement of the python tutorial series on harkcuhh.com.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>2 week tutorial series</h2>

<p>I have drafted a roadmap for a tutorial of 2 weeks. We&rsquo;ll publish Python tutorials here and continue for 2 weeks. There will be 14 tutorials, one for each day. You might be thinking if it is possible to master Python in 2 weeks. It is not. Mastering anything takes time. My aim here is to teach you to start thinking in Python. So that you can open any tutorial over there and make sense of it.</p>

<p>I suppose thing which would be rolling in your head would be something like &ldquo;How much Python will I learn from this tutorial?&rdquo;. There are not actual metrics to know how much of a language you know, but you will learn enough to continue on your own, or to follow more advanced tutorials that I will do after this one.</p>

<p>This series is meant for absolute beginners, who know little to no programming. We will emphasize more on basics and the thought process one needs to solve problems the Python way.</p>

<p>We will start with a very gentle introduction to the Python programming language, and will raise the bar with every tutorial. We will discuss the general programming problems which are taught in most programming classes, just to showcase how easy it is to do same things with Python. It will enable you to do comparison between other languages and Python if you follow some other course in some other programming language.</p>

<p>My reason for starting this series on harkuchh.com is more than teaching some folks programming. Programming is heavily under-rated in our city Chandigarh. Tech scene in the city is daunting. No enthusiastic community, no user groups, and dominance of PHP. It&rsquo;s a nightmare. This should change. I want to build a community of programmers. I want to discover the hidden gems in our blogging community. There are many smart people in this community, who I think can make brilliant programmers.</p>

<h3>Who&rsquo;s the targeted audience?</h3>

<p>As Krishan has told me, primary readers of harkuchh.com are bloggers, not much acquainted with programming. I want to usher those guys to the world of programming, without being hard on their brains. It will be a fun trip.</p>

<h3>How much time you should give to the tutorial?</h3>

<p>It will <strong>not</strong> be a very fast paced or heavily technical tutorial. I am aiming for teaching enough programming that you&rsquo;ll be able to do some fun things yourself, and will be able to pursue deeper tutorials.</p>

<h3>What you will and what you will not learn</h3>

<p>You&rsquo;ll not be able to do magic with just reading these 14 tutorials. At the end of Day 14, you will be able to make sense of any Python tutorial. And depending on how smart you are and with how much dedication you follow this series, you shall be able to automate several of you day-to-day tasks (computer related of course). I won&rsquo;t make huge promises, but you potential is limited by you only. Work hard, love your work, and conquer the world.</p>

<p>Happy Hacking!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launching harkuchh.com/forums to Help Blogging Community]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/launching-harkuchh-dot-com-slash-forums-to-help-blogging-community/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-18T03:39:09+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/launching-harkuchh-dot-com-slash-forums-to-help-blogging-community</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello Friends,</p>

<p>Today I’m very glad to announce that me and my harkuchh team is all set to launch our <a href="http://harkuchh.com/forums/">harkuchh forums</a>. We have been doing a hell of experiments since Charanjit has joined harkuchh. We were playing with this idea of building a community for bloggers. A community that will not suck blood. A community that is not <a href="http://harkuchh.com/corporate-society-is-fraud-bitch-please/">Corporate Society</a>. We envisioned a community that will help each other grow.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p> <br/>
The blogging culture we’ve all been a part for so long is depressing. Good content not getting what it deserve, and spam rolling everywhere; ruining the good work of many. It sucks. Those who create quality content should not suffer. I believe everything stopping a quality blogger from rising is a sin on the spammer’s head who is responsible for his demise.</p>

<p>We tried many things and now we are settled with what I’m here to announce. Things may change in future depending on the response from community; life is an experiment after all.</p>

<p>Ok then, now some questions will come to your mind, which is obvious. Questions like, Harkuchh Forums! But why? What it will do?  Questions like this may tease you, so here I’m explaining the reason behind the origination of Harkuchh forums.</p>

<p>Around two years back I started blogging with my very first blog Harkuchh.com. That time I was unaware of blogging and all other related things like Domain, Hosting, Ranking, Search Engine, Algorithm updates, Penguin, Panda, Humming Bird, SEO, Spam, Quality Post, Backlinks etc etc. I used to ask for help from various bloggers through their blogs comment boxes and facebook messages and they barely gave their time to respond to those message.</p>

<p>When I realized nobody will care to you untill you become something by your own and then I started reading, trying and implementing. Nobody was around to tell me what I’m doing wrong or what I’m doing right.</p>

<p>Blogging was like a big desert where I was familiar with nothing and wherever I turned there was something unknown and complex. I was like the only who had to survive, thankfully I proved myself Bear Grills :P Just kidding.</p>

<p>I mean I’m really thankful to the God that somehow I learnt many things of blogging from sources I don’t remember today but I can never forget Google and YouTube, with these two biggest platforms it was impossible for me to reach wherever I’m today. But it took a long, very long while to reach this place.</p>

<p>So,</p>

<p>As I’ve gone through all this and I know the pain of no result and no answers from people whom we expect to get a genuine reply, I thought of making a platform or a community where people can ask and share their blogging experience, queries with the people from the same world of Blogging. And here is the&hellip;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tricks to Search Amazing Things With Google]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/tricks-to-search-amazing-things-with-google-syntax/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-17T18:54:25+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/tricks-to-search-amazing-things-with-google-syntax</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This gonna be a long post, but I bet you won&rsquo;t want to miss a single word. Krishan tried to convince me to break it into 4 different posts by giving multiple references from all his blogging &lsquo;knowledge&rsquo; (here&rsquo;s a pun if you can get it), but I din&rsquo;t agree. Quality of content is more important imo.</p>

<p>Here I am telling best of the tricks I use to get what I want from Google. They are fun. If you have some more you think I should know, please mention in comments. Enjoy!</p>

<!-- more    -->


<h2>Exclude all results of a website</h2>

<p>So many times we need to search something but results from some spammy website clutter all search results. Search with following query to remove results from a particular website</p>

<blockquote><p> -site:&ldquo;spamy_site_name.com&rdquo;</p></blockquote>

<p>e.g</p>

<blockquote><p> big bang theory episode -site:youtube.com</p></blockquote>

<p>Above query will remove all results of youtube.com.</p>

<h3>How it work</h3>

<p>You know already if would have read my last post about Google Syntax. There are two things working here.</p>

<ul>
<li>&ldquo;&ndash;&#8221;<br/>
The minus(&lsquo;&ndash;&rsquo;) sign tells google to exclude results of the query directly after it.</li>
<li>site:<br/>
This tells google the website to be excluded</li>
</ul>


<h2>Direct download anything</h2>

<p>We all love downloading free music, right? But discovering music has become a tedious task with all those spam sites punching ads in our faces.<br/>
Here&rsquo;s a trick to get to direct links of songs on a website. Search for the following query and replace desired fields to get direct links (most of the time):</p>

<blockquote><p>intitle:&ldquo;index of&rdquo; mp3 wadali brothers</p></blockquote>

<p>You can replace anything after and including &lsquo;mp3&rsquo;.<br/>
In my school days I created a bot to download porn using this technique. I had one hell of a porn collection back then. I still curse me for deleting it :&ndash;/</p>

<h3>How it work</h3>

<p>This trick uses the fact that people on Internet are not actually all smart. There are pretty stupid people around here.</p>

<p>What we are actually doing here is that we are not searching for any pages created by site developer, but for the default pages which server generates for filesystem access over Http. Don&rsquo;t worry if you didn&rsquo;t get it.</p>

<p>Try opening something like &ldquo;file:///&rdquo;. There is no web page over there, but your browser might be showing you a list of files. This is exactly what we are searching for, a page with direct access to the folder on server where &lsquo;mp3&rsquo; are saved.</p>

<h3>Beware of spam</h3>

<p>I am not the only one who know this trick. Spammers know it very well too. This query will work without a glitch for uncommon terms (like &lsquo;wadali brothers&rsquo;) which are not very popular. But if you search for something remotely famous (or too general like hindi songs), you will find herds of spam sites rolling on your site.</p>

<h3>Detect spam</h3>

<p>How can you differentiate b/w spam page and real page you are looking for?<br/>
Well, as I said, we are not actually looking for any page at all. So if you see anything stylish (like colors, styles, ads, sidebars), it&rsquo;s not a real page. Real thing we are looking for do not have anything but white background, black text, blue links (violet visited links), a header and an untitled list. Nothing more.</p>

<h3>How to Avoid spam</h3>

<ul>
<li><p><strong>Use the previous technique of excluding all results from a website</strong><br/>
Just keep adding <code>-site:spamsite.com</code> for every spam site you don&rsquo;t want to see.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Avoid too general queries</strong><br/>
Try to search for something specific like the song name or singer name. It works to a limit though. If you are searching for something very popular, spam is there waiting for you.</p></li>
</ul>


<h2>Download books and documents</h2>

<p>This one is my favorite. I read a lot of books. So of course I download a lot of them. This technique can actually be used to download any kind of document available in some specific file extension.</p>

<blockquote><p>ext:pdf how to think like computer scientist python</p></blockquote>

<p>And there you get direct links to the pdf file. You can replace &lsquo;pdf&rsquo; with &lsquo;doc&rsquo;,&lsquo;odf&rsquo;,&lsquo;epub&rsquo; or any other format. You will likely meet less spam in this dimension, but there are times when you&rsquo;ll not find a book. Publicly available free books will generally be there though.</p>

<h3>How it work</h3>

<p>It search for files with specific file extension. Duh! How else it might be working?</p>

<h2>View public cameras</h2>

<p>You can search cameras which have public access. I mean you can get access to the video stream of some publicly available video cameras. Sometimes there are controls available as well for controlling cameras.</p>

<p>You can look through cameras placed in many places like traffic lights, shopping stores, offices and even home cameras sometime.
You need to search for special queries for this. They are kinda hard to remember, so even I&rsquo;ve made a list of those queries.</p>

<h3>How it work</h3>

<p>It&rsquo;s same technique as &lsquo;direct download anything&rsquo;. We are searching for some &lsquo;special&rsquo; pages on the net that Google has (by mistake?) crawled.</p>

<script type="text/javascript">

</script>


<h3>List of queries for watching online cameras</h3>

<ul>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=inurl:%E2%80%9DViewerFrame?Mode=">inurl:”ViewerFrame?Mode=</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:Axis%202400%20video%20server">intitle:Axis 2400 video server</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=inurl:/view.shtml">inurl:/view.shtml</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:%E2%80%9DLive%20View%20/%20%E2%80%93%20AXIS%E2%80%9D%20|%20inurl:view/view.shtml^">intitle:”Live View / – AXIS” | inurl:view/view.shtml^</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=inurl:ViewerFrame?Mode=">inurl:ViewerFrame?Mode=</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=inurl:ViewerFrame?Mode=Refresh">inurl:ViewerFrame?Mode=Refresh</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=inurl:axis-cgi/jpg">inurl:axis-cgi/jpg</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=inurl:axis-cgi/mjpg">inurl:axis-cgi/mjpg </a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=inurl:view/indexFrame.shtml">inurl:view/indexFrame.shtml</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=inurl:view/index.shtml">inurl:view/index.shtml</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=inurl:view/view.shtml">inurl:view/view.shtml</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=liveapplet">liveapplet</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:%E2%80%9Dlive%20view%E2%80%9D%20intitle:axis">intitle:”live view” intitle:axis</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:liveapplet">intitle:liveapplet</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=allintitle:%E2%80%9DNetwork%20Camera%20NetworkCamera%E2%80%9D">allintitle:”Network Camera NetworkCamera”</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:axis%20intitle:%E2%80%9Dvideo%20server%E2%80%9D">intitle:axis intitle:”video server”</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:liveapplet%20inurl:LvAppl">intitle:liveapplet inurl:LvAppl</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:%E2%80%9DEvoCam%E2%80%9D%20inurl:%E2%80%9Dwebcam.html%E2%80%9D">intitle:”EvoCam” inurl:”webcam.html”</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:%E2%80%9DLive%20NetSnap%20Cam-Server%20feed%E2%80%9D">intitle:”Live NetSnap Cam-Server feed”</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:%E2%80%9DLive%20View%20/%20%E2%80%93%20AXIS%E2%80%9D">intitle:”Live View / – AXIS”</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:%E2%80%9DLive%20View%20/%20%E2%80%93%20AXIS%20206M%E2%80%9D">intitle:”Live View / – AXIS 206M”</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:%E2%80%9DLive%20View%20/%20%E2%80%93%20AXIS%20206W%E2%80%9D">intitle:”Live View / – AXIS 206W”</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:%E2%80%9DLive%20View%20/%20%E2%80%93%20AXIS%20210%E2%80%B3">intitle:”Live View / – AXIS 210″</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=inurl:indexFrame.shtml%20Axis">inurl:indexFrame.shtml Axis</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=inurl:%E2%80%9DMultiCameraFrame?Mode=Motion%E2%80%9D">inurl:”MultiCameraFrame?Mode=Motion”</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:start%20inurl:cgistart">intitle:start inurl:cgistart</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:%E2%80%9DWJ-NT104%20Main%20Page%E2%80%9D">intitle:”WJ-NT104 Main Page”</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intext:%E2%80%9DMOBOTIX%20M1%E2%80%B3%20intext:%E2%80%9DOpen%20Menu%E2%80%9D">intext:”MOBOTIX M1″ intext:”Open Menu”</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intext:%E2%80%9DMOBOTIX%20M10%E2%80%B3%20intext:%E2%80%9DOpen%20Menu%E2%80%9D">intext:”MOBOTIX M10″ intext:”Open Menu”</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intext:%E2%80%9DMOBOTIX%20D10%E2%80%B3%20intext:%E2%80%9DOpen%20Menu%E2%80%9D">intext:”MOBOTIX D10″ intext:”Open Menu”</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:snc-z20%20inurl:home/">intitle:snc-z20 inurl:home/</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:snc-cs3%20inurl:home/">intitle:snc-cs3 inurl:home/</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:snc-rz30%20inurl:home/">intitle:snc-rz30 inurl:home/</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:%E2%80%9Dsony%20network%20camera%20snc-p1%E2%80%B3">intitle:”sony network camera snc-p1″</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:%E2%80%9Dsony%20network%20camera%20snc-m1%E2%80%B3">intitle:”sony network camera snc-m1″</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=site:.viewnetcam.com%20-www.viewnetcam.com">site:.viewnetcam.com -www.viewnetcam.com</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:%E2%80%9DToshiba%20Network%20Camera%E2%80%9D%20user%20login">intitle:”Toshiba Network Camera” user login</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:%E2%80%9Dnetcam%20live%20image%E2%80%9D">intitle:”netcam live image”</a></li>
<li><a href="https://encrypted.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=intitle:%E2%80%9Di-Catcher%20Console%20%E2%80%93%20Web%20Monitor%E2%80%9D">intitle:”i-Catcher Console – Web Monitor”</a></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Firefox Plugins I Can't Live Without]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/5-firefox-plugins-i-cant-live-without/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-16T08:01:47+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/5-firefox-plugins-i-cant-live-without</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I use Firefox as my primary web browser. I have emotional attachments with Mozilla and their <a href="https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/mission/">mission</a>. I used Chrome for sometime, but I ditched it for some reasons. Firefox make me feel more like home. The philosophical bond of trust is a big thing for me.</p>

<p>Here&rsquo;s a list of top 5 Firefox addons I use daily. Whenever I switch to a new machine, installing these is generally the first thing I do.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h3><a href="https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/addon/fxchrome">FxChrome</a></h3>

<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/b7MQxEu.png" alt="FxChrome Firefox plugin" />
FxChrome is a Chrome like theme for Firefox. Firefox is cool, but it doesn&rsquo;t look that cool. By default I mean. This theme make Firefox look like Chrome, while keeping all Mozilla goodness.</p>

<h3><a href="https://wappalyzer.com/">Wappalyzer</a></h3>

<p>Wappalyzer is a browser extension that identifies the technologies used on websites. Whenever I see a good site, first thing that come to mind is what technologies are these guys using?</p>

<p>Wappalyzer save me a lot of work. It shows the technologies used by the sites in the address bar. So whenever I visit a website, it tells me things like they are using Wordpress, jQuery, Google Analytics and other technologies.</p>

<h3><a href="http://www.ghostery.com/">Ghostery</a></h3>

<p>Ghostery is for my paranoid self. It stop websites from tracking me. Ghostery detects and stop all sort of trackers used on websites, from analytics to social media widgets. I used to use AdBlock Plus as well earlier, but now I use Ghostery only.<br/>
After all ads are the reason why content on Internet is free. Ghostery protects my privacy while I am still able to support publishers.</p>

<h3><a href="http://trac.arantius.com/wiki/Extensions/Resurrect">Resurrect Pages</a></h3>

<p>Web pages go down all the time. It happen a lot with me that I visit some website and it&rsquo;s down. Resurrect pages help resurrecting the dead (pages) using various archiving sites of the web. Whenever I visit a dead page, it shows a list of archives, and I can choose to visit a snapshot of the page from there.</p>

<h3><a href="https://www.pushbullet.com">PushBullet</a></h3>

<p>You&rsquo;ll understand the value of PushBullet only if you use the PushBullet app on your Android phone. PushBullet help me share content between my phone and my browser. I send all sort of things with it to my phone, would it be the todo list of things I need to do when I go out of my home (that actually happen very rarely), or links to articles I want to read on phone when lying in bed or notes etc.</p>

<p>And for some reason my brain start producing awesome ideas when I am about to sleep, and there is no time to start my computer to note them. Then I just start my phone, and send those ideas to my computer as notes. It&rsquo;s a really useful app.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Bloggers Need to Save Themselves From Google: Lesson We Got After Losing 400K]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/why-bloggers-need-to-save-themselves-from-google-lesson-we-got-after-losing-400k/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-12T23:56:09+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/why-bloggers-need-to-save-themselves-from-google-lesson-we-got-after-losing-400k</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Google is no more that same open company which had ‘<a href="http://www.zdnet.com/blog/foremski/google-drops-dont-be-evil-motto/435">don’t be evil</a>’ as their slogan.<br/>
Google is evil. We all know it.</p>

<p>But Google can be particularly evil to you if you are a blogger. Being a blogger, most of your living depends on Google one way or other. Google is a major traffic source, all information you need come through Google, and Google Adsense is major source of most blogger’s income. Imagine Google having a grudge against you. I mean against you, as a person in particular. Everything you do is seen with a skeptical eye, and suddenly your websites which were rolling few days back are now ruins facing drought of visitors.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>
Yes, Google can do it, and it does.</p>

<h2>Our Experience</h2>

<p>We at Harkuchh &ndash; The Blogging Valley were unfortunate enough to face the fury of Google. We have multiple blogs here, some good and some not so good. And we are always doing all sort of experiments to try new things. Few months back, we were working as always and things were going as breeze. Then Krishan started a test project, a kind of illegitimate blog. It was an experiment. We spent very little time on it, and it was just lying around in some corner, with Krishan occasionally working on it.</p>

<p>Few weeks after starting that experiment, we started facing problems in getting traffic to our websites. For some reason, all of our websites were facing more than 50% fall in traffic. Even the best quality posts which have backlinks on high PR sites stopped appearing on Google search results. It was incomprehensible. What could we have done wrong to bring this on us? And few days later another nightmare came true. Our Google adsense account got disabled, with no clarification of course. With it went our Rs 400+K sum. All that was left was shattered plans, unbalanced budget and minds full of confusion.</p>

<h2>The Mistake</h2>

<p>You guessed it right. That experiment was the mistake. But it was not at all clear at that time. There was not a single link that could tell any connection between our legitimate blogs and that experiment blog. We do extra effort to not to link our blogs with each other in any way. Then how could Google tell that experiment blog belonged to us? How could it be that all our genuine blogs were suffering Google’s rage?</p>

<p>The real mistake was not that we somehow made some connection between the experiment and some of our real blogs. Because there was no connection. We cross-checked many times.</p>

<p>There was actually no mistake. Things should not have been the way they were.</p>

<h2>The Lesson</h2>

<p>As we noticed later, the only thing that could have resulted in connection was a Google account. What Krishan did was that he used same Google account for analytics and webmaster tools which was also used on our other blogs. But he didn’t use the adsense on the experiment. <br/>
I know Google tracking everyone on Internet is not a new story, but this was new for us. This had never happened before. Google is now making connections between different sites you own. Any one site you run can affect your other sites as well.</p>

<p>So our suggestion is, if you are going to try something crazy never ever use same Google accounts in any way on different sites. It would be even better if you
operate on your experiments in sandboxed environments. That’s what we are doing now. And it’s working, for now at least.</p>

<p>So better save your ass from Google. It’s no longer our all good friend.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I Am Learning Python]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/why-i-am-learning-python/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-11T23:16:11+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/why-i-am-learning-python</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Why I&rsquo;m learning Python? well yes, this is really a very valid question and it has a solid answer too, I think everybody should read this, not because I&rsquo;ve written this for you but because it has much much importance and advantages for you.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Some days back, I was in my office with my friend Channi (Charanjit Singh) we were planning to work on a website for a special purpose. While talking I said him that, “on this website we&rsquo;ll need to do same thing again and again hundreds of time and it will take lots of our time and effort :(“. Then he said &ldquo;Don&rsquo;t worry dude, I&rsquo;ll make a script that will automate all this thing and then you will need to do that only once and rest will be done by the script.”</p>

<p>I was surprised and like, is it possible? He said &ldquo;Yeah dude, it&rsquo;s simple and will not take too long to be developed&rdquo; then I told him to do it fast, and I started writing a post on my movie blog and when I published only one post He said &ldquo;Done bro! here it is.&rdquo;</p>

<p>I said &ldquo;seriously, will it do all those things which I was talking about?&rdquo; I got the best reply, it was &lsquo;off course!&rsquo;.</p>

<p>I said let&rsquo;s see, and unbelievably it done all those things in just minutes, any person who have no knowledge of coding and programming will never believe that the things which required at least 1 week day and night work was done in just minutes. I was shocked! and said to my friend, “Awesome bro, how did you do it”, he replied &ldquo;Python bro, it&rsquo;s awesome&rdquo;.</p>

<p>Till then I just knew that Python is a programming language but I didn&rsquo;t know anything about its working or coding. Actually I didn&rsquo;t know any coding or programming language. Not even C++ in which I spent all four years of my B.tech degree.</p>

<p>So when I heard Python, I didn&rsquo;t take even a second to say, “bro! can&rsquo;t I learn Python?”</p>

<p>“Of course you can”, he said. “But you will need to be regular on it”, he added.</p>

<p>I replied joyfully “of course I will, it will be great if I can do things in minute(s) for which I give hours, days and even weeks to complete, so let&rsquo;s start it now.”</p>

<p>He said No! We will start it from tommorow, let me prepare modules and a structure for teaching Python in the best way to you. And next day we started.</p>

<p>And now, just after a week.. Even I cannot believe that now I can do many things with my own created crawlers which none of you can do even in weeks, please note, I&rsquo;m not showing off here but I&rsquo;m just trying to tell, how much difference simple coding are able to create.</p>

<p>Let me share an example with you so that you can get my words better, previously I used to copy contents of events websites manually in which I needed to..</p>

<ul>
<li><p>Go to a website</p></li>
<li><p>Open a post</p></li>
<li><p>Create a new text file (to copy post)</p></li>
<li><p>Copy posts title from that website</p></li>
<li><p>Paste that into text file</p></li>
<li><p>Copy body of the post</p></li>
<li><p>Paste that into text file again</p></li>
<li><p>Copy keywords, description and tags from source code</p></li>
<li><p>Paste them into text file</p></li>
</ul>


<p>&hellip;and these all steps were required for every post and imagine if there were 100 posts on that site it simply means I needed to do these all things 100 times to get everything in my hand, most of you are doing same, I know. But..</p>

<p>today, I just take some minutes to create a crawler for any specific website and run it, after that crawler do all the rest thing in minutes. Any non technical person will never believe that, it copies posts at the rate of 500-600/minute with proper distinguish between every part of the post which includes title, body, images, keywords, tags, description, category and all related information which I think I require and I told, to to do same thing manually I required at least 2-3 days.</p>

<p>So this is the difference and that all is possible with a simple effort to learn python. That is why I&rsquo;m learning Python.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five Reasons Why Every Blogger Should Learn Programming]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/five-reasons-for-why-you-should-learn-programming/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-07T23:47:12+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/five-reasons-for-why-you-should-learn-programming</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In this post I am writing about why every blogger (and every person in general) should learn to code. Programming as itself is an asset that will make you a better and smarter person. Most important benefit you&rsquo;ll get is the ability to make <strong>literate decisions</strong>. You&rsquo;ll learn how to break down that large problem you are facing, and how to solve it&rsquo;s one piece at a time. Besides, it gives ou great level of confidence.<br/>
Here are five reasons to convince you to learn programming.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>You want to be a God</h2>

<p>I heard yea! So you wanna be a God? Well, you can be actually. Programmers are mini Gods who create little worlds with their programs and control everything. Literally. It&rsquo;s hard to understand this feeling without really experiencing it. But the ultimate control building a software offers is addictive. I myself was a gaming addict in my school time, and now gaming addiction is turned into coding addiction.</p>

<p>The amount of automation you can put in your daily work truly make you feel like a God. It makes me feel real good when I see my script running and think my code can do in 30 minutes what my peers at harkuchh would have taken 4-5 days.</p>

<h2>One blogger who know coding equals ten average bloggers</h2>

<p>Don&rsquo;t get hyper. Let me explain why. Programming skills are valuable in every field directly or remotely related to computers and internet off course.I mean your programming skills become specially important in fields which are completely dependent on computers and Internet. Blogging is such a case. I joined Harkuchh &ndash; The Blogging Valley about a month ago, and the technological improvements we&rsquo;ve made here improved our productivity while brought down the expenses. Although many things are under experiment phase, the time we&rsquo;ve saved so far which would have been wasted in trying things which don&rsquo;t bring any profit is enormous.</p>

<p>To give an example, consider data gathering. We all need to collect data from various sources, many times it involve just copy pasting data from some other source. We&rsquo;ve built a software to automate such things, and saved days of work.</p>

<p>But there are more benefits than I can describe here. Enough benefits that Krishan Kummar (founder of harkuchh.com) is learning to code. (We are thinking about starting giving programming classes to bloggers. Please comment or mail us if you are interested).</p>

<h2>Dream, Believe, Achieve</h2>

<p>These quotes all seem too good to be practical in real world. This might be true, but not in the world where you can even be a God. You just wish if there was a software which would do <em>something awesome here</em>, and you roll out your emacs (or your favorite editor), and voila! It&rsquo;s there. Anything is possible, all you need to do is to believe in your wit and skills. Sounds too good to be real? Welcome to the world of programmers :)</p>

<h2>It teaches you to make better decisions in life</h2>

<p>I just can&rsquo;t emphasize how beneficial it is for anyone (including you bloggers) to have some programming skills. Even if you don&rsquo;t become a wiz, acquaintance with programming is a very much helpful. When you don&rsquo;t know anything about how your websites and software are actually working under-the-hood, you are like riding a bike eye-folded. You either hit a tree or something, or you go too slow.</p>

<p>Most important benefit you&rsquo;ll get is the ability to make <strong>literate decisions</strong>. You&rsquo;ll learn how to break down that large problem you are facing, and how to solve it&rsquo;s one piece at a time. Besides, it give you great level of confidence. When you think of a crazy idea, and you have good programming skills under your belt, you quickly analyze all the steps which you&rsquo;ll need to take to make that awesome thing. You carry this habit to your real life. And suddenly all things become simple, because you&rsquo;ll quickly analyze everything and sort out plans for doing things which seem impossible or very hard to others. It&rsquo;ll give you a new perspective in your career, as well as in your life.</p>

<h2>Programming is fun, and it makes you smarter</h2>

<p>I ditched gaming for coding, not because it give me money, but simply because it&rsquo;s more fun. I still play games once in a while when I want my brain to relax, but I&rsquo;m yet to find a game which&rsquo;ll give me more thrill than coding. If you follow the right steps (like choose right first language, right teacher, right things to do in your first steps in coding world), programming is like playing a very powerful computer game. Projects you do are your highscore and skills you gain are your reward, that&rsquo;ll stay with you for rest of your life. Besides, remember all your kids (the next generation) will be taught coding in schools like we are taught poems, then your children will ask you questions related to coding, what you gonna do then? ;)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strong Passwords, Weak Passwords: How to Generate Strongest Possible Passwords Which You Can Remember]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/strong-passwords-weak-passwords-how-to-generate-strongest-possible-passwords-which-you-can-remember/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-04T00:46:09+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/strong-passwords-weak-passwords-how-to-generate-strongest-possible-passwords-which-you-can-remember</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Passwords we know, the most common method used by almost all websites for authenticating users. But how good is this method? Well, the strength of this method partially depend on the strength of the password we choose.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>What&rsquo;s the strength of a password?</h2>

<p>Strength of a password is determined by a number of things.
* <strong>Character set</strong><br/>
Most important thing which make a password strong is its character set. Character set of a password means which characters are used in the password, like lower case characters, upper case characters, numbers, symbols etc. A password which has all different type of characters is considered stronger.
* <strong>Length of the password</strong><br/>
Second most important thing about strong passwords is their length. Longer passwords are considered more secure.
* <strong>Guessability of the password</strong><br/>
Another thing which determine strength of password is of easy it is to guess a password. Easier to guess passwords are weak. A security researcher has said that <a href="http://www.troyhunt.com/2011/03/only-secure-password-is-one-you-cant.html">any password  you can remember is not safe enough</a>.</p>

<h2>The problem</h2>

<p> So we have a problem here. They say any password we choose which we can remember is not safe enough. Most people choose easy, simple to remember password, which is perfectly reasonable. Why putting extra load on brain? But this laziness can cost more than you think.</p>

<h2><a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">The Solution</a></h2>

<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/Ujh8L6y.png" alt="Fireword password generator" /><br/>
 So I wanted a system which will create passwords for me which I can remember, but which can&rsquo;t be guessed or cracked easily. One solution to this is passphrases. For example, instead of choosing a single word password like &ldquo;facebook123&rdquo;, I choose a sentence like &ldquo;facebookhasbluecolor&rdquo;. And even better, change some character with symbols and numbers, &ldquo;f@c3b00kh4sBlu3C0lOr&rdquo;. Awesome, right! But it still can be remembered. So according to our theory that any password which can be remembered is not safe enough. I want something simple to remember and type and still very strong and long.
 So being a software developer, I made a system which do exactly this. I call it fireword.</p>

<h2>What is fireword?</h2>

<p> <a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a> is an application in which you enter a simple word or phrase, and it give you a very strong and impossible to guess password.</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a> always generate same password for same word. So you remember your simple password, and generate a strong one with this site. And then when you need to login again, regenerate strong password with your simple one.</li>
<li><a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a> allow you to select the length of the password. You can choose from 8 to 128 character long password.</li>
<li>For example, just entering &lsquo;facebook&rsquo; become this &lsquo;bF2A37d5e8%{61?C]>3E[{(9{&rsquo;. Any password can be expanded to at most 128 character long complex password.

<h2>Recommended ways to use <a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a></h2>

<p>It&rsquo;s really simple. Instead of using you easy to remember but weak password for a website, change your password with the password generated by fireword.</p></li>
<li>Enter your simple password in <a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a>, get a strong one, and use it for logging in.</li>
<li>Do not copy-paste strong generated passwords on your hard-disk, it is very insecure. Instead, whenever you need to login again, just get back to the fireword, and generate password again. <a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a> will always generate same strong password for same simple password you enter.

<h2>How to choose passwords?</h2></li>
<li>Instead of choosing ridiculously stupid passwords like &lsquo;password&rsquo;, you should choose little smarter passwords. Even if you are hardening your passwords with fireword, try choosing a better password.</li>
<li>Choose different passwords for different sites following some pattern, like</li>
<li>Use the name of the website for which you are generating password and use some words in front and end of it. Like
<strong> For facebook choose bluefacebookaccount
</strong> For google choose greengoogleaccount
<strong> Come up with your own patterns. You can even use your phone number, your name and the site name in the combo.
</strong> Convert the pattern with fireword, and get strongest password possible.
Amazing. Isn&rsquo;t it!<br/>
<strong>NOTE: Firefox and Chrome extensions are on their way. With them you&rsquo;ll not even need to visit firewordgen.herokuapp.com.</strong></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Fledge Guide on TLD's - What Is Top Level Domain(s)]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/full-fledge-guide-on-tlds-what-is-top-level-domain-s/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-31T02:31:05+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/full-fledge-guide-on-tlds-what-is-top-level-domain-s</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Top level domain which is also abbrebiated as TLD is the very last segment of any domain name, every domain&rsquo;s last part is simply called as TLD. The TLD is the letters immediately following the final dot in an Internet address i.e. any website url, for Instance in Harkuchh.com here .com is TLD of generic class (we will talk about TLD classes below). Most generally TLD is use to identifies something about a website is associated with, like its purpose, the organization that owns it or the geographical area from where it has originates, and every type of TLD has a different registry which is being maintained by a designated organization the Internet Assigned Numbers Authority (IANA) under the direction of ICANN i.e. The Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>
To better understand TLD see our Internet address which is, <a href="http://Harkuchh.com">http://Harkuchh.com</a> now here com is the top-level domain name and Harkuchh is the second-level domain name and if a domain has anything even before second level domain then it is called as a subdomain. When these all merge together they build a fully qualified domain name (FQDN) the addition of <a href="HTTP://">HTTP://</a> makes an FQDN a complete URL.</p>

<h2><strong>Four (4) major categories of TLDs</strong></h2>

<p><strong>Generic top-level domains (gTLD)</strong> &mdash; These are the most used, common and familiar type of TLDs. Examples include &ldquo;com&rdquo; for &ldquo;commercial&rdquo;, &ldquo;org&rdquo; for &ldquo;organization&rdquo; and &ldquo;edu&rdquo; for &ldquo;educational.&rdquo; Most generic TLDs are open for everyone to register, but there is a subgroup that is more strictly controlled and that is not used broadly.</p>

<p><strong>Country-code top-level domains (ccTLD)</strong> &mdash; Each ccTLD identifies a particular country and every ccTLD is two letters long, for example we can see the ccTLD for India is .in and for United States is .us.</p>

<p><strong>Infrastructure top-level domain</strong> &mdash; This type is very often used class of TLD may be that is the reason there is only one TLD in this group, ARPA (Address and Routing Parameter Area). The Internet Assigned Numbers Authority (IANA) manages this TLD for the IETF.</p>

<p><strong>Sponsored top-level domains (sTLD)</strong>: These are overseen by private organizations.</p>

<p>ICANN Proposed an expansion of the TLD system to allow anyone to register and also reserve any spare unused letter sequence as a TLD for Their exclusive use, in April 2009. For example if a company who use to sell sotwares want to to use .Soft as a TLD then they can use it. According to <strong>ICANN chief executive Paul Levins</strong>, Such an extension would lead to thousands of new TLDs in the coming years.</p>

<p>Have any query? just leave a comment, you can also use <a href="http://harkuchh.com/forums" target="_blank"> Harkuchh Forums </a> for any help.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Google Like a Pro: Tips to Use Google Syntax]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-use-google-like-a-pro-tips-to-use-google-syntax/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-30T21:00:32+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-use-google-like-a-pro-tips-to-use-google-syntax</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I know you all use Google to reach everywhere on the Internet, but are you using it properly? Google actually provides a specific syntax for searching which is unknown to the masses. Also known as the Google operators, this syntax can make your Googling much easy and much less frustrating.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s specially useful for bloggers since all of us need to keep an eye on the Internet trends. It&rsquo;s very useful to know how to properly use our most used tool, that is Google.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>So let&rsquo;s waste less time an look at what Google has to offer for us.</p>

<h1>How to use Google syntax?</h1>

<p>All the search operators described here can be used by putting the operator in the search box followed by the search query. Like to use <strong>related:</strong> operator, following query will be used</p>

<pre><code>related:"harkuchh.com"
</code></pre>

<h2><em>related:</em> Search for related sites</h2>

<pre><code>related:"example.com"
</code></pre>

<p><em>related:</em> is used to search for websites which are similar to the website we provide in search box. When we use this operator, Google will search for any information related to the given website from all over the Internet. Google will show websites which have similar content.</p>

<h2><em>link:</em> Search for all pages that link to a particular url</h2>

<pre><code>link:"http://harkuchh.com/trick-to-copy-content-from-a-website-with-copy-protector-enabled/"
</code></pre>

<p>This operator will search for all the pages that link to the given url.</p>

<h2><em>site:</em> Search within a particular website only</h2>

<pre><code>"site:"harkuchh.com" blogging tips
</code></pre>

<p>Above query will only search &lsquo;harkuchh.com&rsquo; for the words &lsquo;blogging tips&rsquo;. This is a very useful operator. Just imagine when you need to find a particular post you once seen on a website but can&rsquo;t find a link to it. It&rsquo;s one of my most used operators.</p>

<h2>Search for an exact phrase or word</h2>

<p>When we search for a sentence on Google, it doesn&rsquo;t just search for that exact sentence.
Try searching for</p>

<pre><code>I will become dictator of the world
</code></pre>

<p>Google will search for text which have &lsquo;I&rsquo;, &lsquo;will&rsquo;, &lsquo;become&rsquo; etc anywhere on the page. But if we want to only search for pages which contain the complete sentence &ldquo;I will become dictator of the world&rdquo;, we can do it just by putting the whole sentence within quotes. Like this</p>

<pre><code>"I will become dictator of the world"
</code></pre>

<h2>Exclude something in the results</h2>

<p>Sometimes we want that some specific type of results should not appear in the search results. Google provide a special operator just for this purpose.<br/>
That is &lsquo;&ndash;&rsquo;.<br/>
Yes just that. Putting a &lsquo;&ndash;&rsquo; in front of any word will show results which do not have that word in them.
To make it even better, this work with other Google operators as well.</p>

<pre><code>hello lady how are you -season
</code></pre>

<p>Above query if searched without &lsquo;-season&rsquo; will show some youtube results about some seasons of some TV program. But running above query will remove those results which have the word &lsquo;season&rsquo; in them.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trick to Copy Content From a Website With Copy Protector Enabled]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/trick-to-copy-content-from-a-website-with-copy-protector-enabled/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-29T22:16:18+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/trick-to-copy-content-from-a-website-with-copy-protector-enabled</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Copy protector is a wordpress plugin which is used by many wordpress sites to stop readers from copying the site content. When you visit a site and find it good to share some part of it, this type of plugins irritate us the most. In these cases, you either share the whole page, or you don&rsquo;t share anything.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>There are many such plugins which prevent users from copying partial content from a website.
Here we have a solution to this problem.</p>

<p>The solution we are mentioning here work against all plugins which prevent copying content. This means you don&rsquo;t need to know which plugin is used by the website that is stopping you from copying, following solution simply work against anything.</p>

<h3>How do these plugins work?</h3>

<p>Although this is not necessary to stop those copy protector plugins, but having proper knowledge is a good thing.</p>

<p>What we see on a web page is HTML content which is styled with CSS stylesheets. HTML and CSS do not offer much programming power to do anything like stopping people from copying content.<br/>
But there is a third power on the webpage which is actually used for programming fancy things on a web page. Its called javascript.</p>

<p><strong>Javascript</strong> is a web scripting language that run in our browser, which can do many many awesome things. Preventing us from copying is one of them. So if we can somehow disable the execution of javascript in our browser, all those plugins which stop us from copying content will simply stop working.</p>

<h3>But how do we do it?</h3>

<p>In previous versions of most browsers, one setting was provided to switch off javascript. But not anymore. New browser no more provide this option since more and more websites are becoming javascript heavy and they simply do not work if javascript is disabled.<br/>
So we need a third party tool which can disable javascript in the browser.</p>

<h3>Browser plugins to the rescue</h3>

<p>Most browsers have addons or plugins which we can install in the browser. Various plugins are available to disable javascript in browsers. We can search the browser addon market and find many.</p>

<h4>Our favorite plugin for this purpose</h4>

<p><strong><a href="http://noscript.net/">No Script</a></strong></p>

<p><img src="https://doc-10-3s-docs.googleusercontent.com/docs/securesc/ha0ro937gcuc7l7deffksulhg5h7mbp1/eon6j3j90nlhk062379b2ms23gemsbrr/1391011200000/04897958604571837647/*/0B2snz8-UNBEmQVdKd201Y1M4UTA?h=16653014193614665626" alt="Trick to copy content from a website with Copy Protector enabled" /></p>

<p>The NoScript Firefox extension provides extra protection for Firefox browsers. It is free and open source add-on which allows JavaScript, Java, Flash and other plugins to be executed only by trusted web sites of your choice. NoScript also provides the most powerful anti-XSS and anti-Clickjacking protection ever available in a browser. <br/>
With noscript we can choose which site can execute javascript and which can&rsquo;t.</p>

<p><strong>So what we actually have to do?</strong></p>

<p>Just install noscript in firefox and follow the tutorial.</p>

<h2>Tutorial to copy content from a website with Copy Protector enabled</h2>

<p>Okay this is a really small tutorial here.<br/>
When you have noscript installed in firefox, there will appear an icon like this in your firefox window.</p>

<p>By default noscript do not allow any site to execute any javascript, java or flash code. So most sites will just stop working the way they usually do.</p>

<p>So first thing we have to do is disable the noscript gloablly.</p>

<ul>
<li>Click on the noscript icon and unselect &ldquo;Forbid Scripts globally&rdquo;.</li>
</ul>


<p>It will show a warning messag saying</p>

<p>&ldquo;Scripts are going to be allowed globally (for every site).
  This is a potentially dangerous action.
  Do you really want to proceed?&rdquo;</p>

<p>Just ignore it and press ok.</p>

<ul>
<li>Now open the site from which you want to copy content.</li>
<li>With that site&rsquo;s page open, again click on the no-script icon and select  &ldquo;Mark &lt;site-name> as Untrusted&rdquo;</li>
</ul>


<p>Doing this will auto-refresh the page and no-scripts will be run from that page. This means none of the copy blocking plugins will work.</p>

<p>So, that&rsquo;s what we wanted to achieve. If you have any questions and queries, please feel free to ask in comments. We also have forums where you can ask any question and me and our team will try to answer as per our knowledge.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corporate Society Is Fraud, Bitch Please !]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/corporate-society-is-fraud-bitch-please/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-05T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/corporate-society-is-fraud-bitch-please</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[You might have heard about Corporate, The <b>Corporate Infocom Pvt. Ltd</b> or <b>Corporate Society</b>, and if you have heard <b>about</b> <b>Corporate Society</b> then there are two strong possibilities that you may heard it’s a great emerging <b>Indian networking company</b> originated from <b>capital of India</b>, Delhi or you may have heard that <b>Corporate society is fraud</b>, fake, cheater company who <b>make people especially youth fool by making fake promises</b> to them. I have no idea what exactly you have heard <b>about</b> <b>Corporate Infocom Pvt. Ltd</b> but I’m damn sure, whatever someone told you <b>about Corporate</b> will be something like that, well just give your sometime to this post and let me explain what is the truth behind Corporate Society.<!--more-->
<br><br>

<a href="http://harkuchh.com/corporate-society-is-fraud-bitch-please/corporate-is-fraud-or-not/" rel="attachment wp-att-8601"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-8601" alt="Corporate is Fraud or not" src="https://fbcdn-sphotos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-ash3/t1/1622048_620819387984253_705217368_n.jpg" width="580" height="213" /></a>
<br><br>

I promise you whatever I’m going to tell you is absolutely truth and trusted because I also joined corporate and I know almost everything about it, I joined corporate and it changed my life completely, hold on ! don’t react too fast, first listen what I’m talking about, Yes this is true that my life got changed and corporate is responsible behind it.
<br><br>
Now I know, you wanted to know, How my life got changed because of Corporate Society ? it’s answer is, corporate gave me that platform on which I’m working right now and this platform have a glorious future ahead, it’s called Blogging. Actually before joining<strong> CIPL</strong> I had no Idea how to develop a complete website and run it on internet even after I was a engineering student from I.T trade, I knew how to create a webpage by using HTML and PHP but if we know how to create a webpage it doesn’t mean we can also make a website with that comfort for example creating a webpage by using HTML is like making a 5 second ad commercial and developing a website is something like making of Titanic and I don’t think I need to explain what is the difference between making these two.
<br><br>
In short, it was not possible for me to create even a 4-5 page static website and deploy it on Internet then you can easily think that how could I think of creating a website like Harkuchh, pay your attention, right now I’m just talking about creating a website not SEO, ranking, Backlinks, Ads, commercial emails, advertising, Social promotion, Database, My Sql, affiliate marketing  etc etc and etc but as you can see today I own a website with world rank near to 25k worldwide and around 2k in India and unbelievable fact is that the worth of my website is more than my dad’s property! and that all is live and true you know why ? because of corporate. Corporate told me I can do it, and I did.
<br><br>
Now let me tell you, if it’s true then why people says Corporate is fraud, fake, cheater and blaw&#8230; blaw&#8230; blaw :P
<br><br>
Well Corporate is actually a networking company, who sales it’s web hosting service by following a referral marketing strategy i.e Corporate gives web hosting for a website and chance to work in networking to it’s associates, and the real story begins here..
<br><br>
When a person is approached for a seminar or PPT (paper presentation) by a friend or any known, he/she’s told by the presenter that we’ll give you hosting to create your own website and tell you how to earn money through Google Adsense and other Ads and along with this, company will also give you some extra money as commission if someone join the company by your referral.<br><br>
After joining, some finds it more profitable to work in network marketing so they start working in it,else who wanted to create their website start working on their website, but when any problem arises to them they expect help from the seniors but their seniors won’t help them (I’m always present to help you) this is a bitter but truth, and this is the biggest reason people call the <b>Corporate is fraud</b> <b>company</b>, but point to pay the attention again is that it’s just a hurdle and if seniors not helping someone and they stop working then it’s neither the senior’s nor company’s it’s your fault. Because problem arise to everyone it doesn’t mean you can not proceed after that, there are so many examples who did it all without the help of any seniors, I’m also one of them.
<br><br>

<span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>&#8220;</b></span><span style="color: #003366;"><em>If you need any kind of help in making website, increasing ranking, traffic, getting Adsense, earnings you can contact me any time, my contact details are given in Author Box in sidebar. If you want to create or develop a website only and not interested in Networking part then also you can contact me for the solution of your problem</em></span>.
<br><br>
<h2><span style="font-family: georgia;"><b>Reviews About Corporate Society
</b></span></h2>
Many people call it fraud, fake blaw&#8230;blaww&#8230; blaw&#8230;. and many people worship corporate, let me share some reviews from the person who are/were the part of Corporate Infocom Private Limited.
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>

<img class=" " alt="" src="https://fbcdn-profile-a.akamaihd.net/hprofile-ak-prn2/t1/p160x160/1545136_3867806511460_1004175759_n.jpg" width="112" height="112" /> <strong>Chandan Sanwal</strong>

&nbsp;</td>
<td>If your senior/upline is Good to you then CIPL is good for you, If not then you will be frustrated after some time and say it is fraud. But actually it is not. People working is CIPL make it fraud by not supporting their downline. Chandan Sanwal</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="text-align: left;">

<img alt="" src="https://fbcdn-profile-a.akamaihd.net/hprofile-ak-ash2/t1/c1.159.339.339/s160x160/1452253_3652895536633_757654845_n.jpg" width="112" height="112" /> <strong>Jatin Malik</strong>

&nbsp;</td>
<td style="text-align: left;">Failure will never blame himself for his failure , he will always blame the platform he opted..but from my according every platform is best , its just how you perform out there..by this reason people who blame the platform to be as FRAUD and having belief that somewhere it was the platform only which was responsible for their failure , i personally call those people A BIG FRAUD for being FRAUD to themselves and to those whom they are saying the platform they opted was FRAUD&#8230;in the end THANX Corporate Society for providing me those things which are priceless to me..love u always..</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>

<img alt="" src="https://fbcdn-profile-a.akamaihd.net/hprofile-ak-ash3/c50.50.621.621/s160x160/558613_4140712009991_2081007018_n.jpg" width="112" height="112" /> <strong>Vinod Krishna</strong></td>
<td>It is the duty of the upline to train their downline, this lack of training is the main reason why some people become negative. But there are also some people who expect a lot to earn but never atleast try to work. Such people are also one of the reason for such rumors.
But it is a proved fact that corporate has changed the lifestyle of many people..</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<br><br>
<strong>Conclusion </strong>: Corporate Society is not a fraud company, it’s all crap ! many people living their life happily on internet world because of Corporate Society, well yes it’s true that many people leaved and leaving corporate society and they doing their own business after leaving corporate but it’s also a fact that whatever they are today because of corporate Society, they are thinking they are king but they may forgot every king was once a child, in short if there would be <strong>no corporate Society</strong> then there would be no&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230; , no&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230; and even no&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Comments Not Getting Approved]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/why-your-comments-not-getting-approved/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-29T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/why-your-comments-not-getting-approved</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[Comments are the basic, easiest and most popular way to <strong>create backlink from a good reputed blog</strong> to your blog, maybe you already know this, may be you don’t. If you know it, that’s good but if you don’t then you must need to know it, because in this awesome business called `<a title="What is Blogging, Why Blogging becoming Popular in Youth ?" href="http://harkuchh.com/what-is-blogging-why-blogging-becoming-popular-in-youth/" target="_blank"><strong>Blogging</strong></a>` links and <strong>backlinks</strong> have a great importance.<!--more-->

Many people are facing a problem in commenting, this might be possible that you also having that problem, problem of not getting your comments approved. Don’t worry today your this problem will be solved, all you need to do is, just read this post very carefully.
<h2><strong>Possible Reasons for Comments not Getting Accepting</strong></h2>
&nbsp;<br><br>
<h3><strong>Formality</strong></h3>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><strong>`Oh Wow&#8230;. What a nice post, great work.`</strong></p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><strong>`This is a good post, thanks for sharing.`</strong></p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><strong>`Full of information, nice thank you.`</strong></p>
These kind of comments are totally formality, if you post comments like that on others blog and hope that those will be approved, you are simply a newbie. Bloggers want real appreciation or suggestions to their work, they don’t need these kind of formality, see if they have written a post, they already know that it’s a great post, you don’t need to tell them it’s great.

&nbsp;<br><br>
<h3><strong>No Gravtar Image</strong></h3>
If you commented on a blog and your comment not got approved by webmaster, this point is may be responsible for it, if you have not a Gravtar image for your profile, Bloggers always want their blog to look good and believe me a comment without Gravtar image looks ugly in comment section and most of the people hate it and they don’t accept comments, no matter how good they are. See : <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-show-photo-with-comment-on-website/" target="_blank"><em>How to Show your photo with your comment</em></a>.

&nbsp;<br><br>
<h3><strong>Fake Accounts</strong></h3>
Never ever use any fake account for commenting purpose, see if a blogger is capable to make you comment on his blog, it simply means he/she is a person with decent knowledge and they can easily find out if your details are fake and in that case there is no chance of approving of your comment, Be original comment with your name, your profile.

&nbsp;<br><br>
<h3><strong>Comment not related to the Article</strong></h3>
If you are reading a post pertaining to blogging or SEO and if at the end of the post you are commenting about Justin Bieber, you are simply showing you have lack of knowledge and you are just trying to show your presence there, which doesn’t have any meaning, so don’t do that ever.

&nbsp;<br><br>
<h3><strong>Comment for Link</strong></h3>
Everybody know if someone is commenting on a blog most probably he is doing that for one basic purpose, that is backlink but if you are showing this clearly through your comment that you only want a backlink from that blog, you don’t care about their content of post they will not approve your comment in any case. You need to understand their write ups and then generate question from it, then if you will ask a question from the blogger regarding the post, they will surely approve your comment and will reply back.

&nbsp;<br><br>
<h3><strong>Link in Comment</strong></h3>
I’m really unable to understand how people are doing this foolishness even in these days. They open a post on a popular blog and writes.

<em>`This is really a good information check this out http:&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;.’</em>

if you have done this it’s ok, everyone was a stupid once, but if you are going to do this again ever, you are going to waste your time, nobody like this type of comment strategy and only inexperienced bloggers approves these type of comments.

You can add link to your comment but only and only when it is must needed, generally never do this, this shows you are new, immature and unknown to blogging.

&nbsp;<br><br>
<h3><strong>Wrong Language and Words</strong></h3>
Don’t use cheap language or any bad stuff related to any religion, racism, or any country. vulgarity is strictly prohibited in the business of blogging, if you are not happy with something that’s your problem don’t show your Pent up feelings to anyone, nobody cares, nobody likes it and this is true. Your comment will be trashed immediately.

&nbsp;<br><br>
<h3><strong>Fallacious English</strong></h3>
This is also a big reason for not getting a comment approved, as big bloggers want their post and blog to look good they also like to see good things in comments below their post. Wrong language and broken English is like a blot to their awesome work and everybody hates it, like you do, so always try to be simple, original and straight forward.
<br><br>

If you have read this post in that way I said, `carefully` then I promise your every comment will be approved at every blog, you just take care of these points and comment originally, related to the topic, in proper language strictly avoid formality and vulgarity. Before commenting must read the post and nothing will be more awesome than this, if your comment will have a doubt or query related to the topic written in post.
<br><br>
If you have any query, doubt or matter to discus with us about Blogging, Online earning or anything which relates this field, you can ask your query here or visit our <a href="http://harkuchh.com/forums" target="_blank">Harkuchh Forums</a> for help.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Your Database From cPanel]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-optimize-your-database-from-cpanel/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-optimize-your-database-from-cpanel</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[To help your website or blog in performance, keeping your database(s) optimized is always a great step. No matter you are using InMotion Hosting, GoDaddy Hosting, Hostgator hosting or any other hosting cPanel account or hosting Account, this can be easily done using <strong>phpMyAdmin</strong>. Make it sure before optimizing your database all your data backup.<!--more-->

You can &#8221;<strong>Optimize Table</strong>&#8221; to reclaim unused space and defregment the data file for optimal performance.  If a lot of changes have been made to a table, optimizing the table can sometimes significantly improve performance.
<h2><b>Steps to Optimize Database tables from cPanel..</b></h2>
<ul>
	<li><b>Log in</b> to your website <b>cPanel.</b></li>
</ul>
<img alt="Optomise website  database from cpanel" src="https://fbcdn-sphotos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-frc3/t1/1509159_621269021272623_836157722_n.jpg" width="394" height="365" />
<br><br>
<ul>
	<li>Click on <b>phpMyAdmin </b>under Databases section.</li>
</ul>
<img alt="Click on phpMyAdmin under Databases section" src="https://fbcdn-sphotos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-ash3/t1/1157555_621269154605943_1380000268_n.jpg" width="580" height="124" /></a>
<ul>
<br><br>
	<li>Now look at left, you will see your `<b>Database</b>` name on which you’re working on there, just click on it.</li>
</ul>
<img alt="How to Optimize your Database from cPanel" src="https://fbcdn-sphotos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-frc3/t1/1558573_621269144605944_1141189434_n.jpg" width="580" height="279" /></a>
<br><br>
<ul>
	<li>Now go down and click on `<b>Check All</b>` it will select all your database tables.</li>
</ul>
<img alt="Steps to Optimize Database tables from cPanel" src="https://fbcdn-sphotos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-frc3/t1/1526458_621269134605945_1212466637_n.jpg" width="580" height="353" /></a>

&nbsp;
<ul>
	<li>Click on drop down Menu next to `<b>Check All/Uncheck All</b>` and select `<b>Optimize table</b>`.</li>
</ul>
<img title="Optimize your Database Table ufrom your MyphpAmin" alt="Optimize your Database Table ufrom your MyphpAmin" src="https://fbcdn-sphotos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-ash3/t1/1797469_621269117939280_2072595790_n.jpg" width="511" height="333" /></a>
<p style="text-align: center;"></p>
This is it, you have done, database of your website has been optimized, if you have any sub-domains or any Add on domains in your account then just do same things (step 3 to 5) to optimize their databases.

<strong>Database optimization</strong> is recommended to do on a regular basis as a preventive measure, it doesn’t take much effort but it do affect a site’s or blog’s performance a lot.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get PR for My Blog ?]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-get-pr-for-my-blog/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-15T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-get-pr-for-my-blog</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[I’m sure you have heard of PR or Page Rank or Google Page Rank, these all are the same thing. As I said I’m sure you may have heard of Google Page rank, but.. there are only very few people who knows what exactly <b>Google Page rank stands for</b>. If you get <b>high pr <a title="what are backlinks and how to get it ?" href="http://harkuchh.com/what-are-the-back-links-and-how-to-build-back-links/" target="_blank">backlinks</a></b> for your blog it take your blog to the great height. You don’t need to go for any <b>buy back links</b> from any paid <b>link building service </b>you can get <b>PR in free</b> just by following tips given here.<!--more-->
<br><br>
<img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-9291" alt="PR logo" src="https://fbcdn-sphotos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-prn1/t1/1620673_621275264605332_1882577745_n.jpg" width="580" height="364" /></a>
<br><br>
Having a blog or website in present Internet world is not enough, there are thousands of people over internet doing same thing you’re doing, so you must need to make your blog content visible enough to get maximum hits. Google PageRank is one of the most important factors that Google uses to determine the importance of any blog and it is strongly based on the value of your Blog’s inbound links.

Google generally evaluates how many links there are to your blog from other pages, and the relevance and quality of the linking sites.
<h2><b>How to Get Google Pagerank </b></h2>
<b>Getting pagerank</b> or <b>improve page rank</b> is not everyone’s cup of tea. One need to utilize all techniques available in order to make their web presence attractive, unique and appealing so that it help them in `<b>improve search engine ranking</b>`. This is just a meta description, read further if you are now thinking `<b>how to increase page rank of my website</b>` reading and taking them in practice will surely help you to <b>boost your webpage ranking</b> further.

Also read : <em><a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-increase-website-blog-traffic-and-ranking/" target="_blank">How to Increase Traffic, Ranking and Presence</a>.</em><br><br>
<h3><b>High Quality Content</b></h3>
Well, in blogging field it is most important to know that `<b>Content is King</b>` if you want Page Rank for your blog or you want <b>increase Page Rank</b>, then you must have high quality original content on your blog. If your blog will have original and valuable content then readers will love to spend their time reading your articles and sharing goes higher this way.
<br><br>
<h3><b>Guest posting</b></h3>
Guest posting is the most popular, trusted and <b>effective way to get PR for a blog </b>see when you writes a guest post for a blog having remarkable Page Rank, then you gets a high-quality, relevant inbound link to your website and Google gives it preference more than anything else to consider a blog for giving Pagerank.You must ensure that the blog where you’re going to publish your article is a reputed blog and it’s having good Page Rank.
<br><br>
<h3><b>Directory Submission</b></h3>
Directory submission is a bit time consuming process, but it is also true that in order to boost Page Rank you must have high quality Backlinks associated with your blog name and believe me submit your site on different web directories and article directories  is the best way to generate quality backlinks for any blog. Some popular Directories to submit your blog link are Yahoo Directory, DMOZ, Best Of The Web, Ezine Articles, Article Base.
<br><br>
<h3><b>Comment on Blogs</b></h3>
I think this is the easiest and most crucial step in getting and improving Google Page Rank. Blogging requires a Blogger very active socially. When you land on any blog for any kind of information make it your habit to leave a genuine comment there, because some Blogs are Do-Follow and they can help you to easily generate back links for your blog.
<br><br>
<h3><b>Social Bookmarking</b></h3>
I don’t think I need to explain importance of Social Bookmarking, as it is a most common effective way to get free traffic as well as increase Page Rank, look when we share our Site on different Social networks we gets decent traffic and also free Backlink. Most popular Social Bookmarking Sites are Facebook, g+, Twitter, Stumble Upon , digg.
<br><br>
<h3> Website Accessibility</h3>
This is the fact which most of the people don’t care about, but this plays very significant role in reputation of your blog in front of Google. It can be easily understood that, if a Website remains  down for a long period of time, Google slowly reduce the ranking of that particular site. So You must ensure that your Website is always up.
<br><br>
<h3><b>Regularly Updation</b></h3>
Imagine you’re a teacher and there are many student in your class, some comes for lecture occasionally where as some comes daily, then whom will you prefer as your best students, you know your answer very well, same like that Google really like blogs that keep their content fresh and unique. The more you post, Google crawls your site more and it simply increases chances for you to improve page rank.
<br><br>
Fun Blogging : <a title="Google is male or female ?" href="http://harkuchh.com/google-is-a-girl-i-can-prove-it/" target="_blank"><em>Google is a Girl, I can Prove it</em></a>.
<br><br>
&nbsp;
<h3><b>Link Exchange</b></h3>
This technique is one of that rare technique which is in use from the starting of blogging and surprisingly it still works, many tops bloggers doing this and in order to get a good Page Rank for your blog, you should link your blog to high page rank blogs, by following this you will surely get  Page Rank for your blog and also your blog will get traffic from that site.

<br><br>
<h3><b>No-follow Links</b></h3>
There are millions of blogger over internet world these days, and they keep on posting on their blogs and websites for some specific purposes but I bet most of them don’t know about dofollow and nofollow links properly and because of lack of knowledge about this, they are spreading free dofollow links to other sites unnecessarily. Must read : <i>How to make a link nofollow or dofollow</i>.
<br><br>
<h3><b>Keywords and Tags</b></h3>
You may know that already, keywords and meta tags are one of the key factor for getting traffic to a site and it is one of the most crucial factors in the <b>search engine ranking</b> system. This step is quite taskful as searching of valuable keywords in never easy and once you get best keywords by following it&#8217;s searching and competition volume, use them strategically. This will boost your Traffic, ranking, earnings and yes Page Rank.
<br><br>
<h3><strong></strong><b>Inter Linking </b></h3>
Inter linking your posts is a way to provide access to a related posts from one post and it’s a very useful tool to get better ranking, it increases your websites accessibility so when you think you can link your any previous post to your new one must integrate them because this is a basic as well as effective technique for <b>effective link building</b>.
<br><br>
<h3><b>Engage Visitor</b></h3>
Nothing is more effective than this point, if you successfully keep your the visitors engaged in reading your Articles via interesting and likeable stuff. You can make your visitor stick to your blog by interactive site design, interesting feedback section and Videos which make the visitor watch them.
<br><br>
Also read : <a title="Make much of promoting, free !" href="http://harkuchh.com/idiotic-but-superb-tricks-to-promote-your-blog/" target="_blank"><em>Idiotic but superb ways to promote your blog</em></a>.
<br><br>
Google have not updated PR after it’s last updation in Feb, 2013 so it is expected that, next <b>PR distribution</b> date is very close now, so without wasting time start try to link your blog with <b>high</b><b> pr sites</b> and if you can successfully get <b>high pr back links </b>then <b>chances of getting PR</b> increases much more.
<br><br>
You can also go for <b>Website Advertising</b>, <b>participation on forums</b> for making your blog presence everywhere you can, but don’t ever use any <b>illegal or wrong way to getting backlink</b> to your blog because in starting they may give you some links and traffic but eventually it sounds so bitter and you may fall in trouble, so Be Genuine, Be original, Work your Ass off and leave rest on <strong>G(od+oogle)</strong> Happy Blogging, I really hope Google will give you and Me Page Rank in this update.. ;)<br><br>
If you have any query, doubt or matter to discus with us about Blogging, Online earning or anything which relates this field, you can ask your query here or visit our <a href="http://harkuchh.com/forums" target="_blank">Harkuchh Forums</a> for help.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips & Requirements for Get Approved Adsense Account]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[Many people owning many blogs and websites and most of them doing that thing for getting income, Google Adsense is the most famous name for earning through the Internet. Google Adsense provide Ads to the Blogs and sites and when a visitor visit to the blog He/She see Ads over there If they like to know more about the thing shown in the Ad and open it by clicking on it, then Google provide some Income to the Adsence Account from where the Ads were placed on the Blog or website.</span>

<!--more--> </span>
<br><br>
The hardest part of getting started with Adsense is getting Google to approve your website. In fact  for many people even  it is easier to get a loan of $100,000 from bank than getting a approved Google Adsense account :) . The solution of such problem is to make your blog prepared before you apply for Adsense.
<br><br>
You can’t start using Google Adsense on your Blog until you are approved by Google. The very first thing you must do is read Carefully<strong> <a href="http://support.google.com/adsense/bin/answer.py?hl=en&amp;answer=48182" target="_blank">Adsense Program Policies</a></strong> &amp; <strong><a href="http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Terms of Service (TOS)</span></a></strong> and also very important <a href="https://www.google.com/adsense/localized-terms" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Terms and Conditions</span></a>. If your site doesn’t fall within the guidelines that Google sets out, it will be denied.</span>

<br><br>Some very important points are listed below which every webmaster or Blogger need to keep in their mind and follow them carefully before applying for Google Adsense Account..
<br><br>
<h3><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Points need to focus for approved by Google Adsense :</strong></span></h3>
<ul>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">Your Blog should not be Under Construction it shoud be running.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;"> Website Fulfill almost every points mentioned on Program Policies &amp; Terms of Service (TOS).</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">Website or Blog Getting  decent Traffic.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">There is no too many pages on your Blog.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">There is no Copyrighted data on your blog from any other blog use original content, write for your blog by yourself.</span></li>
</ul>
<span style="color: #333333;"> Now you may understand Creating a website is not a big deal at all, the real challenge is to get traffic and that too from search engines so if your blog has very less traffic than wait few months and than apply for Adsense.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;">Your website should be according to the Terms and Conditions of Google make it sure there is  no adult content, warez, gambling sites, Hacking and hate spreading contents &amp; Copyrighted Data or post on your website.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;">Be Regular on updating Post try to upload a new post in 3-4 days on your blog  if it’s not possible for you than fix a time interval for uploading posts and follow them sincerely, regularly updating Blogs attracts Google and If they find useful contents on your blog your account will be approved without any problem.</span>
<br><br>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong> Quality and Original  Content
</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="color: #333333;">Quality Content is the Best than anything on a blog,  as a famous writer said “<em><strong>It’s Good to publish a single quality Article once in a week than Publishing Scrap Daily</strong></em>”. This is very simple to understand If Post or Content on your Blog is Original (not copyrighted) and written in the best manner then your Application will be accepted very easily by the Adsense Team.</span>


<span style="color: #333333;">You can take ideas from any blog or website but you can’t Copy and paste them on your blog otherwise You will never Get  an Approved Adsense Account.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span><br><br>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Simple and Easy Design</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="color: #333333;"> Before submitting your site for Adsense make sure that the design you use in the site is a simple one with no much graphics works also it is nice if you have a easy navigation process in your site and try to avoid other ad networks while the reviewing process is going on, its not a compulsory one but a simple factor which may  help you to get the Adsense. </span>


<br><br>
<span style="color: #333333;">Also remember to avoid any kinds of adult, hate spreading and Hacking contents since Adsense won&#8217;t approve any sites that is having such contents.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span><br><br>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong> </strong><strong>Apply Once, wait for Reply
</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

Now If you think that your Blog is ready for submitting to Adsense after reading the points given above then you go to <a href="https://accounts.google.com/ServiceLogin?service=adsense&amp;rm=hide&amp;nui=15&amp;alwf=true&amp;ltmpl=adsense&amp;passive=true&amp;continue=https://www.google.com/adsense/gaiaauth2&amp;followup=https://www.google.com/adsense/gaiaauth2&amp;hl=en_US" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Adsense  Sign up Page </span></a>and then submit complete information about your Blog &amp; yourself and make it sure you  fill only real personal information.</span>
<br><br>

<span style="color: #333333;">After sending application to Adsense you will get a reply e-mail from Adsense Team regarding they partially checked your website after that  follow the procedure given in the mail.  If You can’t received any mail from them then Don’t worry you will be surely respond, sometimes it takes time because they have millions of application from the bloggers all over the world. Generally they reply in maximum 4 days, sometime they reply in 2 days or even 1 day.</span>
<br><br>
<span style="color: #333333;">If your application got Disapproved by the Adsense Team, don’t start Crying :D Don’t worry they mention point why your request got  disapproved just fulfill the requirement (mentioned in point)  and apply again because they have lot of applications and they give preference to only Best. Some people when get disapproval mail they send another request instantly  from different email account without taking care of the point in the mail, you don’t do this foolish thing because your blog was not checked by any person their machine or Software check blogs and Website and don’t matter how many email accounts you use for submitting application they only approve your blog if their machine and Software declare it okay.</span>
<br><br>
<span style="color: #333333;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/google-adsense-harkuchh/" rel="attachment wp-att-2443"><span style="color: #333333;"><img class="alignleft  wp-image-2443" title="Google Adsense - Harkuchh" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/Google-Adsense-Harkuchh.jpg" width="174" height="100" /></span></a>By fulfilling all these points and following steps you will get an approved Google Adsense Account easily in maximum 4-5 days. This post give the complete information of many Adsense related questions like, What are requirements for a blog approved by Google Adsense, Tips to get approval for Google Adsense &amp; Best way to get approved by Google Adsense..</span>
<h1 style="padding-left: 30px;"></h1>
<h2 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;"><em><strong>Note :</strong></em></span></h2>
<span style="color: #333333;">Use your real name instead of using any nick or fake name in application if You need to be 18 years old or above, and always remember Even after your blog got approved and you start running Google ads on your blog or website you can’t post anything on it, if you break the TOS, your Adsense account will be removed or possibly banned.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;">Read and obey very carefully <strong><a href="https://www.google.com/adsense/localized-terms" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Adsense Terms and Conditions</span></a></strong>, it may take your time but it is very necessary for good business with Google. as we said in the earlier post  <a title="Permalink to What is Blogging, Why Blogging becoming Popular in Youth ?" href="http://harkuchh.com/what-is-blogging-why-blogging-becoming-popular-in-youth/"><span style="color: #333333;">What is Blogging, Why Blogging becoming Popular in Youth ?</span></a> <strong>never think money is the fruits for your hard deeds but to earn these fruits, you need to show dedicated efforts. Always remember good things takes time.</strong></span>

<span style="color: #333333;">I Hope this post gives you the way to get an approved Adsense account, if you have any Query and Suggestions to share please comment below, <strong> It will my honor to communicate with you..</strong></span><br><br>
If you have any query, doubt or matter to discus with us about Blogging, Online earning or anything which relates this field, you can ask your query here or visit our <a href="http://harkuchh.com/forums" target="_blank">Harkuchh Forums</a> for help.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Common Reasons for Disapproval of Google Adsense Application]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/most-common-reasons-for-disapproval-of-google-adsense-application/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/most-common-reasons-for-disapproval-of-google-adsense-application</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[In blogging many people says that I applied for Ads to the Google, but my application got rejected or whenever I apply for Adsense Ads, Google disapproves my request. Even my requests got disapproved two times before I got approved, but people don’t know, what are the reasons responsible for the disapproval of their Adsense application, Google always mentions some reasons in reply email which are responsible for not accepting one’s Ads application. If you read those email(s) properly then you will understand some of the points why Google rejected it.<!--more-->
<br/>
<br/>
<h1><strong>Most common reasons for disapproval of your Adsense Application..</strong></h1>
<h2 style="padding-left: 30px;">1. Too Many Tags or Keywords</span></h2>
You  might know that Tags plays a very important role in improving your page&#8217;s visibility in the search engines. Search engines always search for the tags which show what is in your post. Actually these tags are the keywords or the word phrases that people types on different search engines for searching answer of their query. If you don’t know that then must settle this thing in your mind that, you should not give too many keywords in your post, because sometimes written articles are not so informative, but if it contains too many keywords search engines crawls, just because there are many keywords, but Google will not take the post as a healthy webpage, which makes a negative impression of your site to the search engine and Google never approve ads request from those blogs/sites.  
<br/>
<br/>
Tags must be used in the post according to it’s quantity and quality. Using unusual, useless and irrelevant tags with an article reduces your credibility with the search engines and even people who come to see your website will not feel good, just imagine the moment you are searching for something and you open pages shown from search engine but you won’t find anything about the thing you are searching for, I’m sure you will never comeback to that particular site then why someone comes to your.
<br/>
<br/>
See using irrelevant, useless and inappropriate tags in your post may increase your visitors but Google will not accept your Adsense request, because as a good service provider Google always wants to provide best output to the every person using it.
<h2>2. Lack of Quality Content</h2>
You must read this very very carefully, whenever you start writing for you website or any website you must write informative and original content instead of copying someone’s idea before you apply for Google Adsense. As I said Google is the best search engine and as the best service provider Google always looks for content that visitors would love to read from beginning till the end. If your website contains very few articles you will find it really difficult to get approve Adsense account. Atleast in the beginning, prefer to write content that which attaract the attention of readers so that Google consider your application. In your post use titles  and heading that are catchy as well as popular, and never neglect to post genuine and innovative material.and one most important point in article writing is it is better to have text as well as quality pictures in your post and also include videos too, these things make the post more interactive. People love to stay on those pages instead of the webpages that contain only text in post, but it doesn’t mean you use use picture in each of your post, if pictures are not relevant don&#8217;t use them.
<br/>
<br/>
<h2>3. Presence of Copied Content</h2>
People think they can make Google fool but dear this is really a very tough thing to do, so if you are using any kind of copy paste either you stop this or stop dreaming of Adsense ads on your site because Google really hate copied and it’s not so tough for google to figure out copied content in a post or webpage, You may don’t know that but it’s true that by doing this you are harming your prestige in the cyber world. Google uses many algorithms and systems to track any kind copied content or any material easily, and most important by doing this you will disgrace your image in front of your readers.
<br/>
<br/>
It’s pretty easy to understand that, copy+paste is very easy for anyone one can copy content of a website and paste it on his own but as we know such kind of content isn’t consider as new and so that the particular blog or site will not get indexed by search engines and will not get ranking too. If Google or other search engines will not index your page then from where you will get visitors, from nowhere ! and as the result visits, views and clicks on your blog will be very low and you will get nothing. In short don’t do copy-paste.
<br/>
<br/>
<h2>4. Invalid Clicks and Comments</h2>
Many people generally thinks that if they click on their webpages their pageviews, traffic will increase and by doing this they will earn better but guys it’s called invalid clicks which is considered as a fraud or cheating by the internet companies. People who don’t have Adsense yet must remember, invalid clicks activity will make it much more difficult for your blog to get approved and even if you have approved Adsense account it doesn&#8217;t meant it will stay with you forever, invalid clicks and impression can also lead to cancellation of your approved adsense account.
<br/>
<br/>
<h2>5. Incomplete Websites</h2>
This is the most important factor people don’t think about, they won’t give their attention to this but Google does, various necessary pages like About page, Privacy page and Contact page is very essential for Adsense, these pages provides info. about the blogger and Blog (the content what your blog contains) it creates a bond between readers and the blogger. Before submitting your application for Google Adsense you must have complete webpages that can be considered by Google, and yes Incomplete webpages will not be accepted and your application will get rejected until you complete it and resubmit your form.
<br/>
<br/>
I hope my effort help you, If you have any query, doubt or matter to discus with us about Blogging, Online earning or anything which relates this field, you can ask your query here or visit our <a href="http://harkuchh.com/forums" target="_blank">Harkuchh Forums</a> for help. 
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome SEO Tricks to Optimize Your Website in SERP]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/awesome-seo-tricks-to-optimize-your-website-in-serp/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-30T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/awesome-seo-tricks-to-optimize-your-website-in-serp</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[SEO (<strong>Search Engine Optimization</strong>) is the most critical factor which is responsible for optimizing of any blog or website and make it&#8217;s appearance on all the <strong>top Search Engine</strong> in searched Results which enhance the <a title="read how to increase your site traffic" href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-increase-website-blog-traffic-and-ranking/" target="_blank"><strong>traffic on your a website</strong></a></span>. Critical factor which is important here is to get the keywords on which you want the visitors to <strong>reach your site through SERP</strong> (Search Engine Results Page). Well in case you are new in blogging field then you must need to  be aware of some very <strong>basic SEO tips and tricks</strong> to <strong>improve your website’s ranking</strong> in the Search engine results.<!--more-->
<br/>
<br/>
<h2><strong>Awesome SEO tricks to Optimize Your Website in SERP</strong></h2>
<h3><strong>Keywords in Title Tag</strong></h3>
If you know about this then read this point one time and if you are not familiar with this I will recommend you to read this at least thrice, Title Tag is one of the most important factor to take  your posts on higher level searched results based on Keywords you chosen. This tag gets visible in the clickable link on the SERPs. It is always recommended to to start your title with a long-tail keyword having less competition, you must use <a href="https://adwords.google.com/" target="_blank"><strong>Adwords tool</strong></a> for this. Always try to use your Keyword within the range of 65 characters as search engine bots give preference to them, and always try to repetition of Keywords in your posts title otherwise your site could be penalized.
<br/>
<br/>
<h3><strong>Use Keywords in Header Tags</strong></h3>
Header tags are one of the most compelling on-page search engine optimization factors. Try to use the same keywords in all the heading tags by following this simple trick you can easily transfer focus of the page on a single keyword while superiority in search engines. You should better use your main keyword in the first section tag and try to keep the use of keywords in mandatory required way.
<br/>
<br/>
<h3><strong>Use Keywords in Image Alt tag</strong></h3>
I think this point is very much responsible for success of Harkuchh.com and many other blogs on web, Images are best way to express many words, and Search Engine Spiders don’t understand image so it have to translate any images they only read the alt tag with text description to understand the image. Therefore, it is essential to have a substantial description of any image you use in your post on your website. This will surely optimize the images in your content and rank higher in search image.
<br/>
<br/>
<h3><strong>Use Power of Internal Linking</strong></h3>
Never ever make mistake of avoiding internal linking as it’s one of the most significant factor and most of the bloggers specially Newbies often ignore Internal Linking which lead them to failure. The better approach is to reactivate and revitalize the old posts in archive, as compared to link them in your fresh posts. Never ignore the role of internal linking in the distribution of page rank.
<br/>
<br/>
<h3><strong>Links from Directories</strong></h3>
There are so many top Directories over internet which helps the submitted websites and links to get searched on search engines so Planting in directories, like Google’s Webmasters, Yahoo, DMOZ and some other article and content directories can be very helpful to achieve positive ranking and get more searched as well.
<br/>
<br/>
<h3><strong>Meta Description</strong></h3>
Well Google now gives quite less importance to meta tags but still there are two meta tags matter in SEO, Meta description tag are important for both human and search engine perspective. Description meta tag is what you use to illustrate your website. In fact, this description is what visitors see when your site appears in the search results.
<br/>
<br/>
<h3><strong>Use Keywords Meta Tag</strong></h3>
Put your relevant keywords in Keywords tags but take care of avoiding replicas and Keyword stuffing in post, tags or anywhere else. The keywords that you mention in the keyword tag is used to the context of your page are relevant, and the keywords used in meta keywords must be written somewhere in your post or article, if you will not do this by this way your website will be penalized for irrelevant content and it will give you that pain which is not easy to suffer from.
<br/>
<br/>
If you have any query, doubt or matter to discus with us about Blogging, Online earning or anything which relates this field, you can ask your query here or visit our <a href="http://harkuchh.com/forums" target="_blank">Harkuchh Forums</a> for help.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Link Nofollow in WordPress]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-make-a-link-nofollow-in-wordpress/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-make-a-link-nofollow-in-wordpress</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[Before proceeding, I think knowing the <strong>difference between a no-follow and a do-follow link</strong> is very vital, Nofollow and dofollow are two very oftenly used words in SEO. Blogging became very popular in last half decade, but many Bloggers of our generation making a big mistake in blogging, and it is spreading of dofollow links to other website-blogs unnecessarily<a href="http://Google.com/" target="_blank">.</a><!--more-->
<strong></strong>

See, while writing post on your blog when you give a link of any other blog somewhere in your post it becomes a dofollow link and by this way you are giving a free do follow link to that blog, which is really not needed<a href="http://bing.com/" target="_blank">.</a>

A normal <b>Dofollow</b> <b>link</b> allows all <a href="http://harkuchh.com/" target="_blank">search engines</a> to follow them and reach the linked website. It give link juice and a back link. If a webmaster is linking back to you with this link both Search Engine and people will be able to follow. Enable The best way to give someone dofollow love making keyword in the anchor text. This means that when you use a link to a website or page, the targeted keywords as anchor text.

A modified <b>Nofollow links</b> does not allow any search engine robot to surf the link, now here point to pay attention is that, if you’ll give a nofollow attribute tag to a links on your web page or website it links you from other page but because of nofollow attribute, it does not pass <a href="http://harkuchh.com/category/blogging/" target="_blank"><b>link juice</b></a>. Any Reader can only follow the links but search engines don’t.

It’s a strong Google’s recommendation that when we link our article with any other website we must have to be very sure that it’s a good website. Sometimes we need to link some p0rn , hacking kind of sites which are generally not consider as a legit or good site, there you will have to add nofollow link attribute. It becomes even more necessary if you are using affiliate marketing, and keep adding affiliate links on your blog.

Being truthful, adding a nofollow tag to any link is damn easy, in order to make any link nofollow, all you need to do is `<b>add nofollow attributes in HTML formal</b>` for example

<span style="color: #ff0000;"><strong>&lt;a href=&#8221;http://royalyouth.com&#8221; rel=&#8221;nofollow&#8221; &gt; <span style="text-decoration: underline;"><span style="color: #008000;"><a href="http://Royalyouth.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><span style="color: #008000; text-decoration: underline;">Royalyouth</span></a></span></span>&lt;/a&gt;</strong></span>

But I’m pretty sure many of us wants to get things done more easier, I know some might not like the idea of using HTML to add Nofollow link attribute.
<h2>WordPress plugin to add no-follow Tag attribute</h2>
As the most awesome feature of WordPress is that, you can have plugin for doing almost any thing. For WordPress users there are some plugins which will let then make all the outgoing links nofollow, but we don’t have to make all external links nofollow because there are also several benefits of dofollow external link in SEO.

<b>Ultimate Nofollow WordPress plugin</b> is best of it’s type, it helps blogger to quickly add nofollow tag to any link while writing post. This is a plug and play plugin so for using this All you have to do is, <b>download and install Ultimate Nofollow plugin </b>to your WordPress account, once you activate th plugin, it will add a nofollow option box in insert link pop-up box in WordPress post editor (see the pic below).

[caption id=&#8221;attachment_8842&#8221; align=&#8221;aligncenter&#8221; width=&#8221;480&#8221;]<a href="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/how-to-add-nofollow-to-a-link-in-wordpress.jpg"><img class="size-full wp-image-8842" alt="make a link nofollow in WordPress" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/how-to-add-nofollow-to-a-link-in-wordpress.jpg" width="480" height="249" /></a> <strong>make a link nofollow in WordPress</strong>[/caption]

For <strong>making the comments links nofollow</strong>, You can also go to <strong>settings &gt; Nofollow</strong>, and uncheck the option to<strong> make your comment links nofollow</strong>. So if you was searching for the <strong>best way to make a link nofollow</strong> in WordPress or <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-make-a-link-nofollow-in-wordpress/"><strong>How to make a link Nofollow in WordPress</strong></a>, it’s the best way. Enjoy this plugin it’s for you.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
