<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[harkuchh]]></title>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-01-29T01:21:45+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://harkuchh.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[harkuchh]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Comments not Getting Approved]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/why-your-comments-not-getting-approved/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-29T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/why-your-comments-not-getting-approved</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[Comments are the basic, easiest and most popular way to <strong>create backlink from a good reputed blog</strong> to your blog, maybe you already know this, may be you don’t. If you know it, that’s good but if you don’t then you must need to know it, because in this awesome business called `<a title="What is Blogging, Why Blogging becoming Popular in Youth ?" href="http://harkuchh.com/what-is-blogging-why-blogging-becoming-popular-in-youth/" target="_blank"><strong>Blogging</strong></a>` links and <a title="read : What is Backlink and How to Build Back Links" href="harkuchh.com/what-are-the-back-links-and-how-to-build-back-links/" target="_blank"><strong>backlinks</strong></a> have a great importance.<!--more-->

Many people are facing a problem in commenting, this might be possible that you also having that problem, problem of not getting your comments approved. Don’t worry today your this problem will be solved, all you need to do is, just read this post very carefully.
<h2><strong>Reasons for Comments not Accepting</strong></h2>
&nbsp;
<h3><strong>Formality</strong></h3>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><strong>`Oh Wow&#8230;. What a nice post, great work.`</strong></p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><strong>`This is a good post, thanks for sharing.`</strong></p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><strong>`Full of information, nice thank you.`</strong></p>
These kind of comments are totally formality, if you post comments like that on others blog and hope that those will be approved, you are simply a newbie. Bloggers want real appreciation or suggestions to their work, they don’t need these kind of formality, see if they have written a post, they already know that it’s a great post, you don’t need to tell them it’s great.

&nbsp;
<h3><strong>No Gravtar Image</strong></h3>
If you commented on a blog and your comment not got approved by webmaster, this point is may be responsible for it, if you have not setted up a Gravtar image for your profile, Bloggers always want their blog to look good and believe me a comment without Gravtar image looks ugly in comment section and most of the people hate it and they don’t accept comments, no matter how good they are. See : <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-show-photo-with-comment-on-website/" target="_blank"><em>How to Show your photo with your comment</em></a>.

&nbsp;
<h3><strong>Fake Accounts</strong></h3>
Never ever use any fake account for commenting purpose, see if a blogger is capable to make you comment on his blog, it simply means he/she is a person with decent knowledge and they can easily find out if your details are fake and in that case there is no chance of approving of your comment, Be original comment with your name, your profile.

&nbsp;
<h3><strong>Comment not related to the Article</strong></h3>
If you are reading a post pertaining to blogging or SEO and if at the end of the post you are commenting about Justin Bieber, you are simply showing you have lack of knowledge and you are just trying to show your presence there, which doesn’t have any meaning, so don’t do that ever.

&nbsp;
<h3><strong>Comment for Link</strong></h3>
Everybody know if someone is commenting on a blog most probably he is doing that for one basic purpose, that is backlink but if you are showing this clearly through your comment that you only want a backlink from that blog, you don’t care about their content of post they will not approve your comment in any case. You need to understand their write ups and then generate question from it, then if you will ask a question from the blogger regarding the post, they will surely approve your comment and will reply back.

&nbsp;
<h3><strong>Link in Comment</strong></h3>
I’m really unable to understand how people are doing this foolishness even in these days. They open a post on a popular blog and writes.

<em>`This is really a good information check this out http:&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;.’</em>

if you have done this it’s ok, everyone was a stupid once, but if you are going to do this again ever, you are going to waste your time, nobody like this type of comment strategy and only inexperienced bloggers approves these type of comments.

You can add link to your comment but only and only when it is must needed, generally never do this, this shows you are new, immature and unknown to blogging.

&nbsp;
<h3><strong>Wrong Language and Words</strong></h3>
Don’t use cheap language or any bad stuff related to any religion, racism, or any country. vulgarity is strictly prohibited in the business of blogging, if you are not happy with something that’s your problem don’t show your Pent up feelings to anyone, nobody cares, nobody likes it and this is true. Your comment will be trashed immediately.

&nbsp;
<h3><strong>Fallacious English</strong></h3>
This is also a big reason for not getting a comment approved, as big bloggers want their post and blog to look good they also like to see good things in comments below their post. Wrong language and broken English is like a blot to their awesome work and everybody hates it, like you do, so always try to be simple, original and straight forward.

Must read : <a href="http://harkuchh.com/tag/adsense/" target="_blank"><em>Best and All Adsense Tips and Tutorials.</em></a>

If you have read this post in the same way I said above, `carefully` then I promise your every comment will be approved at every blog, you just take care of these points and comment originally, related to the topic, in proper language strictly avoid formality and vulgarity. Before commenting must read the post and nothing will be more awesome than this, if your comment will have a doubt or query related to the topic written in post.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize your Database from cPanel]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-optimize-your-database-from-cpanel/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-optimize-your-database-from-cpanel</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[To help your website or blog in performance, keeping your database(s) optimized is always a great step. No matter you are using InMotion Hosting, GoDaddy Hosting, Hostgator hosting or any other hosting cPanel account or hosting Account, this can be easily done using <strong>phpMyAdmin</strong>. Make it sure before optimizing your database all your data backup.<!--more-->

You can &#8221;<strong>Optimize Table</strong>&#8221; to reclaim unused space and defregment the data file for optimal performance.  If a lot of changes have been made to a table, optimizing the table can sometimes significantly improve performance.
<h2><b>Steps to Optimize Database tables from cPanel..</b></h2>
<ul>
	<li><b>Log in</b> to your website <b>cPanel.</b></li>
</ul>
[caption id=&#8221;attachment_9432&#8221; align=&#8221;aligncenter&#8221; width=&#8221;394&#8221;]<a href="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Optomise-website-database-from-cpanel.jpg"><img class="size-full wp-image-9432" alt="Optomise website  database from cpanel" src="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Optomise-website-database-from-cpanel.jpg" width="394" height="365" /></a> <strong>Log in to cPanel</strong>[/caption]

&nbsp;
<ul>
	<li>Click on <b>phpMyAdmin </b>under Databases section.</li>
</ul>
[caption id=&#8221;attachment_9433&#8221; align=&#8221;aligncenter&#8221; width=&#8221;580&#8221;]<a href="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Click-on-phpMyAdmin-under-Databases-section.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-9433" alt="Click on phpMyAdmin under Databases section" src="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Click-on-phpMyAdmin-under-Databases-section-580x124.jpg" width="580" height="124" /></a> <strong>Click on phpMyAdmin under Databases section</strong>[/caption]
<ul>
	<li>Now look at left, you will see your `<b>Database</b>` name on which you’re working on there, just click on it.</li>
</ul>
[caption id=&#8221;attachment_9434&#8221; align=&#8221;aligncenter&#8221; width=&#8221;580&#8221;]<a href="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/How-to-Optimize-your-Database-from-cPanel.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-9434" alt="How to Optimize your Database from cPanel" src="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/How-to-Optimize-your-Database-from-cPanel-580x279.jpg" width="580" height="279" /></a> <strong>click on Database` name on which you’re working</strong>[/caption]
<ul>
	<li>Now go down and click on `<b>Check All</b>` it will select all your database tables.</li>
</ul>
[caption id=&#8221;attachment_9435&#8221; align=&#8221;aligncenter&#8221; width=&#8221;580&#8221;]<a href="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Optimize-your-Database-Table-using-your-phpMyAmin.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-9435" alt="Steps to Optimize Database tables from cPanel" src="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Optimize-your-Database-Table-using-your-phpMyAmin-580x353.jpg" width="580" height="353" /></a> <strong>click on check all to select all tables</strong>[/caption]

&nbsp;
<ul>
	<li>Click on drop down Menu next to `<b>Check All/Uncheck All</b>` and select `<b>Optimize table</b>`.</li>
</ul>
[caption id=&#8221;attachment_9436&#8221; align=&#8221;aligncenter&#8221; width=&#8221;511&#8221;]<a href="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Optimize-your-Database-Table-ufrom-your-MyphpAmin.jpg"><img class=" wp-image-9436 " title="Optimize your Database Table ufrom your MyphpAmin" alt="Optimize your Database Table ufrom your MyphpAmin" src="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Optimize-your-Database-Table-ufrom-your-MyphpAmin.jpg" width="511" height="333" /></a> click on Optimize Table[/caption]
<p style="text-align: center;"></p>
This is it, you have done, database of your website has been optimized, if you have any sub-domains or any Add on domains in your account then just do same things (step 3 to 5) to optimize their databases.

<strong>Database optimization</strong> is recommended to do on a regular basis as a preventive measure, it doesn’t take much effort but it do affect a site’s or blog’s performance a lot.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get PR for my Blog ?]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-get-pr-for-my-blog/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-15T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-get-pr-for-my-blog</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[I’m sure you have heard of PR or Page Rank or Google Page Rank, these all are the same thing. As I said I’m sure you may have heard of Google Page rank, but.. there are only very few people who knows what exactly <b>Google Page rank stands for</b>. If you get <b>high pr <a title="what are backlinks and how to get it ?" href="http://harkuchh.com/what-are-the-back-links-and-how-to-build-back-links/" target="_blank">backlinks</a></b> for your blog it take your blog to the great height. You don’t need to go for any <b>buy back links</b> from any paid <b>link building service </b>you can get <b>PR in free</b> just by following tips given here.<!--more-->

<a href="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/PR-logo.jpg"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-9291" alt="PR logo" src="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/PR-logo-580x364.jpg" width="580" height="364" /></a>

Having a blog or website in present Internet world is not enough, there are thousands of people over internet doing same thing you’re doing, so you must need to make your blog content visible enough to get maximum hits. <a href="http://harkuchh.com/google-e-book-service-for-indian-android-users/" target="_blank">Google</a> PageRank is one of the most important factors that Google uses to determine the importance of any blog and it is strongly based on the value of your Blog’s inbound links.

Google generally evaluates how many links there are to your blog from other pages, and the relevance and quality of the linking sites.
<h2><b>How to Get Google Pagerank </b></h2>
<b>Getting pagerank</b> or <b>improve page rank</b> is not everyone’s cup of tea. One need to utilize all techniques available in order to make their web presence attractive, unique and appealing so that it help them in `<b>improve search engine ranking</b>`. This is just a meta description, read further if you are now thinking `<b>how to increase page rank of my website</b>` reading and taking them in practice will surely help you to <b>boost your webpage ranking</b> further.

Also read : <em><a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-increase-website-blog-traffic-and-ranking/" target="_blank">How to Increase Traffic, Ranking and Presence</a>.</em>
<h3><b>High Quality Content</b></h3>
Well, in <a href="http://harkuchh.com/category/blogging/" target="_blank">blogging</a> field it is most important to know that `<b>Content is King</b>` if you want Page Rank for your blog or you want <b>increase Page Rank</b>, then you must have high quality original content on your blog. If your blog will have original and valuable content then readers will love to spend their time reading your articles and sharing goes higher this way.

<b> </b>
<h3><b>Guest posting</b></h3>
Guest posting is the most popular, trusted and <b>effective way to get PR for a blog </b>see when you writes a guest post for a blog having remarkable Page Rank, then you gets a high-quality, relevant inbound link to your website and Google gives it preference more than anything else to consider a blog for giving Pagerank.You must ensure that the blog where you’re going to publish your article is a reputed blog and it’s having good Page Rank.

&nbsp;
<h3><b>Directory Submission</b></h3>
Directory submission is a bit time consuming process, but it is also true that in order to boost Page Rank you must have high quality Backlinks associated with your blog name and believe me submit your site on different web directories and article directories  is the best way to generate quality backlinks for any blog. Some popular Directories to submit your blog link are Yahoo Directory, DMOZ, Best Of The Web, Ezine Articles, Article Base.

&nbsp;
<h3><b>Comment on Blogs</b></h3>
I think this is the easiest and most crucial step in getting and improving Google Page Rank. Blogging requires a Blogger very active socially. When you land on any blog for any kind of information make it your habit to leave a genuine comment there, because some Blogs are Do-Follow and they can help you to easily generate back links for your blog.

&nbsp;
<h3><b>Social Bookmarking</b></h3>
I don’t think I need to explain importance of Social Bookmarking, as it is a most common effective way to get free traffic as well as increase Page Rank, look when we share our Site on different Social networks we gets decent traffic and also free Backlink. Most popular Social Bookmarking Sites are Facebook, g+, Twitter, Stumble Upon , digg.

&nbsp;
<h3><strong>Website Accessibility</strong></h3>
This is the fact which most of the people don’t care about, but this plays very significant role in reputation of your blog in front of Google. It can be easily understood that, if a Website remains  down for a long period of time, Google slowly reduce the ranking of that particular site. So You must ensure that your Website is always up.

&nbsp;
<h3><b>Regularly Updation</b></h3>
Imagine you’re a teacher and there are many student in your class, some comes for lecture occasionally where as some comes daily, then whom will you prefer as your best students, you know your answer very well, same like that Google really like blogs that keep their content fresh and unique. The more you post, Google crawls your site more and it simply increases chances for you to improve page rank.

Fun Blogging : <a title="Google is male or female ?" href="http://harkuchh.com/google-is-a-girl-i-can-prove-it/" target="_blank"><em>Google is a Girl, I can Prove it</em></a>.

&nbsp;
<h3><b>Link Exchange</b></h3>
This technique is one of that rare technique which is in use from the starting of blogging and surprisingly it still works, many tops bloggers doing this and in order to get a good Page Rank for your blog, you should link your blog to high page rank blogs, by following this you will surely get  Page Rank for your blog and also your blog will get traffic from that site.

<b> </b>
<h3><b>No-follow Links</b></h3>
There are millions of blogger over internet world these days, and they keep on posting on their blogs and websites for some specific purposes but I bet most of them don’t know about dofollow and nofollow links properly and because of lack of knowledge about this, they are spreading free dofollow links to other sites unnecessarily. Must read : <i>How to make a link nofollow or dofollow</i>.

&nbsp;
<h3><b>Keywords and Tags</b></h3>
You may know that already, keywords and meta tags are one of the key factor for getting traffic to a site and it is one of the most crucial factors in the <b>search engine ranking</b> system. This step is quite taskful as searching of valuable keywords in never easy and once you get best keywords by following it&#8217;s searching and competition volume, use them strategically. This will boost your Traffic, ranking, earnings and yes Page Rank.

&nbsp;
<h3><strong></strong><b>Inter Linking </b></h3>
Inter linking your posts is a way to provide access to a related posts from one post and it’s a very useful tool to get better ranking, it increases your websites accessibility so when you think you can link your any previous post to your new one must integrate them because this is a basic as well as effective technique for <b>effective link building</b>.

&nbsp;
<h3><b>Engage Visitor</b></h3>
Nothing is more effective than this point, if you successfully keep your the visitors engaged in reading your Articles via interesting and likeable stuff. You can make your visitor stick to your blog by interactive site design, interesting feedback section and Videos which make the visitor watch them.

Also read : <a title="Make much of promoting, free !" href="http://harkuchh.com/idiotic-but-superb-tricks-to-promote-your-blog/" target="_blank"><em>Idiotic but superb ways to promote your blog</em></a>.

Google have not updated PR after it’s last updation in Feb, 2013 so it is expected that, next <b>PR distribution</b> date is very close now, so without wasting time start try to link your blog with <b>high</b><b> pr sites</b> and if you can successfully get <b>high pr back links </b>then <b>chances of getting PR</b> increases much more.

You can also go for <b>Website Advertising</b>, <b>participation on forums</b> for making your blog presence everywhere you can, but don’t ever use any <b>illegal or wrong way to getting backlink</b> to your blog because in starting they may give you some links and traffic but eventually it sounds so bitter and you may fall in trouble, so Be Genuine, Be original, Work your Ass off and leave rest on <strong>G(od+oogle)</strong> Happy Blogging, I really hope Google will give you and Me Page Rank in this update.. ;)
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips & Requirements for Get Approved Adsense Account]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<span style="color: #333333;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/rules_graphic1/" rel="attachment wp-att-2437"><span style="color: #333333;"><img class="alignleft  wp-image-2437" style="margin-left: 7px; margin-right: 7px;" title="Google Adsense Rules" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/Rules_Graphic1.jpg" width="180" height="200" /></span></a>Many people owning many blogs and websites and most of them doing that thing for getting income, Google Adsense is the most famous name for earning through the Internet. Google Adsense provide Ads to the Blogs and sites and when a visitor visit to the blog He/She see Ads over there If they like to know more about the thing shown in the Ad and open  it by clicking  on it, then Google provide some Income to the Adsence Account from where the Ads were placed on the Blog or website. </span>

<span style="color: #333333;"><!--more--> </span>

<span style="color: #333333;">The hardest part of getting started with Adsense is getting Google to approve your website. In fact  for many people even  it is easier to get a loan of $100,000 from bank than getting a approved Google Adsense account :) . The solution of such problem is to make your blog prepared before you apply for Adsense.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;">You can’t start using Google Adsense on your Blog until you are approved by Google. The very first thing you must do is read Carefully<strong> <a href="http://support.google.com/adsense/bin/answer.py?hl=en&amp;answer=48182" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Adsense Program Policies</span></a></strong> &amp; <strong><a href="http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Terms of Service (TOS)</span></a></strong> and also very important <a href="https://www.google.com/adsense/localized-terms" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Terms and Conditions</span></a>. If your site doesn’t fall within the guidelines that Google sets out, it will be denied.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> Some very important points are listed below which every webmaster or Blogger need to keep in their mind and follow them carefully before applying for Google Adsense Account..</span>

&nbsp;
<h3><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Points need to focus for approved by Google Adsense :</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<ul>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">Your Blog should not be Under Construction it shoud be running.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;"> Website Fulfill almost every points mentioned on Program Policies &amp; Terms of Service (TOS).</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">Website or Blog Getting  decent Traffic.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">There is no too many pages on your Blog.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">There is no Copyrighted data on your blog from any other blog use original content, write for your blog by yourself.</span></li>
</ul>
<span style="color: #333333;"> Now you may understand Creating a website is not a big deal at all, the real challenge is to get traffic and that too from search engines so if your blog has very less traffic than wait few months and than apply for Adsense.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;">Your website should be according to the Terms and Conditions of Google make it sure there is  no adult content, warez, gambling sites, Hacking and hate spreading contents &amp; Copyrighted Data or post on your website.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;">Be Regular on updating Post try to upload a new post in 3-4 days on your blog  if it’s not possible for you than fix a time interval for uploading posts and follow them sincerely, regularly updating Blogs attracts Google and If they find useful contents on your blog your account will be approved without any problem.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong> Quality and Original  Content
</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="color: #333333;">Quality Content is the Best than anything on a blog,  as a famous writer said “<em><strong>It’s Good to publish a single quality Article once in a week than Publishing Scrap Daily</strong></em>”. This is very simple to understand If Post or Content on your Blog is Original (not copyrighted) and written in the best manner then your Application will be accepted very easily by the Adsense Team.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/valuable-original-content/" rel="attachment wp-att-2460"><span style="color: #333333;"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2460" title="valuable original content" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/valuable-original-content.jpg" width="266" height="200" /></span></a></span>

<span style="color: #333333;">You can take ideas from any blog or website but you can’t Copy and paste them on your blog otherwise You will never Get  an Approved Adsense Account.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Simple and Easy Design</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="color: #333333;"> Before submitting your site for Adsense make sure that the design you use in the site is a simple one with no much graphics works also it is nice if you have a easy navigation process in your site and try to avoid other ad networks while the reviewing process is going on, its not a compulsory one but a simple factor which may  help you to get the Adsense. </span>

<span style="color: #333333;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/simple-design-of-a-website-bmp/" rel="attachment wp-att-2462"><span style="color: #333333;"><img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-2462" title="simple design of a website.bmp" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/simple-design-of-a-website.bmp-300x182.jpg" width="300" height="182" /></span></a></span>

<span style="color: #333333;">Also remember to avoid any kinds of adult, hate spreading and Hacking contents since Adsense won&#8217;t approve any sites that is having such contents.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong> </strong><strong>Apply Once, wait for Reply
</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="color: #333333;">Now If you think that your Blog is ready for submitting to Adsense after reading the points given above then you go to <a href="https://accounts.google.com/ServiceLogin?service=adsense&amp;rm=hide&amp;nui=15&amp;alwf=true&amp;ltmpl=adsense&amp;passive=true&amp;continue=https://www.google.com/adsense/gaiaauth2&amp;followup=https://www.google.com/adsense/gaiaauth2&amp;hl=en_US" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Adsense  Sign up Page </span></a>and then submit complete information about your Blog &amp; yourself and make it sure you  fill only real personal information.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/apply-once-and-wait-for-reply-of-adsense-team/" rel="attachment wp-att-2463"><span style="color: #333333;"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2463" title="Apply once and wait for reply of adsense team" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/Apply-once-and-wait-for-reply-of-adsense-team.jpg" width="320" height="164" /></span></a></span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

<span style="color: #333333;">After sending application to Adsense you will get a reply e-mail from Adsense Team regarding they partially checked your website after that  follow the procedure given in the mail.  If You can’t received any mail from them then Don’t worry you will be surely respond, sometimes it takes time because they have millions of application from the bloggers all over the world. Generally they reply in maximum 4 days, sometime they reply in 2 days or even 1 day.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;">If your application got Disapproved by the Adsense Team, don’t start Crying :D Don’t worry they mention point why your request got  disapproved just fulfill the requirement (mentioned in point)  and apply again because they have lot of applications and they give preference to only Best. Some people when get disapproval mail they send another request instantly  from different email account without taking care of the point in the mail, you don’t do this foolish thing because your blog was not checked by any person their machine or Software check blogs and Website and don’t matter how many email accounts you use for submitting application they only approve your blog if their machine and Software declare it okay.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

<span style="color: #333333;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/google-adsense-harkuchh/" rel="attachment wp-att-2443"><span style="color: #333333;"><img class="alignleft  wp-image-2443" title="Google Adsense - Harkuchh" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/Google-Adsense-Harkuchh.jpg" width="174" height="100" /></span></a>By fulfilling all these points and following steps you will get an approved Google Adsense Account easily in maximum 4-5 days. This post give the complete information of many Adsense related questions like, What are requirements for a blog approved by Google Adsense, Tips to get approval for Google Adsense &amp; Best way to get approved by Google Adsense..</span>
<h1 style="padding-left: 30px;"></h1>
<h2 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;"><em><strong>Note :</strong></em></span></h2>
<span style="color: #333333;">Use your real name instead of using any nick or fake name in application if You need to be 18 years old or above, and always remember Even after your blog got approved and you start running Google ads on your blog or website you can’t post anything on it, if you break the TOS, your Adsense account will be removed or possibly banned.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;">Read and obey very carefully <strong><a href="https://www.google.com/adsense/localized-terms" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Adsense Terms and Conditions</span></a></strong>, it may take your time but it is very necessary for good business with Google. as we said in the earlier post  <a title="Permalink to What is Blogging, Why Blogging becoming Popular in Youth ?" href="http://harkuchh.com/what-is-blogging-why-blogging-becoming-popular-in-youth/"><span style="color: #333333;">What is Blogging, Why Blogging becoming Popular in Youth ?</span></a> <strong>never think money is the fruits for your hard deeds but to earn these fruits, you need to show dedicated efforts. Always remember good things takes time.</strong></span>

<span style="color: #333333;">I Hope this post gives you the way to get an approved Adsense account, if you have any Query and Suggestions to share please comment below, <strong> It will my honor to communicate with you..</strong></span>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Common reasons for Disapproval of Google Adsense Application]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/most-common-reasons-for-disapproval-of-google-adsense-application/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/most-common-reasons-for-disapproval-of-google-adsense-application</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[In blogging many people says that I applied for Ads to the Google, but my application got rejected or whenever I apply for Adsense Ads, Google disapproves my request. Even my requests got disapproved two times before I got approved, but people don’t know, what are the reasons responsible for the disapproval of their Adsense application, Google always mentions some reasons in reply email which are responsible for not accepting one’s Ads application. If you read those email(s) properly then you will understand some of the points why Google rejected it.<!--more-->

<a href="http://harkuchh.com/most-common-reasons-for-disapproval-of-google-adsense-application/google-adsense-disappoval-reasons/" rel="attachment wp-att-8382"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-8382" alt="Google Adsense Disappoval reasons" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/Google-Adsense-Disappoval-reasons-580x229.jpg" width="580" height="229" /></a>
<h2><strong>Here are the some most common reasons for disapproval of your Adsense Application..</strong></h2>
<h1 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #000000;">1. Too Many Tags or Keywords</span></h1>
You  might know that Tags plays a very important role in improving your page&#8217;s visibility in the search engines. Search engines always search for the tags which show what is in your post. Actually these tags are the keywords or the word phrases that people types on different search engines for searching answer of their query. If you don’t know that then must settle this thing in your mind that, you should not give too many keywords in your post, because sometimes written articles are not so informative, but if it contains too many keywords search engines crawls, just because there are many keywords, but Google will not take the post as a healthy webpage, which makes a negative impression of your site to the search engine and Google never approve ads request from those blogs/sites.

Tags must be used in the post according to it’s quantity and quality. Using unusual, useless and irrelevant tags with an article reduces your credibility with the search engines and even people who come to see your website will not feel good, just imagine the moment you are searching for something and you open pages shown from search engine but you won’t find anything about the thing you are searching for, I’m sure you will never comeback to that particular site then why someone comes to your.

See using irrelevant, useless and inappropriate tags in your post may increase your visitors but Google will not accept your Adsense request, because as a good service provider Google always wants to provide best output to the every person using it.
<h1 style="text-align: left; padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #000000;"> 2. Lack of Quality Content</span></h1>
You must read this very very carefully, whenever you start writing for you website or any website you must write informative and original content instead of copying someone’s idea before you apply for Google Adsense. As I said Google is the best search engine and as the best service provider Google always looks for content that visitors would love to read from beginning till the end. If your website contains very few articles you will find it really difficult to get approve Adsense account. Atleast in the beginning, prefer to write content that which attaract the attention of readers so that Google consider your application. In your post use titles  and heading that are catchy as well as popular, and never neglect to post genuine and innovative material.and one most important point in article writing is it is better to have text as well as quality pictures in your post and also include videos too, these things make the post more interactive. People love to stay on those pages instead of the webpages that contain only text in post, but it doesn’t mean you use use picture in each of your post, if pictures are not relevant don&#8217;t use them.
<h1 style="padding-left: 30px;"> <span style="color: #000000;">3. Presence of Copied Content</span></h1>
People think they can make Google fool but dear this is really a very tough thing to do, so if you are using any kind of copy paste either you stop this or stop dreaming of Adsense ads on your site because Google really hate copied and it’s not so tough for google to figure out copied content in a post or webpage, You may don’t know that but it’s true that by doing this you are harming your prestige in the cyber world. Google uses many algorithms and systems to track any kind copied content or any material easily, and most important by doing this you will disgrace your image in front of your readers.

It’s pretty easy to understand that, copy+paste is very easy for anyone one can copy content of a website and paste it on his own but as we know such kind of content isn’t consider as new and so that the particular blog or site will not get indexed by search engines and will not get ranking too. If Google or other search engines will not index your page then from where you will get visitors, from nowhere ! and as the result visits, views and clicks on your blog will be very low and you will get nothing. In short don’t do copy-paste.
<h1 style="padding-left: 30px;"> <span style="color: #000000;">4. Invalid Clicks and Comments</span></h1>
Many people generally thinks that if they click on their webpages their pageviews, traffic will increase and by doing this they will earn better but guys it’s called invalid clicks which is considered as a fraud or cheating by the internet companies. People who don’t have Adsense yet must remember, invalid clicks activity will make it much more difficult for your blog to get approved and even if you have approved Adsense account it doesn&#8217;t meant it will stay with you forever, invalid clicks and impression can also lead to cancellation of your approved adsense account.
<h1 style="padding-left: 30px;"> <span style="color: #000000;">5. Incomplete Websites</span></h1>
This is the most important factor people don’t think about, they won’t give their attention to this but Google does, various necessary pages like About page, Privacy page and Contact page is very essential for Adsense, these pages provides info. about the blogger and Blog (the content what your blog contains) it creates a bond between readers and the blogger. Before submitting your application for Google Adsense you must have complete webpages that can be considered by Google, and yes Incomplete webpages will not be accepted and your application will get rejected until you complete it and resubmit your form.

I hope my effort help you, for any query, suggestion must comment, don&#8217;t forget to share..
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome SEO Tricks to Optimize Your Website in SERP]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/awesome-seo-tricks-to-optimize-your-website-in-serp/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-30T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/awesome-seo-tricks-to-optimize-your-website-in-serp</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[SEO (<strong>Search Engine Optimization</strong>) is the most critical factor which is responsible for optimizing of any<a href="http://harkuchh.com/category/blogging/" target="_blank"><strong> blog or website</strong></a> and make it&#8217;s appearance on all the <strong>top Search Engine</strong> in searched Results which enhance the <span style="text-decoration: underline;"><a title="read how to increase your site traffic" href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-increase-website-blog-traffic-and-ranking/" target="_blank"><strong>traffic on your a website</strong></a></span>. Critical factor which is important here is to get the keywords on which you want the visitors to <strong>reach your site through SERP</strong> (Search Engine Results Page). Well in case you are new in blogging field then you must need to  be aware of some very <a href="http://harkuchh.com/tag/seo/" target="_blank"><strong>basic SEO tips and tricks</strong></a> to <strong>improve your website’s ranking</strong> in the Search engine results.<!--more-->

<a href="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/Awesome-SEO-Tricks-to-Optimize-Your-Website-in-SERP.png"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-8942" alt="Awesome SEO Tricks to Optimize Your Website in SERP" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/Awesome-SEO-Tricks-to-Optimize-Your-Website-in-SERP.png" width="430" height="309" /></a>
<h2><strong>Awesome SEO tricks to Optimize Your Website in SERP</strong></h2>
<h3><strong>Keywords in Title Tag</strong></h3>
<strong></strong> If you know about this then read this point one time and if you are not familiar with this I will recommend you to read this at least thrice, Title Tag is one of the most important factor to take  your posts on higher level searched results based on Keywords you chosen. This tag gets visible in the clickable link on the SERPs. It is always recommended to to start your title with a long-tail keyword having less competition, you must use <span style="text-decoration: underline;"><a href="https://adwords.google.com/" target="_blank"><strong>Adwords too</strong></a><strong>l</strong></span> for this. Always try to use your Keyword within the range of 65 characters as search engine bots give preference to them, and always try to repetition of Keywords in your posts title otherwise your site could be penalized.
<h3><strong>Use Keywords in Header Tags</strong></h3>
Header tags are one of the most compelling on-page search engine optimization factors. Try to use the same keywords in all the heading tags by following this simple trick you can easily transfer focus of the page on a single keyword while superiority in search engines. You should better use your main keyword in the first section tag and try to keep the use of keywords in mandatory required way.
<h3><strong>Use Keywords in Image Alt tag</strong></h3>
I think this point is very much responsible for success of Harkuchh.com and many other blogs on web, Images are best way to express many words, and Search Engine Spiders don’t understand image so it have to translate any images they only read the alt tag with text description to understand the image. Therefore, it is essential to have a substantial description of any image you use in your post on your website. This will surely optimize the images in your content and rank higher in search image.
<h3><strong>Use Power of Internal Linking</strong></h3>
Never ever make mistake of avoiding internal linking as it’s one of the most significant factor and most of the bloggers specially Newbies often ignore Internal Linking which lead them to failure. The better approach is to reactivate and revitalize the old posts in archive, as compared to link them in your fresh posts. Never ignore the role of internal linking in the distribution of page rank.
<h3><strong>Links from Directories</strong></h3>
There are so many top Directories over internet which helps the submitted websites and links to get searched on search engines so Planting in directories, like Google’s Webmasters, Yahoo, DMOZ and some other article and content directories can be very helpful to achieve positive ranking and get more searched as well.
<h3><strong>Meta Description</strong></h3>
Well Google now gives quite less importance to meta tags but still there are two meta tags matter in SEO, Meta description tag are important for both human and search engine perspective. Description meta tag is what you use to illustrate your website. In fact, this description is what visitors see when your site appears in the search results.
<h3><strong>Use Keywords Meta Tag</strong></h3>
Put your relevant keywords in Keywords tags but take care of avoiding replicas and Keyword stuffing in post, tags or anywhere else. The keywords that you mention in the keyword tag is used to the context of your page are relevant, and the keywords used in meta keywords must be written somewhere in your post or article, if you will not do this by this way your website will be penalized for irrelevant content and it will give you that pain which is not easy to suffer from.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make a link Nofollow in WordPress]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-make-a-link-nofollow-in-wordpress/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-make-a-link-nofollow-in-wordpress</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[Before proceeding, I think knowing the <strong>difference between a no-follow and a do-follow link</strong> is very vital, Nofollow and dofollow are two very oftenly used words in SEO. Blogging became very popular in last half decade, but many Bloggers of our generation making a big mistake in blogging, and it is spreading of dofollow links to other website-blogs unnecessarily<a href="http://Google.com/" target="_blank">.</a><!--more-->
<strong></strong>

See, while writing post on your blog when you give a link of any other blog somewhere in your post it becomes a dofollow link and by this way you are giving a free do follow link to that blog, which is really not needed<a href="http://bing.com/" target="_blank">.</a>

A normal <b>Dofollow</b> <b>link</b> allows all <a href="http://harkuchh.com/" target="_blank">search engines</a> to follow them and reach the linked website. It give link juice and a back link. If a webmaster is linking back to you with this link both Search Engine and people will be able to follow. Enable The best way to give someone dofollow love making keyword in the anchor text. This means that when you use a link to a website or page, the targeted keywords as anchor text.

A modified <b>Nofollow links</b> does not allow any search engine robot to surf the link, now here point to pay attention is that, if you’ll give a nofollow attribute tag to a links on your web page or website it links you from other page but because of nofollow attribute, it does not pass <a href="http://harkuchh.com/category/blogging/" target="_blank"><b>link juice</b></a>. Any Reader can only follow the links but search engines don’t.

It’s a strong Google’s recommendation that when we link our article with any other website we must have to be very sure that it’s a good website. Sometimes we need to link some p0rn , hacking kind of sites which are generally not consider as a legit or good site, there you will have to add nofollow link attribute. It becomes even more necessary if you are using affiliate marketing, and keep adding affiliate links on your blog.

Being truthful, adding a nofollow tag to any link is damn easy, in order to make any link nofollow, all you need to do is `<b>add nofollow attributes in HTML formal</b>` for example

<span style="color: #ff0000;"><strong>&lt;a href=&#8221;http://royalyouth.com&#8221; rel=&#8221;nofollow&#8221; &gt; <span style="text-decoration: underline;"><span style="color: #008000;"><a href="http://Royalyouth.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><span style="color: #008000; text-decoration: underline;">Royalyouth</span></a></span></span>&lt;/a&gt;</strong></span>

But I’m pretty sure many of us wants to get things done more easier, I know some might not like the idea of using HTML to add Nofollow link attribute.
<h2>WordPress plugin to add no-follow Tag attribute</h2>
As the most awesome feature of WordPress is that, you can have plugin for doing almost any thing. For WordPress users there are some plugins which will let then make all the outgoing links nofollow, but we don’t have to make all external links nofollow because there are also several benefits of dofollow external link in SEO.

<b>Ultimate Nofollow WordPress plugin</b> is best of it’s type, it helps blogger to quickly add nofollow tag to any link while writing post. This is a plug and play plugin so for using this All you have to do is, <b>download and install Ultimate Nofollow plugin </b>to your WordPress account, once you activate th plugin, it will add a nofollow option box in insert link pop-up box in WordPress post editor (see the pic below).

[caption id=&#8221;attachment_8842&#8221; align=&#8221;aligncenter&#8221; width=&#8221;480&#8221;]<a href="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/how-to-add-nofollow-to-a-link-in-wordpress.jpg"><img class="size-full wp-image-8842" alt="make a link nofollow in WordPress" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/how-to-add-nofollow-to-a-link-in-wordpress.jpg" width="480" height="249" /></a> <strong>make a link nofollow in WordPress</strong>[/caption]

For <strong>making the comments links nofollow</strong>, You can also go to <strong>settings &gt; Nofollow</strong>, and uncheck the option to<strong> make your comment links nofollow</strong>. So if you was searching for the <strong>best way to make a link nofollow</strong> in WordPress or <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-make-a-link-nofollow-in-wordpress/"><strong>How to make a link Nofollow in WordPress</strong></a>, it’s the best way. Enjoy this plugin it’s for you.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage Blog and Blogging During Exams]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-manage-blog-and-blogging-during-exams/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-23T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-manage-blog-and-blogging-during-exams</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<span style="color: #333333;">Exam time is close now and this is the most popular question for bloggers category that ‘How to deal with blog and study during exams consistently’ and it’s like a task for all bloggers to manage blog and study during exams, as a blogger you can’t stop <a href="http://harkuchh.com/category/blogging/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">blogging</span></a> for long time interval and you also can’t ignore academic exams because these are very important.<!--more-->
</span>

<span style="color: #333333;">So the question is `How to manage Blog and Exams Together` if you ask this to people mostly will suggest you to stop or ignore blogging until your exams get over but I <a title="most important plug-ins for Wordpress blog" href="http://harkuchh.com/most-important-plugins-for-wordpress-blog/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">recommend</span></a> you to don’t do that otherwise it will effect your site <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-increase-website-blog-traffic-and-ranking/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">ranking, traffic</span></a> and earnings as well.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;">I have great solutions for this problem which I follow during my engineering exams, and trust me, they work always like a charm for me to effectively manage my blog during exams and I’m 100% sure they will also help you a lot, here are the..</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h2><span style="color: #008000;"><strong>5 Simple Ways To Manage Your Blog During Exams</strong></span></h2>
<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3><span style="color: #333333;"><strong> 1.   Write Posts in Advance and Schedule them for later</strong></span></h3>
<span style="color: #333333;">WordPress, Jhoomla and all CMS give us ability to schedule our post to publish later automatically then why don’t we take advantage of this technology in need, You just need to write some posts in advance and schedule it to publish during exams this is the best way to manage your blog during exams.  </span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3><span style="color: #333333;"> <strong>2.   </strong><strong>In holidays between exams give little time to your Blog</strong></span></h3>
<span style="color: #333333;">No matter how busy you are during exams, spend sometime to write quick blog posts. Just think it’s not a big deal, as we all know, no one do study 24*7 during exams specially bloggers can’t, just make a strong promise to yourself that you will not waste your time on social sites and will sit on PC for just a little time and in that little time you must have to complete and publish a post. This idea really works. You just need to be honest to your self promise.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3><span style="color: #333333;"><strong> 3.   Publish your already published old but useful post as new</strong></span></h3>
<span style="color: #333333;">This is one of my favourite idea it’s lil bit creative but very easy and smart, all you need to do is that during exams you just need to give maximum 5-10 minutes to your blog and <a title="see how" href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-show-an-old-post-on-homepage-as-first-post/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">publish your an old post again as new</span></a> about which your visitors don’t know or rarely know, if you do that with minor editing if required, your visitors will think you working regularly on it, this way your regular readers will be regular on your blog.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>4.   </strong><strong>Seek Your Fellow Bloggers for Help</strong></span></h3>
<span style="color: #333333;">When a blogger do blogging regularly then he automatically come in contact with many bloggers and building a good relationship with fellow bloggers is very important. You can ask your friend blogger to manage your blog during exams, like writing articles, accepting guest posts, approving comments, this can be done by paying some money to him or doing it for free depend on your friendship.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3><span style="color: #333333;"><strong> 5.   Ask your real life close Friends to help</strong></span></h3>
<span style="color: #333333;">You can also ask to your real life close friends for writing posts about various topics, discus with  them the topics on which you need posts and if it’s OK with your friend then it’s great otherwise you can also ask them to write on a topic they can write easily, by this way you will have many posts for your blog and you can publish them on your blog in exams by moderating it in your taste. I’m thnkful to my dear friend Raj who helped me in same category. I’m sure you also have some nice friends like me.  </span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

Don&#8217;t miss : <a href="http://harkuchh.com/what-is-subdomain-how-to-create-subdomain-of-my-website/" target="_blank"><em>Simple way to create a Subdomain of your blog or website</em></a>

<span style="color: #333333;">By following these ways you never have to worry too much about your blog in even exam days or whenever it’s not easy for you to work on blog. This way will not only give you free time when you’re busy they also make it easy for you to manage your blog when you don’t have enough time. :lol: </span>

<span style="color: #333333;">Hope you enjoyed reading this article, now if you have any other ideas to manage blog and exams please let me and the readers know about them. Your point will be published on this blog with your name.  ;-) </span>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things to Ensure Before Applying for Google Adsense]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/things-to-ensure-before-applying-for-google-adsense/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/things-to-ensure-before-applying-for-google-adsense</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<span style="font-family: georgia;">I have written it many times and writing it again here that `Adsense is the King of all Ad Networks` and reasons are more than enough for this like  it’s payouts CPC (cost per click), CPM, CTR are much higher when compared to other Ads Networks, and off course due to the brand Google, almost every Blogger want Adsense on their Blog.<!--more--></span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">Getting Adsense is not everyone’s cup of Tea, Google is very strict in order to approve Adsense account to any blog or website, there is no place for any mistake you need to follow their Terms and conditions very strictly, even a very small mistake can led to un-approval of your Adsense application.</span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">Here is the list of all important things you should ensure before applying for Adsense to Google.</span>
<h4><strong><span style="font-family: georgia;">1.          High Level Domain</span></strong></h4>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">When we apply for Adsense our site/blog undergoes two reviews, respectively called as Partial Review and Overall review. The first review can be easily surpassed if you have a domain ending  with .com, .org. In former time Adsense used to accept free domains from WordPress and blogspot but in present era Google become more choosy &amp; strict in its selection and give preference to high level domains ( .com, .org) in its first review.</span>

&nbsp;
<h4><strong><span style="font-family: georgia;">2.         Strictly Avoid <span style="color: #ff0000;">Copy+Paste</span></span></strong></h4>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">Before applying for Adsense must ensure that there is no copied content on your site or blog means you have not copied any post from any website and pasted on our site (most of people do this and later cry for Adsense). If you have any copied content on your website then `Google may surpass partial review but in second review your application will be disapproved for sure`, so if you are really serious about your earnings with Adsense do stick to the original content. If you don’t take it serious then you will get this reply from Google..</span>

<a href="http://harkuchh.com/things-to-ensure-before-applying-for-google-adsense/adsense-application-got-disapproved-because-of-copyrighted-material-pic/" rel="attachment wp-att-6300"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-6300" alt="Adsense Application Got Disapproved because of Copyrighted Material Pic" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/Adsense-Application-Got-Disapproved-because-of-Copyrighted-Material-Pic.jpg" width="463" height="220" /></a>

&nbsp;
<h4><strong><span style="font-family: georgia;">3.         Enough content</span></strong></h4>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">Insufficient no. of posts or so called less content also led to disapproval of an Adsense application. Some people will also tell you that `Content doesn’t play a bright role in Adsense approval` but sadly believe me it’s not true at all ! If you believe me, at least 10 posts should be  there before applying for Adsense otherwise be ready to receive this..</span>

<a href="http://harkuchh.com/things-to-ensure-before-applying-for-google-adsense/adsense-application-got-disapproved-because-of-insufficient-content-pic/" rel="attachment wp-att-6301"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-6301" alt="Adsense Application Got Disapproved because of insufficient content Pic" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/Adsense-Application-Got-Disapproved-because-of-insufficient-content-Pic.jpg" width="469" height="221" /></a>
<h4><strong><span style="font-family: georgia;">4.         Quality and Type of Content</span></strong></h4>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">In order to build a good relationship with Google Adsense, Content on your blog must obey rules stated by Google Adsense. Don’t promote any product related to Pornographic, Drugs, weapons or anything degrading nations &amp; religion peace. Google highly give preference to English as main language so you also try to provide content in form it wants. You may have noticed many sites have more than enough content but they have no Adsense, Do you know why ? because of quality and value of their content, and length of posts. A post should be at least of 300 words.</span>

&nbsp;
<h4><strong><span style="font-family: georgia;">5.         Age of Applicant</span></strong></h4>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">Google wants to deal with Adults not teens i.e. Age plays an important role in Adsense Approval, if anybody is going to applying for Adsense then he/she must be 18 years old. If you are a blogger having blog fulfilling all the Terms and Conditions of Adsense but your age is less than minimum then you can apply for Adsense through email account of any member of family whose age  is 18+. Otherwise you will get this answer from Adsense..</span>

<a href="http://harkuchh.com/things-to-ensure-before-applying-for-google-adsense/adsense-application-got-disapproved-because-of-age-issue-pic/" rel="attachment wp-att-6299"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-6299" alt="Adsense Application Got Disapproved because of age issue Pic" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/Adsense-Application-Got-Disapproved-because-of-age-issue-Pic.jpg" width="433" height="110" /></a>

&nbsp;
<h4><strong><span style="font-family: georgia;">6.         Easily visible About &amp; <a href="http://harkuchh.com/contact-us/" target="_blank">Contact Me</a> Page</span></strong></h4>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">Many people won’t give their attention towards this but Google does, About page is very essential for Adsense, About page provides info. about the blogger and Blog (the content what your blog contain’s) it creates a bond between you and your readers. If you don’t have About Page on your blog then stop dreaming of Adsense ! Must mention your email address and your name same as that mentioned in the Adsense application this ensure trust that might build Adsense team on you.</span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">Along with About Page `Contact Me` Page is also required though which your readers directly interact with you, this will make your good image to Google. Adsense Team will be glad they are working with one, who not only care about Audience but also like to interact with them and Guide them. In short, this helps Google to make a conclusion that you are more interested in building Audience than earning money.</span>

&nbsp;
<h4><strong><span style="font-family: georgia;">7.         Blog design or Theme</span></strong></h4>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">Always try to make your blog theme as simple as possible, because in creation of a building something big, every small things counted as important part.  Ensure that your blog is quick loading, SEO friendly, simple and easy for use of readers, in easy words let your blog describe what it is all about i.e and let a Gadget Blog looks like a Gadget.</span>

&nbsp;
<h4><strong><span style="font-family: georgia;">8.         Different Ad Networks</span></strong></h4>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">Adsense allows different Ad networks along with it, but not every ! If you have no Adsense ads on your blog and you running Ads of other Networks and now you thinking of apply for Adsense  then I strongly recommend you to remove current ads or do check whether those ads are allowed with Adsense or not because even a minor mistake might count and become a negative point for your blog.</span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">I’m not saying that you stop permanently using other Ads on your blog, You just stop showing other network ads while applying for Adsense and let them off until Adsense team replies about your account acceptance. If Adsense approve your blog for Ads then you can check if those ads are allowed with Adsense or not then make decision of using them and if Adsense reject your application then you can continue with previous Ads.</span>

&nbsp;
<h4><strong><span style="font-family: georgia;">9.         Good Traffic</span></strong></h4>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">See, Google Adsense is the Ads King so they have millions of pending Ads request, Good Traffic is one of the main thing Adsense team always looks for, they focus at profit to their advertisers, Your dream of having Adsense Ads will be uncompleted until your blog get a good traffic at least 80-100 visitors per day, for more details you must check this post `<a href="http://harkuchh.com/time-to-apply-for-adsense/" target="_blank">What is the minimum requirement of Adsense</a>`.</span>

&nbsp;
<h4><strong><span style="font-family: georgia;">10.       Paid Traffic</span></strong></h4>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">People use some cheap ways to get traffic on their site one of the most common example is ‘Buying Traffic’, but Dear if you have a wish to earn from best Ads Company, you strictly avoid those cheap things because it might led to disapproval of your Adsense application, and yeah don’t think you are smart and you can make Google fool ! Instead there are many <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-increase-website-blog-traffic-and-ranking/" target="_blank">ways to get massive traffic to your blog</a>.</span>

&nbsp;
<h4><strong><span style="font-family: georgia;">11.        Avoid Shortcuts, use Complete Words &amp; Sentences in Paragraphs</span></strong></h4>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">We have already discussed about `Quality and Type of Content` but I also wanted to tell my Readers that you must use proper completed sentences with formation of paragraphs after an interval interval, this is recommended by Adsense and avoiding it’s ‘Content Type’ criteria may led to disapproval of your Adsense application.</span>

&nbsp;
<h4><strong><span style="font-family: georgia;">12.        Privacy Policy</span></strong></h4>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">You must have <a href="http://harkuchh.com/privacy/" target="_blank">Privacy</a> policy on your blog, it gives a Professional touch to your blog. It can mention in any way, you can place this page with Titles ‘Privacy policy’ or ‘Terms and conditions’. Google says you must focus tio provide best service to your audience and all the readers and ignoring this may became a reason of disapproval of your Adsense Application, then why to take a chance.</span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">I have discussed all the important points and possible ways and it will help you to get an Approved Adsense for sure, now if you have any confusion, query, or point regarding it, please let me know via comment. It will be like an honor to interact with you.</span>

Read <a href="http://inhindi.harkuchh.com/google-adsense-ke-liye-apply-karne-se-pehle-kin-cheezon-ka-dhyaan-rakhe/" target="_blank"><em><strong>this post in Hindi</strong></em></a>.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are the Back links and How to Build Back Links]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/what-are-the-back-links-and-how-to-build-back-links/"/>
    <updated>2013-05-19T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/what-are-the-back-links-and-how-to-build-back-links</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[To make decent money in Blogging the thing which every blogger needs more than anything else is <b>huge traffic to the blog</b>. We all are the bloggers and we know, every blogger, writer or webmaster wish to get more and <b>more traffic to their blog</b>, because it’s a simple formula i.e. <b>more audiences means more money</b>. I’ve seen many Bloggers doing very hard job on their blogs but still they won’t get the remarkable traffic to their blogs and I noticed generally they won’t pay their attention to <b>Back link building </b>and if you tell them to <b>generate backlinks</b> they thinks that we are asking them to <b>buy back links </b>because<b> </b>they don’t know the proper way to <b>building back links</b>, if you are one of them then must read this post at least twice because if you get it properly it will be the the best <b>SEO help </b>for you, forever<a href="http://bing.com" target="_blank">.</a><a href="http://google.com/" target="_blank">.</a><!--more-->
<h1><b>What are Back links ?</b></h1>
<strong>Backlinks</strong> enable the reader to keep track of some other pages on the web which is linked to the current post they are reading, let’s make it easy with an example, suppose I’ve written a post about <a href="http://harkuchh.com/tag/adsense/" target="_blank"><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Google Adsense</strong></span></a> on my blog and then you come to my blog and read that post, you finds it interesting, then you goes to your own blog and writes a post inspired by my post and you link your post with my original post from where you took the idea (remember giving credit is necessary). Now my post will automatically show that you has linked to it, and it will provide a short snippet of my text and a link to my post, that is the reason why in <b>seo backlink</b> plays a very important role.

<a href="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/What-are-the-Back-links-and-How-to-Build-Back-Links.png"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-8894" alt="What are the Back links and How to Build Back Links" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/What-are-the-Back-links-and-How-to-Build-Back-Links.png" width="350" height="263" /></a>
<h2><b>Why Backlink is important ?</b></h2>
<b> </b>Backlink is one of the key factor to get good raputation to your blog as well as <b>buildings backlinks</b> are one of the best, popular and effective ways to <b>get more traffic to any blog or website </b>not only that it is also said that it is the best <b>search engine optimization strategy</b> generating backlinks..

&nbsp;
<h2><b>How to Build Backlinks ?</b></h2>
Well when it comes to building back links there are two <b>ways to generate backlinks for blogs</b> which are the <b>right way to build backlinks</b> and a <b>wrong way to build back links</b>, as it’s very valuable it take efforts but once you&#8217;ve done the right way, soon you will see the traffic coming to your blog.

&nbsp;
<h2><b>Let’s know what are the way to generate backlinks ?</b></h2>
<b> </b>
<h3>The Wrong Way to Build Backlinks</h3>
I know this very well because I also did it when I was new to this field but thankful to the <a href="http://Labnol.org" target="_blank"><strong>Labnol.org</strong></a> I came to know about it very soon and I stopped doing that, but what’s that ? Actually many people especially newbies normally tries to build their back links by the wrong way at one point due to lack of knowledge about it, people generally do not care that the way the are following is a wrong way, even if they knew. The wrong way to create backlink is, go and post your links every where you can, like in comments, social sites, but this is called spamming, by doing this you’re doing nothing more than posting irrelevant links and remember by following this way you will never get <b>quality backlinks</b>, for example you go to YouTube and open one of the Eninem’s video then in comments you post a comment with URL of your post `How to keep keep your Adsense Account Secure` boy by doing this you’re wasting your time because nobody is going click on that link and eventually your link will be removed.

&nbsp;
<h3><b>The Right Way to Build Quality Backlinks</b></h3>
Now you know what mistakes you were doing let’s know the <b>best way to build Quality backlinks</b>, well the right way to do it is Place your links to the relevant places where it would be useful, meaningful and desirable. if you’ll place your links to such pages then it will surely drive traffic to your blog easily. For instance you have written a post `<span style="text-decoration: underline;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/justin-biebers-untold-story/" target="_blank"><b>You are small enough to make fun of Justin Bieber</b></a></span>`then you go to some other websites with questions or controversy on Justin Bieber then you leave a relevant relevant comment with the link of your article where you have written something related to the topic like `No, you are wrong, you are making fun of Justin Bieber you’re calling him Gay but you don’t know his power <a href="http://harkuchh.com/justin-biebers-untold-story/" target="_blank">check this out</a> first and then see where you stands`.

&nbsp;

That way when readers will see your that strong &amp; meaningful comment related to the subject they are talking about will surely click on your link to see more information. Believe me this is the <b>best way to build smart referral link</b>. This is great quality of work which is important and when someone comes to that post and really find what they are looking for then most probably you will a potential fan and another reader.

&nbsp;

<b>Note</b> : If you will do it gently then you will never feel requirement of <b>search engine optimization packages</b>, <b>link building service</b><b> </b>for seo of your blog and that is the reason building quality backlinks is called as the <b>best search engine optimization </b>tool and it will let you save the expense of <b>search engine optimization software</b>s because the right way will give you <b>free back links</b>. This is the <b>affordable search engine optimization </b>strategy for everyone, after all it’s free.

Happy Blogging &#8230; :)
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Track IP who Performing invalid Clicks on Adsense using StatCounter]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-track-ip-who-performing-invalid-clicks-on-adsense-using-statcounter/"/>
    <updated>2013-04-19T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-track-ip-who-performing-invalid-clicks-on-adsense-using-statcounter</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[Just 2-3 days back I wrote a guest post for Ammar Ali’s  blog Allbloggingtips with title `<a title="checkout the Post" href="http://allbloggingtips.com/2013/04/16/protect-adsense-from-invalid-clicks/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><em>Why and How To Protect Adsense Account From Invalid Clicks?</em></a>` and because I wrote that post so Ammar sir gave me privilege to handle all the comments below that post, when I visited that page next day I saw many comments at the bottom, most of them thanked Author(<em><a href="https://www.facebook.com/Haarkuchh" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">me</a></em>) for sharing that useful info but there I noticed almost every person saying <span style="font-size: medium;">`</span><em>Hey Thanks K.K this is really helpful, I&#8217;m also having a serious issue of invalid clicks on one of my websites these days you have given awesome info. kindly also tell us<strong> how to detect those IP’s from where invalid clicks are being performed on our blog<span style="font-size: large;">`</span></strong></em>, so this post is dedicated to all those bloggers who are keen to know `<strong>How to track invalid Adsense clicks</strong> using StatCounter`<a href="http://google.com" target="_blank">.</a><!--more-->

Every Adsense publisher knows that <strong>Invalid Click Activity</strong> <strong>on Adsense Ads</strong> is really a very serious issue which can lead them to a banned Adsense account from Google and painful thing is that that ban remains permanent. Google may knows everything and it can give you result of any query but still it doesn’t provide any tool to <strong>detect the IP’s from where Invalid Clicks or Click Bombing have done</strong>. So it’s all publisher’s duty to fetch those IP’s to <strong>protecting their <a href="http://harkuchh.com/tag/adsense/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">AdSense account</a> from Invalid Click Activity</strong>.

Many webmasters and bloggers have <strong>lost their AdSense account just because of Invalid Click Activity</strong> and their unawareness, but I’m sure you’re aware enough that’s why you are reading this article on <a href="http://harkuchh.com" target="_blank"><em>Harkuchh.com</em></a>, so let’s discus how to <strong>track the IP address from where you are getting Invalid Clicks on your Ads</strong>.

You can<strong> track every single</strong> <b>IP performing clicks on Adsense Ads</b> <strong>by using StatCounter</strong>, and it’s pretty easy. All you need to do is read and follow the given steps very carefully, must note that<span style="color: #ff0000;"> You can’t afford to miss any point</span>. Let’s start..
<h1><strong>Track invalid Adsense Clicks using Statcounter</strong></h1>
<strong>1.</strong> Create an account on <a href="http://statcounter.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Statcounter</a> by using your permanent email account.

<strong>2.</strong> After that you’ll need to create a new project for your website which you want to track. Click on <b>Add</b><b> New Project </b>and in Project url fill your website URL and fill all the required information like, Project Title, Country, Time Zone, etc. Just select <b>Invisible</b><b> Tracking</b> and you can choose to receive monthly or weekly reports via email<a href="http://yahoo.com/" target="_blank">.</a>

<a href="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/How-To-detect-IP-Performing-invalid-Clicks-on-Adsense-Ads-tutorial.jpg"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-8760" alt="How To detect IP Performing invalid Clicks on Adsense Ads tutorial" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/How-To-detect-IP-Performing-invalid-Clicks-on-Adsense-Ads-tutorial.jpg" width="554" height="292" /></a>

&nbsp;

<strong>3.</strong> Once you’re done with the previous step, StatCounter will <strong>detect the platform of your website</strong> and <strong>gives you a code</strong> with detailed instructions on <b>how to install the stat counter code in your website</b>, just follow the given instruction carefully<a href="http://bing.com" target="_blank">.</a>
<h1><strong>How to Track IP clicking on Ads</strong></h1>
Now once you have set statcounter for your website by following the given instructions, you can start viewing all your site related reports within minutes. Now back to the Statcounter Home page.

<strong>4.</strong> First of all click on your project name (your site) then click on <b>Stats </b>and next then click on <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-track-ip-who-performing-invalid-clicks-on-adsense-using-statcounter"><strong>Exit Link Activity</strong></a> here you can find all the Links on which your visitors clicked to Exit from your site. You can find date, time, exit link name and also the page on which the exit link was clicked. <i>Exit link means the link by clicking which a user jumps to a new page that might be your Ad </i>or a link to any other website.

<a href="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/How-To-detect-IP-Performing-invalid-Clicks-on-Adsense-Ads.jpg"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-8761" alt="How To detect IP Performing invalid Clicks on Adsense Ads" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/How-To-detect-IP-Performing-invalid-Clicks-on-Adsense-Ads.jpg" width="533" height="296" /></a>

If you will examine the links clicked<strong> you can find how many clicks are performed there on advertisements and also at what time the click was made</strong>.

So there you get all the clicks performed on your Ads but this information is not enough because still you are far from those IP’s from where clicks are done so let’s move further, look at the opened page you can easily see a <strong>Magnifying glass icon</strong> before the date in every row of the table. By clicking on that magnifying glass you will get to the page where you can see more detailed information about the visitor who clicked on the link.

<a href="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/How-To-Track-IP-who-Performing-invalid-Clicks-on-Adsense-using-StatCounter.jpg"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-8762" alt="How To Track IP who Performing invalid Clicks on Adsense using StatCounter" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/How-To-Track-IP-who-Performing-invalid-Clicks-on-Adsense-using-StatCounter-580x138.jpg" width="580" height="138" /></a>

<strong>You can find the IP address of the clicker(s) here</strong> along with his location, host name, browser, OS, resolution, ISP, visiting length, and the pages he viewed including the exit link.

Now if you use a bit of your awesome brain you can track all the valid as well as invalid clicks on your Adsense Ads. If you find any IP clicked on your Ads many times it simply means you are <strong>being <a href="http://harkuchh.com" target="_blank">click bombed</a> by that IP</strong>, then you can disable ads temporarily on your website or remove your website from authorized websites list in Google AdSense, you can also ban the fetched IP for showing your Ads from cPanel of your site.

Hey publisher, it is highly recommended that whenever you feel any sudden or suspicious change in your Adsense Account  like <strong>sudden increase in Page CTR</strong> or many clicks but <strong>Zero or very low CPC</strong> then your most important task is to detect the location and IP address of the person doing invalid click activity on your Ads.

This is highly recommended because in case you unfortunately get <b>banned from AdSense because of invalid activity on Ads, </b><strong>you will have stats which you can use at the time of appeal for your account being reinstated</strong><b>.</b>

I hope if your question was <strong>how to check someone’s IP</strong> or how to find those IPs who are doing froud clicks, this <b>complete tutorial to featch the IP of invalid clicker on Ads</b> will help you to keep your Adsense safe and along with your forever, have a look of my other Adsense tutorials those will be also helpful for you. For this awesome guidance I expect a share and a comment from your side, will I get it..
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Subdomain ? How to Create SubDomain of my Website]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/what-is-subdomain-how-to-create-subdomain-of-my-website/"/>
    <updated>2013-04-15T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/what-is-subdomain-how-to-create-subdomain-of-my-website</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<span style="color: #333333;">Few days back I created a Subdomain of my website and when I advertised it on Facebook one of my friend asked me Hey K.K, How did you created Subdomain of your website then I said to him that it’s very easy, you can we can create sub-domain of your website through cPanel.<!--more--></span>

<span style="color: #333333;">He said sorry I don’t know much about cPanel so please tell me in detail `How to create Sub domain in cPanel` then I explained it to him, he suggested me to write a post on it because many people who running their blogs and websites don’t know properly How to create sub-domain of a Domain name, so I’m going to tell you this in very easy language and explained everything very clearly..</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h2><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>What is Subdomain ?</strong></span></h2>
<span style="color: #333333;">Subdomains are the third level domains that are used to organize different types of your web site content. Suppose you have a website on Automobile and now you also want to create a site for Gadgets at that time rather than purchasing a new domain, you can create sub domain using the domain you already own, and by this way you can create multiple site by purchasing only one domain.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;">Same like that I wanted to create a website for career tips then I simply made a subdomain (<a href="http://careerguide.harkuchh.com" target="_blank">careerguide.harkuchh.com</a>) of my domain name Harkuchh.com.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h2><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>How to Create Subdomain of My Website ?</strong></span></h2>
<span style="color: #333333;">To <strong>create a Subdomain</strong> just follow instruction given below..</span>
<ol start="1">
	<li><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Log in to cPanel.</strong></span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;"><a title="Click to see Preview" href="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/SubDomain-of-Website.jpg" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">click on<strong> Subdomains</strong></span></a> under Domain Section.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">Type the <a title="See Preview" href="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/Create-subdomain-of-my-website.jpg" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>subdomain name</strong></span></a> you want in the box before the domain name.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">Click inside the &#8221;<strong>Document Root</strong>&#8221; box and it will auto-fill.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">Hit the <strong>Create</strong> button.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">You Will see a<a title="See preview" href="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/Subdomain-created.jpg" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;"> message</span></a> that Subdomain has been created ! Now Go back to cPanel Home.<strong> </strong></span></li>
</ol>
<span style="color: #333333;"><strong> </strong></span>
<h2><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>How to Install WordPress in Sub-domain</strong></span></h2>
<span style="color: #333333;">After making a Subdomain You must need to install a CMS to work in it, so in order to <strong>Install Wordpress Instructions</strong> are given below..</span>
<ol>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">Click on <a title="See preview" href="http://harkuchh.com/?attachment_id=5083" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Fantastico De Luxe</strong></span></a> in cPanel.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">Now Click on <strong>WordPress </strong>at left.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">Carefully <a title="See Preview" href="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/Click-on-finish-Install.jpg" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>choose Domain</strong></span></a> in which you want to Install WordPress.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">Fill Admin <a href="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/Click-on-finish-Install.jpg" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Username and Password</strong></span></a> in Admin access data section.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;">Click on <strong>Create</strong>.</span></li>
	<li><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Done !</strong> now open your subdomain Wordpress account and work. :lol:</span></li>
</ol>
<span style="color: #333333;"> Must Check : <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-make-backup-of-website/" target="_blank"><em>How to create backup of your blog and site.</em></a></span>
<h2 style="padding-left: 30px;"></h2>
&nbsp;
<h2 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>FAQ’s regarding Subdomains</strong></span></h2>
<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Can I delete Subdomain after once created ?</strong></span></h3>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;">Yes, You can delete is anytime you want from cPanel.</span></p>

<h3><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>How many Subdomains can I create on one Domain name?</strong></span></h3>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;">It’s depend on your hosting company, generally 25 Subdomain are allowed with one domain.</span></p>

<h3><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Can I Use Different CMS in Subdomains ?</strong></span></h3>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;">Yes, If you are using Wordpress in main Domain you are free to choose any CMS for subdomain like Wordpress, Jhoomla.</span></p>

<h3><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>How do I create a subdomain in my control panel ?</strong></span></h3>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;">Stupid read the post from starting, all is written.</span></p>

<h3><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Where to create Subdomains ?</strong></span></h3>
<span style="color: #333333;"><strong>           </strong> Subdomains can be created from cPanel of your website.</span>
<h3><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Change made in main domain will effect subdomain or not ?</strong></span></h3>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;">change in any domain whether it&#8217;s main or subdomain can&#8217;t effect any other.</span></p>
<span style="color: #333333;">Now if anything is not clear to you or you are not getting anything properly feel free to ask. Just comment below.</span>

Read <a href="http://inhindi.harkuchh.com/subdomain-kya-hota-hai-apni-site-ka-sub-domian-kaise-bnau" target="_blank"><em>this post in Hindi.</em></a>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Show Photo with Comment on website]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-show-photo-with-comment-on-website/"/>
    <updated>2013-04-09T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-show-photo-with-comment-on-website</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;"><span style="font-size: large;"><strong>“</strong></span>When I comment on any website or blog then a logo come in front of my name, but I have seen with comments of many people there photo come with there name at the place of logo, I also want that when I comment on any website then my Pic come there with my name instead of that ugly logo, How to do that ?<span style="font-size: large;"><strong>”</strong></span><!--more--></span>

<a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-show-photo-with-comment-on-website/how-to-show-photo-with-comment-on-website/" rel="attachment wp-att-6084"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-6084" alt="How to show Photo with comment on Website" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/01/How-to-show-Photo-with-comment-on-Website-580x120.jpg" width="580" height="120" /></a>

<span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">This was a message I received from a guy few days back, I explained to him all procedure then another guy asked me same question last evening, then I realised writing a post about this will be better instead of explaining same thing again and again to different people. So here is the</span>

<span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;"><b>Procedure to show your photo with your comment at the place of logo..</b>
<span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;"><em>this is very easy and simple and not require more than 3-4 minutes.</em></span></span>
<ul>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">First of all you go to <strong style="color: #000000; font-family: georgia;"><a title="click here" href="https://en.gravatar.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Gravtar.com</a></strong> and fill your email address there.</span></li>
</ul>
<a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-show-photo-with-comment-on-website/show-photo-with-comment-on-website/" rel="attachment wp-att-6083"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-6083" alt="Show photo with comment on website" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/01/Show-photo-with-comment-on-website.jpg" width="548" height="91" /></a>
<ul>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">Then go to your e-mail box there you will find a mail from <b style="color: #000000; font-family: georgia;">Gravtar </b>just click on it and your account is created. Now just fill your username and password.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">Upload your Photo which you want to show with your comment, then click <b style="color: #000000; font-family: georgia;">Next </b>and you will see `<strong style="color: #000000; font-family: georgia;">Choose a rating for your Gravatar</strong>` option with 4 options, click on <b style="color: #000000; font-family: georgia;">rated G </b>(G rated Gravatar is suitable for display on all websites with any audience type). Procedure is 90% completed.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">Now you go to your WordPress Dashboard and click on users there fill your First name, Last name name and Username and your email address ( fill same email, with which you created your Gravtar account). Eventually click on <b style="color: #000000; font-family: georgia;">Update profile.</b></span></li>
</ul>
<span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">You done ! From now whenever you will comment on a website there your photo will shown with your name and comment. Now say, I love Harkuchh.Com :)</span>

Read <a href="http://inhindi.harkuchh.com/website-par-apne-comment-ke-saath-photo-kaise-show-kru/" target="_blank"><em><strong>this post in Hindi</strong></em></a>.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Search Engines Webmasters ?]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/what-are-search-engines-webmasters/"/>
    <updated>2013-04-01T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/what-are-search-engines-webmasters</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[Every <strong>top, popular and reputed Search engines</strong> like <strong>Google, Bing, Baidu</strong> have their search engine webmasters, these are the tools through which a webmaster or any website owner <strong>directly register their websites to these top search engines</strong>.<!--more-->

<a href="http://harkuchh.com/what-are-search-engines-webmasters/webmaster-tools-tips-from-google/" rel="attachment wp-att-8574"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-8574" alt="Webmaster-Tools-Tips-From-Google" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/Webmaster-Tools-Tips-From-Google.jpg" width="336" height="336" /></a>

Registration of any website to the engine webmasters search are essential and are very helpful in finding many things relating to their websites and ownership verification, site crawling, site errors, such as 404 (Not Found), 500 (Internal server error), denied, keywords through which the traffic is coming from search engines that and many other things.

Recommended : <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-submit-website-on-google-and-all-other-top-search-engines/" target="_blank"><em>How to submit your site on all top search engines</em></a>.
<h1><span style="color: #000000;"><b>Steps To Register a site on Google Webmasters</b></span></h1>
<h3><b>Registration To Google Webmasters</b></h3>
<ul>
	<li>Sign in to your Gmail account.</li>
	<li>Now Go to <a href="google.com/webmasters" target="_blank">google.com/webmasters</a>.</li>
	<li>Click On <span style="text-decoration: underline;">Add Site</span> Orange Button.</li>
	<li>Choose Your Suitable Method To Verify Ownership of that website to know google that you owns that website.</li>
</ul>
<ol start="1">
<ol start="1">
	<li><b>HTML Verification</b> - Just download the html file from the page in front of you and upload the given HTML file to your website’s root folder via File Manager in cPanel or through FTP Client like filezilla in the ‘public_html’ folder.</li>
	<li><b>HTML Tag Verification</b> – Click on it and you found a single line of code. Copy it and paste within the header section of your website.</li>
	<li><b>Google Analytics Script </b>- Sign In Google Analytics and link it to your website.</li>
</ol>
</ol>
<ul>
	<li>Now Click Verify. Thus Ownership Verified</li>
	<li>Now Go To Webmasters Tool Home and click on Add/Test Sitemap Button and put your website’s sitemap URL like <strong>http://Harkuchh.com/sitemap.xml.</strong></li>
</ul>
That&#8217;s all, you Done and have fun&#8230; don&#8217;t forget to share.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Apply for Google Adsense Ads]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-apply-for-google-adsense-ads/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-19T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-apply-for-google-adsense-ads</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[I believe anybody reading this post already knows <b>What is Google Adsense,</b> Google adsense Ads program is the king of all the ads providing companies over internet, almost every blogger start his/her blogging career with the willingness of making money from their blog with the help of Goggle’s Adsesne Ads program because it provides <b>Google Ads for free, </b>there are many ads network but <b>ads like google adsense</b> is no-one.<!--more-->

I realized it many times that people don’t know <b>how to apply google adsense</b> Ads to the google, if you are also  one of them then congrats ! now you are at the very right place, here you will get the best answer for your problem..
<h1><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>How to add google adsense to your website</strong></span></h1>
<strong>1.</strong> Go to the Google <a title="click here" href="http://google.com/adsense" target="_blank">Adsense home page</a> (Google.com/Adsense)

<strong>2.</strong> Fill your e-mail (gmail) ID and password and Click on <b>Sign in</b>, (you’ll need to go for Sign up in case you don’t have gmail account yet).
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-apply-for-google-adsense-ads/complete-procedure-to-for-adsense-ads/" rel="attachment wp-att-8403"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-8403" alt="complete procedure to for Adsense Ads" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/complete-procedure-to-for-Adsense-Ads.jpg" width="328" height="288" /></a></p>
&nbsp;

<strong>3.</strong> Now in <b>step 1</b> just click on `<b>Yes, Proceed to Google Account Sign in</b>`.
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-apply-for-google-adsense-ads/how-to-apply-for-adsense/" rel="attachment wp-att-8404"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-8404" alt="How to apply for Adsense" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/How-to-apply-for-Adsense-580x248.jpg" width="580" height="248" /></a></p>
&nbsp;

<strong>4.</strong> Now in <b>step 2 </b>fill your full website address (<em>www.abc.com</em>), select content language `<b>English-English</b>` Tick mark the check box (<em>I have read and Agre&#8230;&#8230;</em>) and click on <b>next</b>.
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-apply-for-google-adsense-ads/how-to-apply-for-adsense-step-2/" rel="attachment wp-att-8405"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-8405" alt="How to apply for Adsense step-2" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/How-to-apply-for-Adsense-step-2-580x458.jpg" width="580" height="458" /></a></p>
&nbsp;

<strong>5.</strong> In <b>step 3</b>, select your country name (India) then click on account type (Individual), then in Payee name fill your complete name, then in next boxes fill up your complete address House number, city, state, postal code etc very carefully, then fill up your contact no. and then in the box given next to How did you get to know adsense select <b>Friends/collegue</b> and in <b>email preferences</b>, after thaty click on first radio button (<em>customized help and performance&#8230;.</em>) and finally click on `<b>Submit my application</b>`.
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-apply-for-google-adsense-ads/how-to-apply-for-adsense-step-3-jh/" rel="attachment wp-att-8406"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-8406" alt="How to apply for Adsense step-3 jh" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/How-to-apply-for-Adsense-step-3-jh.jpg" width="643" height="820" /></a></p>
&nbsp;

<b>Also read</b> : <a href="http://harkuchh.com/ads-providing-sites-for-blogs-and-websites/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Alternatives to google adsense</a>.

Done ! now your blog or website is submitted to Google for approval of Adsense Ads, after some hours of this submission you’ll receive an email from Google about the partially checking of your website and in that mail Google will ask you to generate Ad code by giving you an Adsense Account with proper instructions and after generating code you’ll need to place that code somewhere on your site, you can place that code in Widgets (text) or ad space given in your theme or somewhere in your post, once you place the ad code on your site Google will come to check your website completely and if their content team approves your content, then the area where you have placed that generated ad code will start showing Adsense ads and you are ready to place the ads anywhere on your site.

In case Google reject your Adsense application then don’t think it’s all over, Google always gives the reason why your request is not got approved you just work hard to fix that ponit and after some day of working on your blog send the application again to Google, by chance google refuse again to give you adsense you try again but after working on point google mentioned in refusal mail, I people who got approved by google in their tenth try, which means Google may take time but it will surely give ads to google.

Google don’t give ads easily same like a girl not accepts a friendship proposal easily, to understand this better way you must read my `<a href="http://harkuchh.com/google-is-a-girl-i-can-prove-it/" target="_blank"><strong>Google is a girl, I can prove it</strong></a>` post.
<h2><span style="color: #000000;"><b>Adsense is the most popular Online Ads service because&#8230; </b></span></h2>
<ul>
	<li>Adsense Ads is the <b>Google ads for free </b>it won’t take anything from the publisher.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
	<li><b>google adsense for mobile apps</b> or <b>adsense mobile ads</b> helps the publishers to show ads on mobile devices too.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
	<li>By using <b>google adsense advertising</b> people making decent money by working anywhere.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
	<li>Adsense provides <b>free banner ads </b>which help users to see related information on any device.</li>
</ul>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Common FAQ’s about Blog and Blogging]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/most-common-faqs-about-blog-and-blogging/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-17T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/most-common-faqs-about-blog-and-blogging</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<span style="color: #333333;">Believe me I’m not showing off but it’s true that my this blog became quite popular in very short period and it’s really great to answer questions of many people regularly, which they ask through comments and mails after reading my posts, I found some questions very common and frequent asked by many so here I’m trying to present all FAQ&#8217;s in a package..<!--more--></span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h4><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>I want to show small part of my posts and if the visitor click on <em>read more</em> than full post will open, How to do this ?</strong></span></h4>
<span style="color: #333333;">Actually this is very easy and simple too, you won’t have to do any hard effort for that, while writing your post before publishing it just go to point after which you want to hide post and just click on<a title="See Pics of button" href="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/Insert-More-Tag.jpg" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong> Insert More Tag</strong></span></a> button given in toolbar above or you can also press <strong>Alt+Shift+T</strong>. Done.
</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h4><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Many Comments Come in my blog as spams what are these, can I approve them.</strong></span></h4>
<span style="color: #333333;">Spams are the comment responsible for comment based hacking of blogs and website, these are trapdoor to access your site database illegally, never approve them, and must<a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-install-akismet-in-wordpress-for-free/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;"> install Akismet</span></a> as it is the best tool to protect website from spams.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h4><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>I commented on my friend’s site and he told me that my comment came to his site as spam, how did it happened ?</strong></span></h4>
<span style="color: #333333;">Some words and links are not allowed to post in comments and when we do commenting using such words or links it goes into spam.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h4><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>What is Subdomains, How to make a Subdomain of my Website ?</strong></span></h4>
<span style="color: #333333;"><span style="color: #ff0000;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/what-is-subdomain-how-to-create-subdomain-of-my-website/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #ff0000;"><strong>Check thi</strong>s</span></a> </span>Out&#8230;</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h4><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Blog and Website, are these things same or different ?</strong></span></h4>
<span style="color: #333333;">This is actually a good question, and it’s answer is that blogs and website are quite different things, a website is that which make once and don’t need daily updations like a website of an Institute but blog which we make are diffrent as they need regular updations and we do interact with our visitors.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h4><span style="color: #333333;"><strong> </strong><strong>If my blog will be hacked then do I need to do all the work again ?</strong></span></h4>
<span style="color: #333333;">No if you have backup of your blog then you just need to do few tasks and you will recover your blog easily and even in very small time but if you don’t create backups of your blog regularly you will be fuc_ed up ! see <em><span style="color: #ff0000;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-make-backup-of-website/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #ff0000;">how to create backup</span></a></span> of blogs and website. </em></span>

<span style="color: #333333;"><em> </em></span>
<h4><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>What is the most common reason of hacking of a website, how to prevent it ?</strong></span></h4>
<span style="color: #333333;">As simplest method of doing anything become as the most common method so Comment based hacking is most common type of hacking, <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-protect-website-from-comment-based-hacking/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">see this</span></a> for datailed info.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h4><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Can I use Different CMS’s in different subdomains of a Domain name ?</strong></span></h4>
<span style="color: #333333;">Yes you can use different CMS for different subdomains, like if you are using WordPress in main Domain you are free to use Jhoomla or any other CMS in subdomains. If you have 5 subdomains you are can use 5 CMS for them.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h4><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>What is Indexing of website, How to Register My website on Google and all leading search engines ?</strong></span></h4>
<span style="color: #333333;">A search engine show your blog posts on it’s page only and only if it will be Indexed in their database, so must <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-submit-website-on-google-and-all-other-top-search-engines/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">register your blog</span></a> on all popular search engines like Google, Bing, Msn etc.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h4><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>What are Plugins, Which are the most popular and useful Plug-ins for WordPress Blog/Website ?</strong></span></h4>
<span style="color: #333333;">Plug-ins are like small software packages designed for various purpose it widely used in making of websites and using them can save efforts and time, these are like awesome free gifts to developers, see the<a href="http://harkuchh.com/most-important-plugins-for-wordpress-blog/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;"> list on most useful plug-ins</span></a>.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h4><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>What is the best time to apply for Ads to Adsense ?</strong></span></h4>
<span style="color: #333333;">Many people start applying for ads to adsense just after posting 8-10 posts on their blogs which is not good, you also don&#8217;t need hundreds of posts and thousands of visitors but you must need to ready for them see what&#8217;s the <a href="http://harkuchh.com/tag/adsense/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">right time to apply for adsense</span></a>.
</span>

<span style="color: #333333;">If you are new in Blogging field I strongly recommend you to save a bookmark of <em><strong><a href="http://harkuchh.com/category/blogging/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">this link</span></a></strong></em> as here all info is very valuable and in very easy language you must try to read all posts there at least once. Now if you have any query about blog and blogging must comment here, by following this way I also learn many things and I will be very thankful to you for that.</span>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Pop-ups or what are the Pop up ads ?]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/what-are-pop-ups-or-what-are-the-pop-up-ads/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/what-are-pop-ups-or-what-are-the-pop-up-ads</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<b>Popup ads</b> or <b>pop up advertising</b> are the advertisements that show up in a new browser window when you click or hover on a link or image while surfing on internet. The overall <b>definition of a popup</b> is `<em>a browser window that appears out of nowhere as you are viewing content on the web.</em>` There are also programs known as <b>pop under ads</b>, which display windows behind your web browser window. As a user is surfing the web and visiting various websites, new windows may suddenly (<em>and without user initiation</em>) open and display advertisements and promotions.<!--more-->

<a href="http://harkuchh.com/what-are-pop-ups-or-what-are-the-pop-up-ads/what-are-pop-up-ads/" rel="attachment wp-att-8100"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-8100" alt="what are pop up ads" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/what-are-pop-up-ads.jpeg" width="348" height="341" /></a>

<span style="color: #ff0000;"><strong>Pop-Ups</strong> are NOT security risks</span>. They can NOT carry Spy Bots, Viruses, or Trojans. The reason they may be blocked is that, if they are designed to open automatically, they can be annoying nuisances!
<h1>Major Concerns of PopUps</h1>
<ul>
	<li>A screen flooded with pop-ups may make navigating the web stressful and difficult.</li>
	<li>At times, they may look like browsers of normal web pages and can cause confusion to the users. A pop-up may not be even related to the site itself, thus annoying the user with its irrelevance to the site and its obstruction to the browsing experience.</li>
	<li>Some pop-ups contain inappropriate or even pornographic content, which you may not like to watch.</li>
	<li>Some pop-ups appear as a result in the site being reloaded, causing loss of information for the users.</li>
</ul>
<h1><b>How to Block Popup Ads </b></h1>
Ads pop up can be a tremendous annoyance, but there are ways to deal with them. Your best bet would be to close the window and not interact with those <b>popups</b>. The <b>best way to prevent from Popup ads</b> is don&#8217;t connect to internet without enabling firewall and Anti-virus software. Increase the security settings in the browser so that Activex controls won&#8217;t install automatically and these <b>free classifieds</b> won’t come up to your screen.

Default browser of Microsoft Windows `Internet Explorer` is configured to <b>block all pop-up ads</b> by default. If you don’t like the blocker warning or its associated beep, you can control the <b>pop-up blocker’s</b> settings. Also, any good Anti-virus package can be a great tool for avoiding pop-ups.

For bloggers pop up advertising can be proved as a great source of income from their blog, but we recommend you to don’t go for it, people hates it and most probably you too.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Topics to Write Posts for Blog]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/best-topics-to-write-a-post-for-blog/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/best-topics-to-write-a-post-for-blog</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<span style="font-family: georgia;">We have talked a lot about blogging in our<a href="http://harkuchh.com/category/blogging/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;"> blogging category</span></a>, in posts <a href="http://harkuchh.com/what-is-blogging-why-blogging-becoming-popular-in-youth/" target="_blank"><span style="font-family: georgia;">What is Blogging</span></a>, <a href="http://harkuchh.com/top-blogs-and-bloggers-of-india-and-their-earnings/" target="_blank"><span style="font-family: georgia;">Top Blogs &amp; Bloggers</span></a>, <a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/" target="_blank"><span style="font-family: georgia;">Adsense Tips</span></a>, <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-write-a-good-post-in-a-less-time-for-blog/" target="_blank"><span style="font-family: georgia;">how to write post in less time</span></a> etc but I observed from my personal experience and readers comments and also from chats with bloggers on facebook and Twitter, that making a blog is not a task, it’s easy, anyone can make a blog and run it on Internet.<!--more--></span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">The problem is to picking up the blog to top means getting good ranking, <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-increase-website-blog-traffic-and-ranking/" target="_blank"><span style="font-family: georgia;">decent traffic</span></a> and remarkable income, Many of my friends and collegue bloggers always complaining that their blogs are fail in getting traffic from search engines, Well for getting good traffic you must need to write something which attaract the internet users especially the youth, and if your problem is which niche to choose for best post, stop worrying here we are going to share all topics which are most in demand and you can say evergreen topics for writing posts, have a look..</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><strong>10. Health</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="font-family: georgia;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-topics-to-write-a-post-for-blog/post-about-health-tips-pic-hd/" rel="attachment wp-att-4697"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><img class="alignleft  wp-image-4697" title="post about health tips pic hd" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/post-about-health-tips-pic-hd.png" width="126" height="126" /></span></a>Today is the time of technology so the world going online, people tends to find solutions for their health related matters online. If you have a enough knowledge on medicine and various fitness related issues and you think that you have potential to provide people great information and solutions for their health problems and giving them worth reading and valuable tips regarding fitness and Health, then you will see a great traffic difference on your blog in just a short time. For example You can share post like How to make your body strong and fit with staying on home.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><strong>9. <a href="http://harkuchh.com/popular-fashion-items-which-never-go-out-of-style/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Fashion</span></a></strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="font-family: georgia;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-topics-to-write-a-post-for-blog/fashion-pics-hd/" rel="attachment wp-att-4705"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><img class="alignright  wp-image-4705" title="Fashion Pics hd" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/Fashion-Pics-hd-300x220.jpg" width="180" height="132" /></span></a>Well We know Health and fitness topics are mostly searched only by those who are either suffering from some disease or they want to learn tips for their fitness, but above health, comes Fashion. You will be agree with me if I say “Knowing about health is a need but learning all about fashion is an addiction”. If you have intereset in glamour world and you love to read and write about Fashion trends which leading the society, believe me you can really make huge money with it. People from all around the globe use internet as the best and most easiest way to know about latest fashion and also follow it.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><strong>8. Relationships</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="color: #333333;"><img class="alignleft  wp-image-4700" style="color: #0000ee;" title="Relationship Pic HD" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/Relationship-Pic-HD-253x300.png" width="91" height="108" /></span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">No surprise in this - most of the people have<a href="http://harkuchh.com/top-10-things-to-do-after-break-up/" target="_blank"><span style="font-family: georgia;"> emotional part</span></a> in their personalities which leaves dark effect on their entire life. People takes internet as their best friend the most secure way to improve their relationships, they do believing in the idea of self-aiding learning online about professional working relationships, love relationships and also having advises from people around the world. So it will be a boon for your blog if you start writing good content on relationship.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><strong>7. Finance</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="font-family: georgia;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-topics-to-write-a-post-for-blog/finance-pic-hd/" rel="attachment wp-att-4702"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><img class="alignright  wp-image-4702" title="finance Pic hd" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/finance-Pic-hd-300x269.jpg" width="156" height="140" /></span></a>Money, most probably the only thing which will remain Man’s love till the end of this existing world. Money is the essential need of everyone and this need make common nature of people - to learn ways to double their money encourage them to search about such methods, so Blogs with domain related to ways of improving finances and helping them setting up their own business, telling ways to manage their money always attract them, and it help in generating good traffic for a blog and also good revenue.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><strong>6. Question and Answer Blogs</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="font-family: georgia;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-topics-to-write-a-post-for-blog/question-and-answer/" rel="attachment wp-att-4703"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><img class="alignleft  wp-image-4703" title="question-and-answer" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/question-and-answer.jpg" width="192" height="191" /></span></a>It’s a simple theory remember your achool days to make this concept clear, just think which teacher you preferred to visit the most in times of need, the one who always had a solution of your problems or the one who always use the words come later ? I know what your answer is and I hope We all have same views about it. Similarly, starting a blog or writing posts with niche of active question and answer session will easily generate remarkable revenue. People love to come that places where they can be listened and can get their answer for their queries. For best example we can see answer.com, so you can start a question and answer blog and make great income through it.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><strong>5. Celebrities</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="color: #333333;"><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-4699" title="Celebrities pic hd" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/Celebrities-pic-hd-300x159.jpg" width="300" height="159" /></span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">Celebrities is always considered as the easiest and the most interesting topics to adopt in a blogging career to start writing reviews, updates, latest photos, their videos (specially uncenssored :P) and everything associated with them. The best part for this category is for writing about them you won’t have to be highly qualified, all you need to do this, is your interest in entertainment world.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><strong>4. Buy and sell</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="font-family: georgia;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-topics-to-write-a-post-for-blog/buy-sell-pic-hd/" rel="attachment wp-att-4706"><span style="color: #333333;"><img class="alignleft  wp-image-4706" title="buy sell Pic hd" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/buy-sell-Pic-hd-300x200.jpg" width="189" height="126" /></span></a>You may have familiar with olx.com or many online shopping websites, now a days Online shopping has taken up the physical market with a great pace, you just need to choose what you need or what want direct from your computer table (or also bed if you using laptop :P) and get it delivered at your doorsteps. If you start providing such facility of online shopping with best deals you can easily get bulk of visitors each day.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><strong>3. Social Media</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="font-family: georgia;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-topics-to-write-a-post-for-blog/social-media-pics-hd/" rel="attachment wp-att-4707"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><img class="wp-image-4707 alignright" title="social media pics hd" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/social-media-pics-hd.jpg" width="205" height="188" /></span></a>Social media is a became a need now, do you know any person who use internet regularly and won’t have any account on any social site, you know your answer very well. Today people without using social sites feel always something wrong and even incompleteness in the day, one might not have a bank account but must be having three- four accounts on different social networking websites especially Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn. So if you read interesting, creative and valuable content related to social media people will love to visit your blog again and again because People want to know each and everything about their social media. For example you can<a href="http://harkuchh.com/category/fb/" target="_blank"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><em> see this</em></span></a>.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><strong>2. Technology</strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="font-family: georgia;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-topics-to-write-a-post-for-blog/technology-pic-hd/" rel="attachment wp-att-4708"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><img class="alignleft  wp-image-4708" title="technology pic hd" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/technology-pic-hd-300x199.jpg" width="210" height="139" /></span></a>As I already said this is the technology generation, a latest technology become older the next day this is the field I think changing with the most speed, just remember time of five years back only few reputed people having mobile phones but today everyone have a latest technology mobile phone in pocket (even I have a cellphone :P) People In this Hi-tech world, staying up to date with the latest technology been revealed in the market is mandatory and they do regulalry suffer on internet for searching these things, the biggest benefit of choosing this niche as your blogging topic is, whenever a new <a href="http://harkuchh.com/category/technology/" target="_blank"><span style="font-family: georgia;">gadget</span></a> or device launch in to the market, it automatically creates a hype, big enough to bring visitors to your blog to know more about it. This will give you huge traffic as well as huge income.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>
<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><strong>1. Blogging <a href="http://harkuchh.com/category/blogging/" target="_blank">Tips</a></strong></span></h3>

<hr />

<span style="font-family: georgia;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-topics-to-write-a-post-for-blog/blogging-tips-300x225/" rel="attachment wp-att-4709"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-4709" title="blogging-tips-300x225" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/blogging-tips-300x225.jpg" width="300" height="225" /></span></a>Blogging became most popular in last half decade, this is a great business many people all around the world making six digit or even more income every month by doing blogging (see this list), so many people joining this field every day and The best sources to learn for the new bloggers are the blogs themselves so they search for basic tips on internet and if you write for them in easy and clear language then your blog will be visited many time more than the ordinary visits. This is the reason I regularly write posts on Blogging tips and because of this my blog’s world alexa ranking reach<a title="Checkout Proof" href="http://www.alexa.com/siteinfo/harkuchh.com#trafficstats" target="_blank"><span style="font-family: georgia;"><em> 61k in just 6 months</em></span></a>.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">I recommend you to write and help newbie bloggers and also get good income through ads, beacuse if your blog will get decent traffic then chance of clicking on ads will be increse. require you to have the capability and knowledge about web designing and web development so that whatever content you share, it gains reliability for you from your readers.</span>

<span style="color: #333333;"> </span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">Now I think many people got their title for their next posts, I’m sure this post will help every bloggers to making their blogs, If you like this information please share this, and also comment if you have any other point which you think should be include in this list.</span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">Also See : <em><strong><a title="Permanent Link to Secure your Gmail Account with 2-Step Verification" href="http://harkuchh.com/secure-your-gmail-account-with-2-step-verification/" rel="bookmark"><span style="color: #333333;">Secure your Gmail Account with 2-Step Verification</span></a></strong></em></span>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add Robots.Txt file to WordPress Blog]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-add-robots-txt-file-to-wordpress-blog/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-23T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-add-robots-txt-file-to-wordpress-blog</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<span style="font-family: georgia;">Before proceeding let’s know a bit about <b>Why to add or Set Robot.txt file</b> ? The robots.txt file is the key to control the crawlers activity on your website/blog, this helps you to keep some directories of blog out of range of crawling while allowing some, Adding Robots file makes your Wordpress blog more relevant as it <b>block un-relevant url from indexing to the search engines</b>, in easy words by adding robots file, your blog commands google bot  `Hey Robot ! don&#8217;t index my Harkuchh.com/wp-admin that’s not important to index !`<!--more--></span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">Now let’s see <b>how to add Robots file to your blog</b>, Believe me I’m telling you <b>the best and easiest way to add Robot file to your blog, </b>there are some alternative ways to add robot file via plugin but using much plugins are not good, so here is the <b>simple guidance to add Robots.txt to a blog</b>, it can be added through cPanel, Don’t worry it’s easy, let’s start..</span>
<ul>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;">Go to cPanel</span></li>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;" data-mce-mark="1">Click on </span><b style="font-family: georgia;">File Manager</b><span style="font-family: georgia;" data-mce-mark="1"> under </span><b style="font-family: georgia;">File</b><span style="font-family: georgia;" data-mce-mark="1"> Section and open Home Directory by clicking Go.</span></li>
</ul>
<a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-add-robots-txt-file-to-wordpress-blog/click-on-file-manager-under-file-section/" rel="attachment wp-att-7326"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-7326" alt="Click on File Manager Under File Section" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/Click-on-File-Manager-Under-File-Section.jpg" width="574" height="449" /></a>
<ul>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;">Click on </span><b style="font-family: georgia;">Public_Html</b><span style="font-family: georgia;"> at Left side of the Screen</span></li>
</ul>
<a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-add-robots-txt-file-to-wordpress-blog/click-on-public_html-at-left-side-of-the-screen/" rel="attachment wp-att-7327"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-7327" alt="Click on Public_Html at Left side of the Screen" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/Click-on-Public_Html-at-Left-side-of-the-Screen.jpg" width="339" height="454" /></a>
<ul>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;">Now click on </span><b style="font-family: georgia;">New File</b><span style="font-family: georgia;"> from the top of the screen</span></li>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;">Name it as robots.txt and click on </span><b style="font-family: georgia;">Create New File</b><span style="font-family: georgia;"> (file create)</span></li>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;">Now click on new </span><b style="font-family: georgia;">robots.txt</b><span style="font-family: georgia;"> file</span></li>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;">Then click </span><b style="font-family: georgia;">Edit</b><span style="font-family: georgia;"> Icon and then click on `Edit` again</span></li>
</ul>
<h2><span style="font-family: georgia;" data-mce-mark="1"><span style="font-family: georgia;" data-mce-mark="1"><span style="font-family: georgia;" data-mce-mark="1"><span style="font-family: georgia;" data-mce-mark="1"><span style="font-family: georgia;" data-mce-mark="1"><span style="font-family: georgia;" data-mce-mark="1"><span style="font-family: georgia;" data-mce-mark="1">What to add in Robots.Txt file </span></span></span></span></span></span></span></h2>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">By adding Allow and Disallow commands in robots file we tell the crawler exactly <b>what to crawl and what to not</b>, so here we Disallow all those thing to crawl which are not important to be on Google or any search engine and which are having very important and critical info about the blog, like it’s directories, various parts and components of blog, the thing which we need to exclude from crawling in a normal WordPress blog are given here..</span>
<div style="height: 860px; width: 600px; float: left; background: none repeat scroll 0% 0% #f0f0f0; padding-left: 60px;">Sitemap: http://<strong>Harkuchh.com</strong>/sitemap.xml
Sitemap: http://<strong>Harkuchh.com</strong>/sitemap-image.xmlUser-agent: Mediapartners-Google
Disallow:User-Agent: *
Allow: /

User-agent: *
# disallow all files in these directories
Disallow: /cgi-bin/
Disallow: /wp-admin/
Disallow: /wp-content/
Disallow: /wp-includes/
Disallow: /wp-content/plugins/
Disallow: /wp-content/themes/
Disallow: /wp-content/upgrade/
Disallow: /trackback
Disallow: /*trackback
Disallow: /*trackback*
Disallow: /*/trackback
Disallow: /*.html/$
Disallow: /xmlrpc.php
Disallow: /?s=*
Disallow: *?wptheme
Disallow: /blog/?p=*
Disallow: /blog/search?
Disallow: /xmlrpc.php
disallow: /*?*
Disallow: /?p=*

User-agent: Googlebot-Image
Allow:

User-agent: Adsbot-Google
Allow: /

User-agent: Googlebot-Mobile
Allow: /

</div>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">Copy and paste the complete given list of commands to your robots.txt file and just make a small change –add your blog’s URL at the place of mine Harkuchh.com. Don’t ignore to <b>add robots file</b> to your blog because it just not keep your blog’s critical infosafe instead it also helps in <b>better SEO of your blo</b>g.</span>

Read <strong><a href="http://inhindi.harkuchh.com/robots-txt-file-wordpress-blog-mein-kaise-add-karein/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><em>this post in Hindi</em></a></strong>.
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Money from Blog without Adsense]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-make-money-from-blog-without-adsense/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-18T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-make-money-from-blog-without-adsense</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<span style="font-family: georgia;"><strong>Blog without Adsense</strong> sound bitter. We all know that anyone who make blog have some purposes for sure, some wants to spread their knowledge, some wants to share their thoughts and majority of people <b>make blogs to earn money</b> from Adsense but how those people earn money whose blogs have no Adsense, as you must have noticed some very highly ranked and popular blogs without Adsense, but we know <b>no adsense means no money</b> through ads, so question arises `What happen to those blogs who have no Adsense Ads.`<!--more--></span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">I’m a blogger having a blog so I know the importance of Adsense very well and if you are reading this post then most probably you also a member of Bloggers category and know <b>how essential Adsense is for a blog</b>.</span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">Normally people think Adsense Ads is the only <b>way of earnings from a blog</b> but this is as true as I’m the richest person of the world. I’ve already told you, there are many top blogs without adsense now I want to add ` they have no Adsense it doesn’t mean they are getting nothing` instead they still making decent money through their blogs.</span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">How would you feel if I tell you <b>blogs making millions of bucks withou Adsense</b>, I know it’s like a joke of the day for you but it’s true. Let’s we discus it’s mechanism&#8230;</span>
<h2><span style="font-family: georgia;">How Blogs making Money without Adsense</span></h2>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">They make money via Ads !! surprised, please don’t be. Actually they make money through Ads but not adsense not even from <a href="http://harkuchh.com/ads-providing-sites-for-blogs-and-websites/" target="_blank"><b>Adsense alternatives</b></a> they make big money through Direct Ads marketing which is professionally known as <b>Affiliate marketing</b>, from these direct ads they earn big and fix amount for long term even without up and down like Adsense.</span>

<a href="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/How-to-Make-Money-from-Blog-without-Adsense-answer-is-Direct-ads-marketing-or-Affiliate-marketing.jpg"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-6810" alt="How to Make Money from Blog without Adsense answer is Direct ads marketing or Affiliate marketing" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/How-to-Make-Money-from-Blog-without-Adsense-answer-is-Direct-ads-marketing-or-Affiliate-marketing.jpg" width="458" height="307" /></a>
<h2><span style="font-family: georgia;">What is Direct Ads marketing </span></h2>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">Well it’s preety easy to understand, all you need is bit common sense ! Do you know, in the procedure of Adsense Ads google plays a broker role, suppose Apple is going to lauch a new featured iPad in market then Apple contacts Google for promote that New iPad and Apple pay 3$ to google for one promotion of their product.</span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">Then Google shows that iPad on our blogs and website via Adsense Ads and when a visitor of our blog click on that iPad Ad it’s counted as one promotion ( 1 click) and google gives us 2$ for that click, but Apple paid 3$ to google, then where do the remained 1$ gone, well it gone to the Google’s account for promoting the product via it’s <strong><a href="http://harkuchh.com/tag/adsense/" target="_blank">Adsense</a> Ads Service</strong>.</span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">Same thing happens in direct marketing but without the presence of Google i.e. companies contacts the blog owners directly without broker and they pay a fix amountof money for placing their product on blog in the form of image and link ads, and there is no Google to take credit of that amount.</span>
<h2><span style="font-family: georgia;">Requirements for Direct Ads</span></h2>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">Now if you don’t have adsense Ads because of any <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-keep-my-google-adsense-account-safe/" target="_blank">reason(s)</a> then don’t think your blog have no future and you won’t leave blogging (many people quit blogging for this reason) you still have many <b>ways to make money online</b>, you just need to fulfill some requirement in order to get Directs ads on your blog which are..</span>
<ul>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;">High <a title="click to see how to increase Ranking of your blog" href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-increase-website-blog-traffic-and-ranking/" target="_blank">Alexa Rank</a></span></li>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;">Google Page Rank</span></li>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;">Quality Content</span></li>
</ul>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">Once you fulfill these </span><b style="font-family: georgia;">basic requirements for direct ads on blog</b><span style="font-family: georgia;"> people will come and request you for place just one image or link of their company product and believe me they offer that amount which you even never have expected.</span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;">Affiliate marketing is the most popular way of earning from a blog who have no Adsense but this is not the one and only, people also making good money from..</span>
<ul>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;">Affiliate Marketing</span></li>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;">Selling Ad Space</span></li>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;">Using Text Ads</span></li>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;">Paid Reviews</span></li>
	<li><span style="font-family: georgia;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/ads-providing-sites-for-blogs-and-websites/" target="_blank">Adsense alternatives</a>.</span></li>
</ul>
<span style="font-family: georgia;">So moral of the story is <strong>Blogging have a great future without Adsense</strong> <strong>too</strong>, so from now start working for it, fulfill the requirements and ready for </span><b style="font-family: georgia;">earn huge money from internet</b><span style="font-family: georgia;">, after all I’m here to tell you </span><b style="font-family: georgia;">how to earn from blog without Adsense</b><span style="font-family: georgia;">, so you can still </span><b style="font-family: georgia;">earn money through internet</b><span style="font-family: georgia;"> and best thing is you can </span><b style="font-family: georgia;">earn by doing work from home</b><span style="font-family: georgia;"> or anywhere you want, Happy Blogging.</span>

<span style="font-family: georgia;"><em><strong>check out</strong></em> : <a href="http://harkuchh.com/time-to-apply-for-adsense/" target="_blank">What is the best time to apply for Adsense Ads</a></span>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
