<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Technology | harkuchh]]></title>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/blog/categories/technology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-13T00:02:41+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://harkuchh.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[harkuchh]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five Reasons Why Every Blogger Should Learn Programming]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/five-reasons-for-why-you-should-learn-programming/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-07T23:47:12+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/five-reasons-for-why-you-should-learn-programming</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In this post I am writing about why every blogger (and every person in general) should learn to code. Programming as itself is an asset that will make you a better and smarter person. Most important benefit you&rsquo;ll get is the ability to make <strong>literate decisions</strong>. You&rsquo;ll learn how to break down that large problem you are facing, and how to solve it&rsquo;s one piece at a time. Besides, it gives ou great level of confidence.<br/>
Here are five reasons to convince you to learn programming.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>You want to be a God</h2>

<p>I heard yea! So you wanna be a God? Well, you can be actually. Programmers are mini Gods who create little worlds with their programs and control everything. Literally. It&rsquo;s hard to understand this feeling without really experiencing it. But the ultimate control building a software offers is addictive. I myself was a gaming addict in my school time, and now gaming addiction is turned into coding addiction.</p>

<p>The amount of automation you can put in your daily work truly make you feel like a God. It makes me feel real good when I see my script running and think my code can do in 30 minutes what my peers at harkuchh would have taken 4-5 days.</p>

<h2>One blogger who know coding equals ten average bloggers</h2>

<p>Don&rsquo;t get hyper. Let me explain why. Programming skills are valuable in every field directly or remotely related to computers and internet off course.I mean your programming skills become specially important in fields which are completely dependent on computers and Internet. Blogging is such a case. I joined Harkuchh &ndash; The Blogging Valley about a month ago, and the technological improvements we&rsquo;ve made here improved our productivity while brought down the expenses. Although many things are under experiment phase, the time we&rsquo;ve saved so far which would have been wasted in trying things which don&rsquo;t bring any profit is enormous.</p>

<p>To give an example, consider data gathering. We all need to collect data from various sources, many times it involve just copy pasting data from some other source. We&rsquo;ve built a software to automate such things, and saved days of work.</p>

<p>But there are more benefits than I can describe here. Enough benefits that Krishan Kummar (founder of harkuchh.com) is learning to code. (We are thinking about starting giving programming classes to bloggers. Please comment or mail us if you are interested).</p>

<h2>Dream, Believe, Achieve</h2>

<p>These quotes all seem too good to be practical in real world. This might be true, but not in the world where you can even be a God. You just wish if there was a software which would do <em>something awesome here</em>, and you roll out your emacs (or your favorite editor), and voila! It&rsquo;s there. Anything is possible, all you need to do is to believe in your wit and skills. Sounds too good to be real? Welcome to the world of programmers :)</p>

<h2>It teaches you to make better decisions in life</h2>

<p>I just can&rsquo;t emphasize how beneficial it is for anyone (including you bloggers) to have some programming skills. Even if you don&rsquo;t become a wiz, acquaintance with programming is a very much helpful. When you don&rsquo;t know anything about how your websites and software are actually working under-the-hood, you are like riding a bike eye-folded. You either hit a tree or something, or you go too slow.</p>

<p>Most important benefit you&rsquo;ll get is the ability to make <strong>literate decisions</strong>. You&rsquo;ll learn how to break down that large problem you are facing, and how to solve it&rsquo;s one piece at a time. Besides, it give you great level of confidence. When you think of a crazy idea, and you have good programming skills under your belt, you quickly analyze all the steps which you&rsquo;ll need to take to make that awesome thing. You carry this habit to your real life. And suddenly all things become simple, because you&rsquo;ll quickly analyze everything and sort out plans for doing things which seem impossible or very hard to others. It&rsquo;ll give you a new perspective in your career, as well as in your life.</p>

<h2>Programming is fun, and it makes you smarter</h2>

<p>I ditched gaming for coding, not because it give me money, but simply because it&rsquo;s more fun. I still play games once in a while when I want my brain to relax, but I&rsquo;m yet to find a game which&rsquo;ll give me more thrill than coding. If you follow the right steps (like choose right first language, right teacher, right things to do in your first steps in coding world), programming is like playing a very powerful computer game. Projects you do are your highscore and skills you gain are your reward, that&rsquo;ll stay with you for rest of your life. Besides, remember all your kids (the next generation) will be taught coding in schools like we are taught poems, then your children will ask you questions related to coding, what you gonna do then? ;)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strong Passwords, Weak Passwords: How to Generate Strongest Possible Passwords Which You Can Remember]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/strong-passwords-weak-passwords-how-to-generate-strongest-possible-passwords-which-you-can-remember/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-04T00:46:09+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/strong-passwords-weak-passwords-how-to-generate-strongest-possible-passwords-which-you-can-remember</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Passwords we know, the most common method used by almost all websites for authenticating users. But how good is this method? Well, the strength of this method partially depend on the strength of the password we choose.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>What&rsquo;s the strength of a password?</h2>

<p>Strength of a password is determined by a number of things.
* <strong>Character set</strong><br/>
Most important thing which make a password strong is its character set. Character set of a password means which characters are used in the password, like lower case characters, upper case characters, numbers, symbols etc. A password which has all different type of characters is considered stronger.
* <strong>Length of the password</strong><br/>
Second most important thing about strong passwords is their length. Longer passwords are considered more secure.
* <strong>Guessability of the password</strong><br/>
Another thing which determine strength of password is of easy it is to guess a password. Easier to guess passwords are weak. A security researcher has said that <a href="http://www.troyhunt.com/2011/03/only-secure-password-is-one-you-cant.html">any password  you can remember is not safe enough</a>.</p>

<h2>The problem</h2>

<p> So we have a problem here. They say any password we choose which we can remember is not safe enough. Most people choose easy, simple to remember password, which is perfectly reasonable. Why putting extra load on brain? But this laziness can cost more than you think.</p>

<h2><a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">The Solution</a></h2>

<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/Ujh8L6y.png" alt="Fireword password generator" /><br/>
 So I wanted a system which will create passwords for me which I can remember, but which can&rsquo;t be guessed or cracked easily. One solution to this is passphrases. For example, instead of choosing a single word password like &ldquo;facebook123&rdquo;, I choose a sentence like &ldquo;facebookhasbluecolor&rdquo;. And even better, change some character with symbols and numbers, &ldquo;f@c3b00kh4sBlu3C0lOr&rdquo;. Awesome, right! But it still can be remembered. So according to our theory that any password which can be remembered is not safe enough. I want something simple to remember and type and still very strong and long.
 So being a software developer, I made a system which do exactly this. I call it fireword.</p>

<h2>What is fireword?</h2>

<p> <a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a> is an application in which you enter a simple word or phrase, and it give you a very strong and impossible to guess password.</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a> always generate same password for same word. So you remember your simple password, and generate a strong one with this site. And then when you need to login again, regenerate strong password with your simple one.</li>
<li><a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a> allow you to select the length of the password. You can choose from 8 to 128 character long password.</li>
<li>For example, just entering &lsquo;facebook&rsquo; become this &lsquo;bF2A37d5e8%{61?C]>3E[{(9{&rsquo;. Any password can be expanded to at most 128 character long complex password.

<h2>Recommended ways to use <a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a></h2>

<p>It&rsquo;s really simple. Instead of using you easy to remember but weak password for a website, change your password with the password generated by fireword.</p></li>
<li>Enter your simple password in <a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a>, get a strong one, and use it for logging in.</li>
<li>Do not copy-paste strong generated passwords on your hard-disk, it is very insecure. Instead, whenever you need to login again, just get back to the fireword, and generate password again. <a href="http://channikhabra.github.io/fireword/">Fireword</a> will always generate same strong password for same simple password you enter.

<h2>How to choose passwords?</h2></li>
<li>Instead of choosing ridiculously stupid passwords like &lsquo;password&rsquo;, you should choose little smarter passwords. Even if you are hardening your passwords with fireword, try choosing a better password.</li>
<li>Choose different passwords for different sites following some pattern, like</li>
<li>Use the name of the website for which you are generating password and use some words in front and end of it. Like
<strong> For facebook choose bluefacebookaccount
</strong> For google choose greengoogleaccount
<strong> Come up with your own patterns. You can even use your phone number, your name and the site name in the combo.
</strong> Convert the pattern with fireword, and get strongest password possible.
Amazing. Isn&rsquo;t it!<br/>
<strong>NOTE: Firefox and Chrome extensions are on their way. With them you&rsquo;ll not even need to visit firewordgen.herokuapp.com.</strong></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Fledge Guide on TLD's - What Is Top Level Domain(s)]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/full-fledge-guide-on-tlds-what-is-top-level-domain-s/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-31T02:31:05+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/full-fledge-guide-on-tlds-what-is-top-level-domain-s</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Top level domain which is also abbrebiated as TLD is the very last segment of any domain name, every domain&rsquo;s last part is simply called as TLD. The TLD is the letters immediately following the final dot in an Internet address i.e. any website url, for Instance in Harkuchh.com here .com is TLD of generic class (we will talk about TLD classes below). Most generally TLD is use to identifies something about a website is associated with, like its purpose, the organization that owns it or the geographical area from where it has originates, and every type of TLD has a different registry which is being maintained by a designated organization the Internet Assigned Numbers Authority (IANA) under the direction of ICANN i.e. The Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>
To better understand TLD see our Internet address which is, <a href="http://Harkuchh.com">http://Harkuchh.com</a> now here com is the top-level domain name and Harkuchh is the second-level domain name and if a domain has anything even before second level domain then it is called as a subdomain. When these all merge together they build a fully qualified domain name (FQDN) the addition of <a href="HTTP://">HTTP://</a> makes an FQDN a complete URL.</p>

<h2><strong>Four (4) major categories of TLDs</strong></h2>

<p><strong>Generic top-level domains (gTLD)</strong> &mdash; These are the most used, common and familiar type of TLDs. Examples include &ldquo;com&rdquo; for &ldquo;commercial&rdquo;, &ldquo;org&rdquo; for &ldquo;organization&rdquo; and &ldquo;edu&rdquo; for &ldquo;educational.&rdquo; Most generic TLDs are open for everyone to register, but there is a subgroup that is more strictly controlled and that is not used broadly.</p>

<p><strong>Country-code top-level domains (ccTLD)</strong> &mdash; Each ccTLD identifies a particular country and every ccTLD is two letters long, for example we can see the ccTLD for India is .in and for United States is .us.</p>

<p><strong>Infrastructure top-level domain</strong> &mdash; This type is very often used class of TLD may be that is the reason there is only one TLD in this group, ARPA (Address and Routing Parameter Area). The Internet Assigned Numbers Authority (IANA) manages this TLD for the IETF.</p>

<p><strong>Sponsored top-level domains (sTLD)</strong>: These are overseen by private organizations.</p>

<p>ICANN Proposed an expansion of the TLD system to allow anyone to register and also reserve any spare unused letter sequence as a TLD for Their exclusive use, in April 2009. For example if a company who use to sell sotwares want to to use .Soft as a TLD then they can use it. According to <strong>ICANN chief executive Paul Levins</strong>, Such an extension would lead to thousands of new TLDs in the coming years.</p>

<p>Have any query? just leave a comment, you can also use <a href="http://harkuchh.com/forums" target="_blank"> Harkuchh Forums </a> for any help.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trick to Copy Content From a Website With Copy Protector Enabled]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/trick-to-copy-content-from-a-website-with-copy-protector-enabled/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-29T22:16:18+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/trick-to-copy-content-from-a-website-with-copy-protector-enabled</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Copy protector is a wordpress plugin which is used by many wordpress sites to stop readers from copying the site content. When you visit a site and find it good to share some part of it, this type of plugins irritate us the most. In these cases, you either share the whole page, or you don&rsquo;t share anything.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>There are many such plugins which prevent users from copying partial content from a website.
Here we have a solution to this problem.</p>

<p>The solution we are mentioning here work against all plugins which prevent copying content. This means you don&rsquo;t need to know which plugin is used by the website that is stopping you from copying, following solution simply work against anything.</p>

<h3>How do these plugins work?</h3>

<p>Although this is not necessary to stop those copy protector plugins, but having proper knowledge is a good thing.</p>

<p>What we see on a web page is HTML content which is styled with CSS stylesheets. HTML and CSS do not offer much programming power to do anything like stopping people from copying content.<br/>
But there is a third power on the webpage which is actually used for programming fancy things on a web page. Its called javascript.</p>

<p><strong>Javascript</strong> is a web scripting language that run in our browser, which can do many many awesome things. Preventing us from copying is one of them. So if we can somehow disable the execution of javascript in our browser, all those plugins which stop us from copying content will simply stop working.</p>

<h3>But how do we do it?</h3>

<p>In previous versions of most browsers, one setting was provided to switch off javascript. But not anymore. New browser no more provide this option since more and more websites are becoming javascript heavy and they simply do not work if javascript is disabled.<br/>
So we need a third party tool which can disable javascript in the browser.</p>

<h3>Browser plugins to the rescue</h3>

<p>Most browsers have addons or plugins which we can install in the browser. Various plugins are available to disable javascript in browsers. We can search the browser addon market and find many.</p>

<h4>Our favorite plugin for this purpose</h4>

<p><strong><a href="http://noscript.net/">No Script</a></strong></p>

<p><img src="" alt="Category: technology" /></p>

<p>The NoScript Firefox extension provides extra protection for Firefox browsers. It is free and open source add-on which allows JavaScript, Java, Flash and other plugins to be executed only by trusted web sites of your choice. NoScript also provides the most powerful anti-XSS and anti-Clickjacking protection ever available in a browser. <br/>
With noscript we can choose which site can execute javascript and which can&rsquo;t.</p>

<p><strong>So what we actually have to do?</strong></p>

<p>Just install noscript in firefox and follow the tutorial.</p>

<h2>Tutorial to copy content from a website with Copy Protector enabled</h2>

<p>Okay this is a really small tutorial here.<br/>
When you have noscript installed in firefox, there will appear an icon like this in your firefox window.</p>

<p>By default noscript do not allow any site to execute any javascript, java or flash code. So most sites will just stop working the way they usually do.</p>

<p>So first thing we have to do is disable the noscript gloablly.</p>

<ul>
<li>Click on the noscript icon and unselect &ldquo;Forbid Scripts globally&rdquo;.</li>
</ul>


<p>It will show a warning messag saying</p>

<p>&ldquo;Scripts are going to be allowed globally (for every site).
  This is a potentially dangerous action.
  Do you really want to proceed?&rdquo;</p>

<p>Just ignore it and press ok.</p>

<ul>
<li>Now open the site from which you want to copy content.</li>
<li>With that site&rsquo;s page open, again click on the no-script icon and select  &ldquo;Mark &lt;site-name> as Untrusted&rdquo;</li>
</ul>


<p>Doing this will auto-refresh the page and no-scripts will be run from that page. This means none of the copy blocking plugins will work.</p>

<p>So, that&rsquo;s what we wanted to achieve. If you have any questions and queries, please feel free to ask in comments. We also have forums where you can ask any question and me and our team will try to answer as per our knowledge.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
