<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: blogging | harkuchh]]></title>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/blog/categories/blogging/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-04T00:01:51+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://harkuchh.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[harkuchh]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Fledge Guide on TLD's - What is Top Level Domain(s)]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/full-fledge-guide-on-tlds-what-is-top-level-domain-s/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-31T02:31:05+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/full-fledge-guide-on-tlds-what-is-top-level-domain-s</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Top level domain which is also abbrebiated as TLD is the very last segment of any domain name, every domain&rsquo;s last part is simply called as TLD. The TLD is the letters immediately following the final dot in an Internet address i.e. any website url, for Instance in Harkuchh.com here .com is TLD of generic class (we will talk about TLD classes below). Most generally TLD is use to identifies something about a website is associated with, like its purpose, the organization that owns it or the geographical area from where it has originates, and every type of TLD has a different registry which is being maintained by a designated organization the Internet Assigned Numbers Authority (IANA) under the direction of ICANN i.e. The Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>
To better understand TLD see our Internet address which is, <a href="http://Harkuchh.com">http://Harkuchh.com</a> now here com is the top-level domain name and Harkuchh is the second-level domain name and if a domain has anything even before second level domain then it is called as a subdomain. When these all merge together they build a fully qualified domain name (FQDN) the addition of <a href="HTTP://">HTTP://</a> makes an FQDN a complete URL.</p>

<h2><strong>Four (4) major categories of TLDs</strong></h2>

<p><strong>Generic top-level domains (gTLD)</strong> &mdash; These are the most used, common and familiar type of TLDs. Examples include &ldquo;com&rdquo; for &ldquo;commercial&rdquo;, &ldquo;org&rdquo; for &ldquo;organization&rdquo; and &ldquo;edu&rdquo; for &ldquo;educational.&rdquo; Most generic TLDs are open for everyone to register, but there is a subgroup that is more strictly controlled and that is not used broadly.</p>

<p><strong>Country-code top-level domains (ccTLD)</strong> &mdash; Each ccTLD identifies a particular country and every ccTLD is two letters long, for example we can see the ccTLD for India is .in and for United States is .us.</p>

<p><strong>Infrastructure top-level domain</strong> &mdash; This type is very often used class of TLD may be that is the reason there is only one TLD in this group, ARPA (Address and Routing Parameter Area). The Internet Assigned Numbers Authority (IANA) manages this TLD for the IETF.</p>

<p><strong>Sponsored top-level domains (sTLD)</strong>: These are overseen by private organizations.</p>

<p>ICANN Proposed an expansion of the TLD system to allow anyone to register and also reserve any spare unused letter sequence as a TLD for Their exclusive use, in April 2009. For example if a company who use to sell sotwares want to to use .Soft as a TLD then they can use it. According to <strong>ICANN chief executive Paul Levins</strong>, Such an extension would lead to thousands of new TLDs in the coming years.</p>

<p>Have any query? just leave a comment, you can also use <a href="http://harkuchh.com/forums" target="_blank"> Harkuchh Forums </a> for any help.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Google like a pro: Tips to use Google syntax ]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-use-google-like-a-pro-tips-to-use-google-syntax/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-30T21:00:32+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-use-google-like-a-pro-tips-to-use-google-syntax</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I know you all use Google to reach everywhere on the Internet, but are you using it properly? Google actually provides a specific syntax for searching which is unknown to the masses. Also known as the Google operators, this syntax can make your Googling much easy and much less frustrating.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s specially useful for bloggers since all of us need to keep an eye on the Internet trends. It&rsquo;s very useful to know how to properly use our most used tool, that is Google.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>So let&rsquo;s waste less time an look at what Google has to offer for us.</p>

<h1>How to use Google syntax?</h1>

<p>All the search operators described here can be used by putting the operator in the search box followed by the search query. Like to use <strong>related:</strong> operator, following query will be used</p>

<pre><code>related:"harkuchh.com"
</code></pre>

<h2><em>related:</em> Search for related sites</h2>

<pre><code>related:"example.com"
</code></pre>

<p><em>related:</em> is used to search for websites which are similar to the website we provide in search box. When we use this operator, Google will search for any information related to the given website from all over the Internet. Google will show websites which have similar content.</p>

<h2><em>link:</em> Search for all pages that link to a particular url</h2>

<pre><code>link:"http://harkuchh.com/trick-to-copy-content-from-a-website-with-copy-protector-enabled/"
</code></pre>

<p>This operator will search for all the pages that link to the given url.</p>

<h2><em>site:</em> Search within a particular website only</h2>

<pre><code>"site:"harkuchh.com" blogging tips
</code></pre>

<p>Above query will only search &lsquo;harkuchh.com&rsquo; for the words &lsquo;blogging tips&rsquo;. This is a very useful operator. Just imagine when you need to find a particular post you once seen on a website but can&rsquo;t find a link to it. It&rsquo;s one of my most used operators.</p>

<h2>Search for an exact phrase or word</h2>

<p>When we search for a sentence on Google, it doesn&rsquo;t just search for that exact sentence.
Try searching for</p>

<pre><code>I will become dictator of the world
</code></pre>

<p>Google will search for text which have &lsquo;I&rsquo;, &lsquo;will&rsquo;, &lsquo;become&rsquo; etc anywhere on the page. But if we want to only search for pages which contain the complete sentence &ldquo;I will become dictator of the world&rdquo;, we can do it just by putting the whole sentence within quotes. Like this</p>

<pre><code>"I will become dictator of the world"
</code></pre>

<h2>Exclude something in the results</h2>

<p>Sometimes we want that some specific type of results should not appear in the search results. Google provide a special operator just for this purpose.<br/>
That is &lsquo;&ndash;&rsquo;.<br/>
Yes just that. Putting a &lsquo;&ndash;&rsquo; in front of any word will show results which do not have that word in them.
To make it even better, this work with other Google operators as well.</p>

<pre><code>hello lady how are you -season
</code></pre>

<p>Above query if searched without &lsquo;-season&rsquo; will show some youtube results about some seasons of some TV program. But running above query will remove those results which have the word &lsquo;season&rsquo; in them.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
