<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Blogging | harkuchh]]></title>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/blog/categories/blogging/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-18T05:13:51+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://harkuchh.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[harkuchh]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Bloggers Need to Save Themselves From Google: Lesson We Got After Losing 400K]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/why-bloggers-need-to-save-themselves-from-google-lesson-we-got-after-losing-400k/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-12T23:56:09+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/why-bloggers-need-to-save-themselves-from-google-lesson-we-got-after-losing-400k</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Google is no more that same open company which had ‘<a href="http://www.zdnet.com/blog/foremski/google-drops-dont-be-evil-motto/435">don’t be evil</a>’ as their slogan.<br/>
Google is evil. We all know it.</p>

<p>But Google can be particularly evil to you if you are a blogger. Being a blogger, most of your living depends on Google one way or other. Google is a major traffic source, all information you need come through Google, and Google Adsense is major source of most blogger’s income. Imagine Google having a grudge against you. I mean against you, as a person in particular. Everything you do is seen with a skeptical eye, and suddenly your websites which were rolling few days back are now ruins facing drought of visitors.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>
Yes, Google can do it, and it does.</p>

<h2>Our Experience</h2>

<p>We at Harkuchh &ndash; The Blogging Valley were unfortunate enough to face the fury of Google. We have multiple blogs here, some good and some not so good. And we are always doing all sort of experiments to try new things. Few months back, we were working as always and things were going as breeze. Then Krishan started a test project, a kind of illegitimate blog. It was an experiment. We spent very little time on it, and it was just lying around in some corner, with Krishan occasionally working on it.</p>

<p>Few weeks after starting that experiment, we started facing problems in getting traffic to our websites. For some reason, all of our websites were facing more than 50% fall in traffic. Even the best quality posts which have backlinks on high PR sites stopped appearing on Google search results. It was incomprehensible. What could we have done wrong to bring this on us? And few days later another nightmare came true. Our Google adsense account got disabled, with no clarification of course. With it went our Rs 400+K sum. All that was left was shattered plans, unbalanced budget and minds full of confusion.</p>

<h2>The Mistake</h2>

<p>You guessed it right. That experiment was the mistake. But it was not at all clear at that time. There was not a single link that could tell any connection between our legitimate blogs and that experiment blog. We do extra effort to not to link our blogs with each other in any way. Then how could Google tell that experiment blog belonged to us? How could it be that all our genuine blogs were suffering Google’s rage?</p>

<p>The real mistake was not that we somehow made some connection between the experiment and some of our real blogs. Because there was no connection. We cross-checked many times.</p>

<p>There was actually no mistake. Things should not have been the way they were.</p>

<h2>The Lesson</h2>

<p>As we noticed later, the only thing that could have resulted in connection was a Google account. What Krishan did was that he used same Google account for analytics and webmaster tools which was also used on our other blogs. But he didn’t use the adsense on the experiment. <br/>
I know Google tracking everyone on Internet is not a new story, but this was new for us. This had never happened before. Google is now making connections between different sites you own. Any one site you run can affect your other sites as well.</p>

<p>So our suggestion is, if you are going to try something crazy never ever use same Google accounts in any way on different sites. It would be even better if you
operate on your experiments in sandboxed environments. That’s what we are doing now. And it’s working, for now at least.</p>

<p>So better save your ass from Google. It’s no longer our all good friend.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five Reasons Why Every Blogger Should Learn Programming]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/five-reasons-for-why-you-should-learn-programming/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-07T23:47:12+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/five-reasons-for-why-you-should-learn-programming</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In this post I am writing about why every blogger (and every person in general) should learn to code. Programming as itself is an asset that will make you a better and smarter person. Most important benefit you&rsquo;ll get is the ability to make <strong>literate decisions</strong>. You&rsquo;ll learn how to break down that large problem you are facing, and how to solve it&rsquo;s one piece at a time. Besides, it gives ou great level of confidence.<br/>
Here are five reasons to convince you to learn programming.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>You want to be a God</h2>

<p>I heard yea! So you wanna be a God? Well, you can be actually. Programmers are mini Gods who create little worlds with their programs and control everything. Literally. It&rsquo;s hard to understand this feeling without really experiencing it. But the ultimate control building a software offers is addictive. I myself was a gaming addict in my school time, and now gaming addiction is turned into coding addiction.</p>

<p>The amount of automation you can put in your daily work truly make you feel like a God. It makes me feel real good when I see my script running and think my code can do in 30 minutes what my peers at harkuchh would have taken 4-5 days.</p>

<h2>One blogger who know coding equals ten average bloggers</h2>

<p>Don&rsquo;t get hyper. Let me explain why. Programming skills are valuable in every field directly or remotely related to computers and internet off course.I mean your programming skills become specially important in fields which are completely dependent on computers and Internet. Blogging is such a case. I joined Harkuchh &ndash; The Blogging Valley about a month ago, and the technological improvements we&rsquo;ve made here improved our productivity while brought down the expenses. Although many things are under experiment phase, the time we&rsquo;ve saved so far which would have been wasted in trying things which don&rsquo;t bring any profit is enormous.</p>

<p>To give an example, consider data gathering. We all need to collect data from various sources, many times it involve just copy pasting data from some other source. We&rsquo;ve built a software to automate such things, and saved days of work.</p>

<p>But there are more benefits than I can describe here. Enough benefits that Krishan Kummar (founder of harkuchh.com) is learning to code. (We are thinking about starting giving programming classes to bloggers. Please comment or mail us if you are interested).</p>

<h2>Dream, Believe, Achieve</h2>

<p>These quotes all seem too good to be practical in real world. This might be true, but not in the world where you can even be a God. You just wish if there was a software which would do <em>something awesome here</em>, and you roll out your emacs (or your favorite editor), and voila! It&rsquo;s there. Anything is possible, all you need to do is to believe in your wit and skills. Sounds too good to be real? Welcome to the world of programmers :)</p>

<h2>It teaches you to make better decisions in life</h2>

<p>I just can&rsquo;t emphasize how beneficial it is for anyone (including you bloggers) to have some programming skills. Even if you don&rsquo;t become a wiz, acquaintance with programming is a very much helpful. When you don&rsquo;t know anything about how your websites and software are actually working under-the-hood, you are like riding a bike eye-folded. You either hit a tree or something, or you go too slow.</p>

<p>Most important benefit you&rsquo;ll get is the ability to make <strong>literate decisions</strong>. You&rsquo;ll learn how to break down that large problem you are facing, and how to solve it&rsquo;s one piece at a time. Besides, it give you great level of confidence. When you think of a crazy idea, and you have good programming skills under your belt, you quickly analyze all the steps which you&rsquo;ll need to take to make that awesome thing. You carry this habit to your real life. And suddenly all things become simple, because you&rsquo;ll quickly analyze everything and sort out plans for doing things which seem impossible or very hard to others. It&rsquo;ll give you a new perspective in your career, as well as in your life.</p>

<h2>Programming is fun, and it makes you smarter</h2>

<p>I ditched gaming for coding, not because it give me money, but simply because it&rsquo;s more fun. I still play games once in a while when I want my brain to relax, but I&rsquo;m yet to find a game which&rsquo;ll give me more thrill than coding. If you follow the right steps (like choose right first language, right teacher, right things to do in your first steps in coding world), programming is like playing a very powerful computer game. Projects you do are your highscore and skills you gain are your reward, that&rsquo;ll stay with you for rest of your life. Besides, remember all your kids (the next generation) will be taught coding in schools like we are taught poems, then your children will ask you questions related to coding, what you gonna do then? ;)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Fledge Guide on TLD's - What Is Top Level Domain(s)]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/full-fledge-guide-on-tlds-what-is-top-level-domain-s/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-31T02:31:05+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/full-fledge-guide-on-tlds-what-is-top-level-domain-s</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Top level domain which is also abbrebiated as TLD is the very last segment of any domain name, every domain&rsquo;s last part is simply called as TLD. The TLD is the letters immediately following the final dot in an Internet address i.e. any website url, for Instance in Harkuchh.com here .com is TLD of generic class (we will talk about TLD classes below). Most generally TLD is use to identifies something about a website is associated with, like its purpose, the organization that owns it or the geographical area from where it has originates, and every type of TLD has a different registry which is being maintained by a designated organization the Internet Assigned Numbers Authority (IANA) under the direction of ICANN i.e. The Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>
To better understand TLD see our Internet address which is, <a href="http://Harkuchh.com">http://Harkuchh.com</a> now here com is the top-level domain name and Harkuchh is the second-level domain name and if a domain has anything even before second level domain then it is called as a subdomain. When these all merge together they build a fully qualified domain name (FQDN) the addition of <a href="HTTP://">HTTP://</a> makes an FQDN a complete URL.</p>

<h2><strong>Four (4) major categories of TLDs</strong></h2>

<p><strong>Generic top-level domains (gTLD)</strong> &mdash; These are the most used, common and familiar type of TLDs. Examples include &ldquo;com&rdquo; for &ldquo;commercial&rdquo;, &ldquo;org&rdquo; for &ldquo;organization&rdquo; and &ldquo;edu&rdquo; for &ldquo;educational.&rdquo; Most generic TLDs are open for everyone to register, but there is a subgroup that is more strictly controlled and that is not used broadly.</p>

<p><strong>Country-code top-level domains (ccTLD)</strong> &mdash; Each ccTLD identifies a particular country and every ccTLD is two letters long, for example we can see the ccTLD for India is .in and for United States is .us.</p>

<p><strong>Infrastructure top-level domain</strong> &mdash; This type is very often used class of TLD may be that is the reason there is only one TLD in this group, ARPA (Address and Routing Parameter Area). The Internet Assigned Numbers Authority (IANA) manages this TLD for the IETF.</p>

<p><strong>Sponsored top-level domains (sTLD)</strong>: These are overseen by private organizations.</p>

<p>ICANN Proposed an expansion of the TLD system to allow anyone to register and also reserve any spare unused letter sequence as a TLD for Their exclusive use, in April 2009. For example if a company who use to sell sotwares want to to use .Soft as a TLD then they can use it. According to <strong>ICANN chief executive Paul Levins</strong>, Such an extension would lead to thousands of new TLDs in the coming years.</p>

<p>Have any query? just leave a comment, you can also use <a href="http://harkuchh.com/forums" target="_blank"> Harkuchh Forums </a> for any help.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Google Like a Pro: Tips to Use Google Syntax]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-use-google-like-a-pro-tips-to-use-google-syntax/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-30T21:00:32+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-use-google-like-a-pro-tips-to-use-google-syntax</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I know you all use Google to reach everywhere on the Internet, but are you using it properly? Google actually provides a specific syntax for searching which is unknown to the masses. Also known as the Google operators, this syntax can make your Googling much easy and much less frustrating.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s specially useful for bloggers since all of us need to keep an eye on the Internet trends. It&rsquo;s very useful to know how to properly use our most used tool, that is Google.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>So let&rsquo;s waste less time an look at what Google has to offer for us.</p>

<h1>How to use Google syntax?</h1>

<p>All the search operators described here can be used by putting the operator in the search box followed by the search query. Like to use <strong>related:</strong> operator, following query will be used</p>

<pre><code>related:"harkuchh.com"
</code></pre>

<h2><em>related:</em> Search for related sites</h2>

<pre><code>related:"example.com"
</code></pre>

<p><em>related:</em> is used to search for websites which are similar to the website we provide in search box. When we use this operator, Google will search for any information related to the given website from all over the Internet. Google will show websites which have similar content.</p>

<h2><em>link:</em> Search for all pages that link to a particular url</h2>

<pre><code>link:"http://harkuchh.com/trick-to-copy-content-from-a-website-with-copy-protector-enabled/"
</code></pre>

<p>This operator will search for all the pages that link to the given url.</p>

<h2><em>site:</em> Search within a particular website only</h2>

<pre><code>"site:"harkuchh.com" blogging tips
</code></pre>

<p>Above query will only search &lsquo;harkuchh.com&rsquo; for the words &lsquo;blogging tips&rsquo;. This is a very useful operator. Just imagine when you need to find a particular post you once seen on a website but can&rsquo;t find a link to it. It&rsquo;s one of my most used operators.</p>

<h2>Search for an exact phrase or word</h2>

<p>When we search for a sentence on Google, it doesn&rsquo;t just search for that exact sentence.
Try searching for</p>

<pre><code>I will become dictator of the world
</code></pre>

<p>Google will search for text which have &lsquo;I&rsquo;, &lsquo;will&rsquo;, &lsquo;become&rsquo; etc anywhere on the page. But if we want to only search for pages which contain the complete sentence &ldquo;I will become dictator of the world&rdquo;, we can do it just by putting the whole sentence within quotes. Like this</p>

<pre><code>"I will become dictator of the world"
</code></pre>

<h2>Exclude something in the results</h2>

<p>Sometimes we want that some specific type of results should not appear in the search results. Google provide a special operator just for this purpose.<br/>
That is &lsquo;&ndash;&rsquo;.<br/>
Yes just that. Putting a &lsquo;&ndash;&rsquo; in front of any word will show results which do not have that word in them.
To make it even better, this work with other Google operators as well.</p>

<pre><code>hello lady how are you -season
</code></pre>

<p>Above query if searched without &lsquo;-season&rsquo; will show some youtube results about some seasons of some TV program. But running above query will remove those results which have the word &lsquo;season&rsquo; in them.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
