<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: BLOGGING | harkuchh]]></title>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/blog/categories/blogging/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-01-30T01:24:26+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://harkuchh.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[harkuchh]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Comments not Getting Approved]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/why-your-comments-not-getting-approved/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-29T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/why-your-comments-not-getting-approved</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Comments are the basic, easiest and most popular way to <strong>create backlink from a good reputed blog</strong> to your blog, maybe you already know this, may be you don’t. If you know it, that’s good but if you don’t then you must need to know it, because in this awesome business called <code>&lt;a title="What is Blogging, Why Blogging becoming Popular in Youth ?" href="http://harkuchh.com/what-is-blogging-why-blogging-becoming-popular-in-youth/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blogging&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</code> links and <a title="read : What is Backlink and How to Build Back Links" href="harkuchh.com/what-are-the-back-links-and-how-to-build-back-links/" target="_blank"><strong>backlinks</strong></a> have a great importance.<!--more--></p>

<p>Many people are facing a problem in commenting, this might be possible that you also having that problem, problem of not getting your comments approved. Don’t worry today your this problem will be solved, all you need to do is, just read this post very carefully.</p>

<h2><strong>Reasons for Comments not Accepting</strong></h2>


<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><strong>Formality</strong></h3>


<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><strong>`Oh Wow.... What a nice post, great work.`</strong></p>


<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><strong>`This is a good post, thanks for sharing.`</strong></p>


<p style="padding-left: 30px;"><strong>`Full of information, nice thank you.`</strong></p>


<p>These kind of comments are totally formality, if you post comments like that on others blog and hope that those will be approved, you are simply a newbie. Bloggers want real appreciation or suggestions to their work, they don’t need these kind of formality, see if they have written a post, they already know that it’s a great post, you don’t need to tell them it’s great.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><strong>No Gravtar Image</strong></h3>


<p>If you commented on a blog and your comment not got approved by webmaster, this point is may be responsible for it, if you have not setted up a Gravtar image for your profile, Bloggers always want their blog to look good and believe me a comment without Gravtar image looks ugly in comment section and most of the people hate it and they don’t accept comments, no matter how good they are. See : <a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-show-photo-with-comment-on-website/" target="_blank"><em>How to Show your photo with your comment</em></a>.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><strong>Fake Accounts</strong></h3>


<p>Never ever use any fake account for commenting purpose, see if a blogger is capable to make you comment on his blog, it simply means he/she is a person with decent knowledge and they can easily find out if your details are fake and in that case there is no chance of approving of your comment, Be original comment with your name, your profile.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><strong>Comment not related to the Article</strong></h3>


<p>If you are reading a post pertaining to blogging or SEO and if at the end of the post you are commenting about Justin Bieber, you are simply showing you have lack of knowledge and you are just trying to show your presence there, which doesn’t have any meaning, so don’t do that ever.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><strong>Comment for Link</strong></h3>


<p>Everybody know if someone is commenting on a blog most probably he is doing that for one basic purpose, that is backlink but if you are showing this clearly through your comment that you only want a backlink from that blog, you don’t care about their content of post they will not approve your comment in any case. You need to understand their write ups and then generate question from it, then if you will ask a question from the blogger regarding the post, they will surely approve your comment and will reply back.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><strong>Link in Comment</strong></h3>


<p>I’m really unable to understand how people are doing this foolishness even in these days. They open a post on a popular blog and writes.</p>

<p><em>`This is really a good information check this out <a href="http:........................................%E2%80%99">http:........................................%E2%80%99</a></em></p>

<p>if you have done this it’s ok, everyone was a stupid once, but if you are going to do this again ever, you are going to waste your time, nobody like this type of comment strategy and only inexperienced bloggers approves these type of comments.</p>

<p>You can add link to your comment but only and only when it is must needed, generally never do this, this shows you are new, immature and unknown to blogging.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><strong>Wrong Language and Words</strong></h3>


<p>Don’t use cheap language or any bad stuff related to any religion, racism, or any country. vulgarity is strictly prohibited in the business of blogging, if you are not happy with something that’s your problem don’t show your Pent up feelings to anyone, nobody cares, nobody likes it and this is true. Your comment will be trashed immediately.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><strong>Fallacious English</strong></h3>


<p>This is also a big reason for not getting a comment approved, as big bloggers want their post and blog to look good they also like to see good things in comments below their post. Wrong language and broken English is like a blot to their awesome work and everybody hates it, like you do, so always try to be simple, original and straight forward.</p>

<p>Must read : <a href="http://harkuchh.com/tag/adsense/" target="_blank"><em>Best and All Adsense Tips and Tutorials.</em></a></p>

<p>If you have read this post in the same way I said above, <code>carefully</code> then I promise your every comment will be approved at every blog, you just take care of these points and comment originally, related to the topic, in proper language strictly avoid formality and vulgarity. Before commenting must read the post and nothing will be more awesome than this, if your comment will have a doubt or query related to the topic written in post.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize your Database from cPanel]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-optimize-your-database-from-cpanel/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-optimize-your-database-from-cpanel</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>To help your website or blog in performance, keeping your database(s) optimized is always a great step. No matter you are using InMotion Hosting, GoDaddy Hosting, Hostgator hosting or any other hosting cPanel account or hosting Account, this can be easily done using <strong>phpMyAdmin</strong>. Make it sure before optimizing your database all your data backup.<!--more--></p>

<p>You can &ldquo;<strong>Optimize Table</strong>&rdquo; to reclaim unused space and defregment the data file for optimal performance.  If a lot of changes have been made to a table, optimizing the table can sometimes significantly improve performance.</p>

<h2><b>Steps to Optimize Database tables from cPanel..</b></h2>


<ul>
    <li><b>Log in</b> to your website <b>cPanel.</b></li>
</ul>


<p>[caption id=&ldquo;attachment_9432&rdquo; align=&ldquo;aligncenter&rdquo; width=&ldquo;394&rdquo;]<a href="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Optomise-website-database-from-cpanel.jpg"><img class="size-full wp-image-9432" alt="Optomise website  database from cpanel" src="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Optomise-website-database-from-cpanel.jpg" width="394" height="365" /></a> <strong>Log in to cPanel</strong>[/caption]</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<ul>
    <li>Click on <b>phpMyAdmin </b>under Databases section.</li>
</ul>


<p>[caption id=&ldquo;attachment_9433&rdquo; align=&ldquo;aligncenter&rdquo; width=&ldquo;580&rdquo;]<a href="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Click-on-phpMyAdmin-under-Databases-section.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-9433" alt="Click on phpMyAdmin under Databases section" src="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Click-on-phpMyAdmin-under-Databases-section-580x124.jpg" width="580" height="124" /></a> <strong>Click on phpMyAdmin under Databases section</strong>[/caption]</p>

<ul>
    <li>Now look at left, you will see your `<b>Database</b>` name on which you’re working on there, just click on it.</li>
</ul>


<p>[caption id=&ldquo;attachment_9434&rdquo; align=&ldquo;aligncenter&rdquo; width=&ldquo;580&rdquo;]<a href="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/How-to-Optimize-your-Database-from-cPanel.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-9434" alt="How to Optimize your Database from cPanel" src="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/How-to-Optimize-your-Database-from-cPanel-580x279.jpg" width="580" height="279" /></a> <strong>click on Database` name on which you’re working</strong>[/caption]</p>

<ul>
    <li>Now go down and click on `<b>Check All</b>` it will select all your database tables.</li>
</ul>


<p>[caption id=&ldquo;attachment_9435&rdquo; align=&ldquo;aligncenter&rdquo; width=&ldquo;580&rdquo;]<a href="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Optimize-your-Database-Table-using-your-phpMyAmin.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-9435" alt="Steps to Optimize Database tables from cPanel" src="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Optimize-your-Database-Table-using-your-phpMyAmin-580x353.jpg" width="580" height="353" /></a> <strong>click on check all to select all tables</strong>[/caption]</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<ul>
    <li>Click on drop down Menu next to `<b>Check All/Uncheck All</b>` and select `<b>Optimize table</b>`.</li>
</ul>


<p>[caption id=&ldquo;attachment_9436&rdquo; align=&ldquo;aligncenter&rdquo; width=&ldquo;511&rdquo;]<a href="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Optimize-your-Database-Table-ufrom-your-MyphpAmin.jpg"><img class=" wp-image-9436 " title="Optimize your Database Table ufrom your MyphpAmin" alt="Optimize your Database Table ufrom your MyphpAmin" src="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/Optimize-your-Database-Table-ufrom-your-MyphpAmin.jpg" width="511" height="333" /></a> click on Optimize Table[/caption]</p>

<p style="text-align: center;"></p>


<p>This is it, you have done, database of your website has been optimized, if you have any sub-domains or any Add on domains in your account then just do same things (step 3 to 5) to optimize their databases.</p>

<p><strong>Database optimization</strong> is recommended to do on a regular basis as a preventive measure, it doesn’t take much effort but it do affect a site’s or blog’s performance a lot.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get PR for my Blog ?]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-get-pr-for-my-blog/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-15T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/how-to-get-pr-for-my-blog</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I’m sure you have heard of PR or Page Rank or Google Page Rank, these all are the same thing. As I said I’m sure you may have heard of Google Page rank, but.. there are only very few people who knows what exactly <b>Google Page rank stands for</b>. If you get <b>high pr <a title="what are backlinks and how to get it ?" href="http://harkuchh.com/what-are-the-back-links-and-how-to-build-back-links/" target="_blank">backlinks</a></b> for your blog it take your blog to the great height. You don’t need to go for any <b>buy back links</b> from any paid <b>link building service </b>you can get <b>PR in free</b> just by following tips given here.<!--more--></p>

<p><a href="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/PR-logo.jpg"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-9291" alt="PR logo" src="http://Harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/PR-logo-580x364.jpg" width="580" height="364" /></a></p>

<p>Having a blog or website in present Internet world is not enough, there are thousands of people over internet doing same thing you’re doing, so you must need to make your blog content visible enough to get maximum hits. <a href="http://harkuchh.com/google-e-book-service-for-indian-android-users/" target="_blank">Google</a> PageRank is one of the most important factors that Google uses to determine the importance of any blog and it is strongly based on the value of your Blog’s inbound links.</p>

<p>Google generally evaluates how many links there are to your blog from other pages, and the relevance and quality of the linking sites.</p>

<h2><b>How to Get Google Pagerank </b></h2>


<p><b>Getting pagerank</b> or <b>improve page rank</b> is not everyone’s cup of tea. One need to utilize all techniques available in order to make their web presence attractive, unique and appealing so that it help them in <code>&lt;b&gt;improve search engine ranking&lt;/b&gt;</code>. This is just a meta description, read further if you are now thinking <code>&lt;b&gt;how to increase page rank of my website&lt;/b&gt;</code> reading and taking them in practice will surely help you to <b>boost your webpage ranking</b> further.</p>

<p>Also read : <em><a href="http://harkuchh.com/how-to-increase-website-blog-traffic-and-ranking/" target="_blank">How to Increase Traffic, Ranking and Presence</a>.</em></p>

<h3><b>High Quality Content</b></h3>


<p>Well, in <a href="http://harkuchh.com/category/blogging/" target="_blank">blogging</a> field it is most important to know that <code>&lt;b&gt;Content is King&lt;/b&gt;</code> if you want Page Rank for your blog or you want <b>increase Page Rank</b>, then you must have high quality original content on your blog. If your blog will have original and valuable content then readers will love to spend their time reading your articles and sharing goes higher this way.</p>

<p><b> </b></p>

<h3><b>Guest posting</b></h3>


<p>Guest posting is the most popular, trusted and <b>effective way to get PR for a blog </b>see when you writes a guest post for a blog having remarkable Page Rank, then you gets a high-quality, relevant inbound link to your website and Google gives it preference more than anything else to consider a blog for giving Pagerank.You must ensure that the blog where you’re going to publish your article is a reputed blog and it’s having good Page Rank.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><b>Directory Submission</b></h3>


<p>Directory submission is a bit time consuming process, but it is also true that in order to boost Page Rank you must have high quality Backlinks associated with your blog name and believe me submit your site on different web directories and article directories  is the best way to generate quality backlinks for any blog. Some popular Directories to submit your blog link are Yahoo Directory, DMOZ, Best Of The Web, Ezine Articles, Article Base.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><b>Comment on Blogs</b></h3>


<p>I think this is the easiest and most crucial step in getting and improving Google Page Rank. Blogging requires a Blogger very active socially. When you land on any blog for any kind of information make it your habit to leave a genuine comment there, because some Blogs are Do-Follow and they can help you to easily generate back links for your blog.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><b>Social Bookmarking</b></h3>


<p>I don’t think I need to explain importance of Social Bookmarking, as it is a most common effective way to get free traffic as well as increase Page Rank, look when we share our Site on different Social networks we gets decent traffic and also free Backlink. Most popular Social Bookmarking Sites are Facebook, g+, Twitter, Stumble Upon , digg.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><strong>Website Accessibility</strong></h3>


<p>This is the fact which most of the people don’t care about, but this plays very significant role in reputation of your blog in front of Google. It can be easily understood that, if a Website remains  down for a long period of time, Google slowly reduce the ranking of that particular site. So You must ensure that your Website is always up.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><b>Regularly Updation</b></h3>


<p>Imagine you’re a teacher and there are many student in your class, some comes for lecture occasionally where as some comes daily, then whom will you prefer as your best students, you know your answer very well, same like that Google really like blogs that keep their content fresh and unique. The more you post, Google crawls your site more and it simply increases chances for you to improve page rank.</p>

<p>Fun Blogging : <a title="Google is male or female ?" href="http://harkuchh.com/google-is-a-girl-i-can-prove-it/" target="_blank"><em>Google is a Girl, I can Prove it</em></a>.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><b>Link Exchange</b></h3>


<p>This technique is one of that rare technique which is in use from the starting of blogging and surprisingly it still works, many tops bloggers doing this and in order to get a good Page Rank for your blog, you should link your blog to high page rank blogs, by following this you will surely get  Page Rank for your blog and also your blog will get traffic from that site.</p>

<p><b> </b></p>

<h3><b>No-follow Links</b></h3>


<p>There are millions of blogger over internet world these days, and they keep on posting on their blogs and websites for some specific purposes but I bet most of them don’t know about dofollow and nofollow links properly and because of lack of knowledge about this, they are spreading free dofollow links to other sites unnecessarily. Must read : <i>How to make a link nofollow or dofollow</i>.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><b>Keywords and Tags</b></h3>


<p>You may know that already, keywords and meta tags are one of the key factor for getting traffic to a site and it is one of the most crucial factors in the <b>search engine ranking</b> system. This step is quite taskful as searching of valuable keywords in never easy and once you get best keywords by following it&rsquo;s searching and competition volume, use them strategically. This will boost your Traffic, ranking, earnings and yes Page Rank.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><strong></strong><b>Inter Linking </b></h3>


<p>Inter linking your posts is a way to provide access to a related posts from one post and it’s a very useful tool to get better ranking, it increases your websites accessibility so when you think you can link your any previous post to your new one must integrate them because this is a basic as well as effective technique for <b>effective link building</b>.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><b>Engage Visitor</b></h3>


<p>Nothing is more effective than this point, if you successfully keep your the visitors engaged in reading your Articles via interesting and likeable stuff. You can make your visitor stick to your blog by interactive site design, interesting feedback section and Videos which make the visitor watch them.</p>

<p>Also read : <a title="Make much of promoting, free !" href="http://harkuchh.com/idiotic-but-superb-tricks-to-promote-your-blog/" target="_blank"><em>Idiotic but superb ways to promote your blog</em></a>.</p>

<p>Google have not updated PR after it’s last updation in Feb, 2013 so it is expected that, next <b>PR distribution</b> date is very close now, so without wasting time start try to link your blog with <b>high</b><b> pr sites</b> and if you can successfully get <b>high pr back links </b>then <b>chances of getting PR</b> increases much more.</p>

<p>You can also go for <b>Website Advertising</b>, <b>participation on forums</b> for making your blog presence everywhere you can, but don’t ever use any <b>illegal or wrong way to getting backlink</b> to your blog because in starting they may give you some links and traffic but eventually it sounds so bitter and you may fall in trouble, so Be Genuine, Be original, Work your Ass off and leave rest on <strong>G(od+oogle)</strong> Happy Blogging, I really hope Google will give you and Me Page Rank in this update.. ;)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips & Requirements for Get Approved Adsense Account]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #333333;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/rules_graphic1/" rel="attachment wp-att-2437"><span style="color: #333333;"><img class="alignleft  wp-image-2437" style="margin-left: 7px; margin-right: 7px;" title="Google Adsense Rules" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/Rules_Graphic1.jpg" width="180" height="200" /></span></a>Many people owning many blogs and websites and most of them doing that thing for getting income, Google Adsense is the most famous name for earning through the Internet. Google Adsense provide Ads to the Blogs and sites and when a visitor visit to the blog He/She see Ads over there If they like to know more about the thing shown in the Ad and open  it by clicking  on it, then Google provide some Income to the Adsence Account from where the Ads were placed on the Blog or website. </span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;"><!--more--> </span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;">The hardest part of getting started with Adsense is getting Google to approve your website. In fact  for many people even  it is easier to get a loan of $100,000 from bank than getting a approved Google Adsense account :) . The solution of such problem is to make your blog prepared before you apply for Adsense.</span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;">You can’t start using Google Adsense on your Blog until you are approved by Google. The very first thing you must do is read Carefully<strong> <a href="http://support.google.com/adsense/bin/answer.py?hl=en&amp;answer=48182" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Adsense Program Policies</span></a></strong> &amp; <strong><a href="http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Terms of Service (TOS)</span></a></strong> and also very important <a href="https://www.google.com/adsense/localized-terms" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Terms and Conditions</span></a>. If your site doesn’t fall within the guidelines that Google sets out, it will be denied.</span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;"> Some very important points are listed below which every webmaster or Blogger need to keep in their mind and follow them carefully before applying for Google Adsense Account..</span></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<h3><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Points need to focus for approved by Google Adsense :</strong></span></h3>




<hr />




<ul>
    <li><span style="color: #333333;">Your Blog should not be Under Construction it shoud be running.</span></li>
    <li><span style="color: #333333;"> Website Fulfill almost every points mentioned on Program Policies &amp; Terms of Service (TOS).</span></li>
    <li><span style="color: #333333;">Website or Blog Getting  decent Traffic.</span></li>
    <li><span style="color: #333333;">There is no too many pages on your Blog.</span></li>
    <li><span style="color: #333333;">There is no Copyrighted data on your blog from any other blog use original content, write for your blog by yourself.</span></li>
</ul>


<p><span style="color: #333333;"> Now you may understand Creating a website is not a big deal at all, the real challenge is to get traffic and that too from search engines so if your blog has very less traffic than wait few months and than apply for Adsense.</span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;">Your website should be according to the Terms and Conditions of Google make it sure there is  no adult content, warez, gambling sites, Hacking and hate spreading contents &amp; Copyrighted Data or post on your website.</span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;">Be Regular on updating Post try to upload a new post in 3-4 days on your blog  if it’s not possible for you than fix a time interval for uploading posts and follow them sincerely, regularly updating Blogs attracts Google and If they find useful contents on your blog your account will be approved without any problem.</span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;"> </span></p>

<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong> Quality and Original  Content
</strong></span></h3>




<hr />


<p><span style="color: #333333;">Quality Content is the Best than anything on a blog,  as a famous writer said “<em><strong>It’s Good to publish a single quality Article once in a week than Publishing Scrap Daily</strong></em>”. This is very simple to understand If Post or Content on your Blog is Original (not copyrighted) and written in the best manner then your Application will be accepted very easily by the Adsense Team.</span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/valuable-original-content/" rel="attachment wp-att-2460"><span style="color: #333333;"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2460" title="valuable original content" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/valuable-original-content.jpg" width="266" height="200" /></span></a></span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;">You can take ideas from any blog or website but you can’t Copy and paste them on your blog otherwise You will never Get  an Approved Adsense Account.</span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;"> </span></p>

<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong>Simple and Easy Design</strong></span></h3>




<hr />


<p><span style="color: #333333;"> Before submitting your site for Adsense make sure that the design you use in the site is a simple one with no much graphics works also it is nice if you have a easy navigation process in your site and try to avoid other ad networks while the reviewing process is going on, its not a compulsory one but a simple factor which may  help you to get the Adsense. </span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/simple-design-of-a-website-bmp/" rel="attachment wp-att-2462"><span style="color: #333333;"><img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-2462" title="simple design of a website.bmp" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/simple-design-of-a-website.bmp-300x182.jpg" width="300" height="182" /></span></a></span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;">Also remember to avoid any kinds of adult, hate spreading and Hacking contents since Adsense won&rsquo;t approve any sites that is having such contents.</span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;"> </span></p>

<h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;"><strong> </strong><strong>Apply Once, wait for Reply
</strong></span></h3>




<hr />


<p><span style="color: #333333;">Now If you think that your Blog is ready for submitting to Adsense after reading the points given above then you go to <a href="https://accounts.google.com/ServiceLogin?service=adsense&amp;rm=hide&amp;nui=15&amp;alwf=true&amp;ltmpl=adsense&amp;passive=true&amp;continue=https://www.google.com/adsense/gaiaauth2&amp;followup=https://www.google.com/adsense/gaiaauth2&amp;hl=en_US" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Adsense  Sign up Page </span></a>and then submit complete information about your Blog &amp; yourself and make it sure you  fill only real personal information.</span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/apply-once-and-wait-for-reply-of-adsense-team/" rel="attachment wp-att-2463"><span style="color: #333333;"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2463" title="Apply once and wait for reply of adsense team" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/Apply-once-and-wait-for-reply-of-adsense-team.jpg" width="320" height="164" /></span></a></span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;"> </span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;">After sending application to Adsense you will get a reply e-mail from Adsense Team regarding they partially checked your website after that  follow the procedure given in the mail.  If You can’t received any mail from them then Don’t worry you will be surely respond, sometimes it takes time because they have millions of application from the bloggers all over the world. Generally they reply in maximum 4 days, sometime they reply in 2 days or even 1 day.</span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;">If your application got Disapproved by the Adsense Team, don’t start Crying :D Don’t worry they mention point why your request got  disapproved just fulfill the requirement (mentioned in point)  and apply again because they have lot of applications and they give preference to only Best. Some people when get disapproval mail they send another request instantly  from different email account without taking care of the point in the mail, you don’t do this foolish thing because your blog was not checked by any person their machine or Software check blogs and Website and don’t matter how many email accounts you use for submitting application they only approve your blog if their machine and Software declare it okay.</span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;"> </span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;"><a href="http://harkuchh.com/best-tips-for-approval-of-adsense-google-account-with-requirements-of-adsense/google-adsense-harkuchh/" rel="attachment wp-att-2443"><span style="color: #333333;"><img class="alignleft  wp-image-2443" title="Google Adsense - Harkuchh" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/Google-Adsense-Harkuchh.jpg" width="174" height="100" /></span></a>By fulfilling all these points and following steps you will get an approved Google Adsense Account easily in maximum 4-5 days. This post give the complete information of many Adsense related questions like, What are requirements for a blog approved by Google Adsense, Tips to get approval for Google Adsense &amp; Best way to get approved by Google Adsense..</span></p>

<h1 style="padding-left: 30px;"></h1>


<h2 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #333333;"><em><strong>Note :</strong></em></span></h2>


<p><span style="color: #333333;">Use your real name instead of using any nick or fake name in application if You need to be 18 years old or above, and always remember Even after your blog got approved and you start running Google ads on your blog or website you can’t post anything on it, if you break the TOS, your Adsense account will be removed or possibly banned.</span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;">Read and obey very carefully <strong><a href="https://www.google.com/adsense/localized-terms" target="_blank"><span style="color: #333333;">Adsense Terms and Conditions</span></a></strong>, it may take your time but it is very necessary for good business with Google. as we said in the earlier post  <a title="Permalink to What is Blogging, Why Blogging becoming Popular in Youth ?" href="http://harkuchh.com/what-is-blogging-why-blogging-becoming-popular-in-youth/"><span style="color: #333333;">What is Blogging, Why Blogging becoming Popular in Youth ?</span></a> <strong>never think money is the fruits for your hard deeds but to earn these fruits, you need to show dedicated efforts. Always remember good things takes time.</strong></span></p>

<p><span style="color: #333333;">I Hope this post gives you the way to get an approved Adsense account, if you have any Query and Suggestions to share please comment below, <strong> It will my honor to communicate with you..</strong></span></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Common reasons for Disapproval of Google Adsense Application]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/most-common-reasons-for-disapproval-of-google-adsense-application/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/most-common-reasons-for-disapproval-of-google-adsense-application</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In blogging many people says that I applied for Ads to the Google, but my application got rejected or whenever I apply for Adsense Ads, Google disapproves my request. Even my requests got disapproved two times before I got approved, but people don’t know, what are the reasons responsible for the disapproval of their Adsense application, Google always mentions some reasons in reply email which are responsible for not accepting one’s Ads application. If you read those email(s) properly then you will understand some of the points why Google rejected it.<!--more--></p>

<p><a href="http://harkuchh.com/most-common-reasons-for-disapproval-of-google-adsense-application/google-adsense-disappoval-reasons/" rel="attachment wp-att-8382"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-8382" alt="Google Adsense Disappoval reasons" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/Google-Adsense-Disappoval-reasons-580x229.jpg" width="580" height="229" /></a></p>

<h2><strong>Here are the some most common reasons for disapproval of your Adsense Application..</strong></h2>


<h1 style="padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #000000;">1. Too Many Tags or Keywords</span></h1>


<p>You  might know that Tags plays a very important role in improving your page&rsquo;s visibility in the search engines. Search engines always search for the tags which show what is in your post. Actually these tags are the keywords or the word phrases that people types on different search engines for searching answer of their query. If you don’t know that then must settle this thing in your mind that, you should not give too many keywords in your post, because sometimes written articles are not so informative, but if it contains too many keywords search engines crawls, just because there are many keywords, but Google will not take the post as a healthy webpage, which makes a negative impression of your site to the search engine and Google never approve ads request from those blogs/sites.</p>

<p>Tags must be used in the post according to it’s quantity and quality. Using unusual, useless and irrelevant tags with an article reduces your credibility with the search engines and even people who come to see your website will not feel good, just imagine the moment you are searching for something and you open pages shown from search engine but you won’t find anything about the thing you are searching for, I’m sure you will never comeback to that particular site then why someone comes to your.</p>

<p>See using irrelevant, useless and inappropriate tags in your post may increase your visitors but Google will not accept your Adsense request, because as a good service provider Google always wants to provide best output to the every person using it.</p>

<h1 style="text-align: left; padding-left: 30px;"><span style="color: #000000;"> 2. Lack of Quality Content</span></h1>


<p>You must read this very very carefully, whenever you start writing for you website or any website you must write informative and original content instead of copying someone’s idea before you apply for Google Adsense. As I said Google is the best search engine and as the best service provider Google always looks for content that visitors would love to read from beginning till the end. If your website contains very few articles you will find it really difficult to get approve Adsense account. Atleast in the beginning, prefer to write content that which attaract the attention of readers so that Google consider your application. In your post use titles  and heading that are catchy as well as popular, and never neglect to post genuine and innovative material.and one most important point in article writing is it is better to have text as well as quality pictures in your post and also include videos too, these things make the post more interactive. People love to stay on those pages instead of the webpages that contain only text in post, but it doesn’t mean you use use picture in each of your post, if pictures are not relevant don&rsquo;t use them.</p>

<h1 style="padding-left: 30px;"> <span style="color: #000000;">3. Presence of Copied Content</span></h1>


<p>People think they can make Google fool but dear this is really a very tough thing to do, so if you are using any kind of copy paste either you stop this or stop dreaming of Adsense ads on your site because Google really hate copied and it’s not so tough for google to figure out copied content in a post or webpage, You may don’t know that but it’s true that by doing this you are harming your prestige in the cyber world. Google uses many algorithms and systems to track any kind copied content or any material easily, and most important by doing this you will disgrace your image in front of your readers.</p>

<p>It’s pretty easy to understand that, copy+paste is very easy for anyone one can copy content of a website and paste it on his own but as we know such kind of content isn’t consider as new and so that the particular blog or site will not get indexed by search engines and will not get ranking too. If Google or other search engines will not index your page then from where you will get visitors, from nowhere ! and as the result visits, views and clicks on your blog will be very low and you will get nothing. In short don’t do copy-paste.</p>

<h1 style="padding-left: 30px;"> <span style="color: #000000;">4. Invalid Clicks and Comments</span></h1>


<p>Many people generally thinks that if they click on their webpages their pageviews, traffic will increase and by doing this they will earn better but guys it’s called invalid clicks which is considered as a fraud or cheating by the internet companies. People who don’t have Adsense yet must remember, invalid clicks activity will make it much more difficult for your blog to get approved and even if you have approved Adsense account it doesn&rsquo;t meant it will stay with you forever, invalid clicks and impression can also lead to cancellation of your approved adsense account.</p>

<h1 style="padding-left: 30px;"> <span style="color: #000000;">5. Incomplete Websites</span></h1>


<p>This is the most important factor people don’t think about, they won’t give their attention to this but Google does, various necessary pages like About page, Privacy page and Contact page is very essential for Adsense, these pages provides info. about the blogger and Blog (the content what your blog contains) it creates a bond between readers and the blogger. Before submitting your application for Google Adsense you must have complete webpages that can be considered by Google, and yes Incomplete webpages will not be accepted and your application will get rejected until you complete it and resubmit your form.</p>

<p>I hope my effort help you, for any query, suggestion must comment, don&rsquo;t forget to share..</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
