<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Announcements | harkuchh]]></title>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/blog/categories/announcements/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-18T19:19:37+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://harkuchh.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[harkuchh]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launching harkuchh.com/forums to Help Blogging Community]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/launching-harkuchh-dot-com-slash-forums-to-help-blogging-community/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-18T03:39:09+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/launching-harkuchh-dot-com-slash-forums-to-help-blogging-community</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello Friends,</p>

<p>Today I’m very glad to announce that me and my harkuchh team is all set to launch our <a href="http://harkuchh.com/forums/">harkuchh forums</a>. We have been doing a hell of experiments since Charanjit has joined harkuchh. We were playing with this idea of building a community for bloggers. A community that will not suck blood. A community that is not <a href="http://harkuchh.com/corporate-society-is-fraud-bitch-please/">Corporate Society</a>. We envisioned a community that will help each other grow.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p> <br/>
The blogging culture we’ve all been a part for so long is depressing. Good content not getting what it deserve, and spam rolling everywhere; ruining the good work of many. It sucks. Those who create quality content should not suffer. I believe everything stopping a quality blogger from rising is a sin on the spammer’s head who is responsible for his demise.</p>

<p>We tried many things and now we are settled with what I’m here to announce. Things may change in future depending on the response from community; life is an experiment after all.</p>

<p>Ok then, now some questions will come to your mind, which is obvious. Questions like, Harkuchh Forums! But why? What it will do?  Questions like this may tease you, so here I’m explaining the reason behind the origination of Harkuchh forums.</p>

<p>Around two years back I started blogging with my very first blog Harkuchh.com. That time I was unaware of blogging and all other related things like Domain, Hosting, Ranking, Search Engine, Algorithm updates, Penguin, Panda, Humming Bird, SEO, Spam, Quality Post, Backlinks etc etc. I used to ask for help from various bloggers through their blogs comment boxes and facebook messages and they barely gave their time to respond to those message.</p>

<p>When I realized nobody will care to you untill you become something by your own and then I started reading, trying and implementing. Nobody was around to tell me what I’m doing wrong or what I’m doing right.</p>

<p>Blogging was like a big desert where I was familiar with nothing and wherever I turned there was something unknown and complex. I was like the only who had to survive, thankfully I proved myself Bear Grills :P Just kidding.</p>

<p>I mean I’m really thankful to the God that somehow I learnt many things of blogging from sources I don’t remember today but I can never forget Google and YouTube, with these two biggest platforms it was impossible for me to reach wherever I’m today. But it took a long, very long while to reach this place.</p>

<p>So,</p>

<p>As I’ve gone through all this and I know the pain of no result and no answers from people whom we expect to get a genuine reply, I thought of making a platform or a community where people can ask and share their blogging experience, queries with the people from the same world of Blogging. And here is the&hellip;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
