<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: EDUCATION | harkuchh]]></title>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/blog/categories/education/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-01-29T01:21:45+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://harkuchh.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[harkuchh]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Pop-ups or what are the Pop up ads ?]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/what-are-pop-ups-or-what-are-the-pop-up-ads/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/what-are-pop-ups-or-what-are-the-pop-up-ads</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><b>Popup ads</b> or <b>pop up advertising</b> are the advertisements that show up in a new browser window when you click or hover on a link or image while surfing on internet. The overall <b>definition of a popup</b> is <code>&lt;em&gt;a browser window that appears out of nowhere as you are viewing content on the web.&lt;/em&gt;</code> There are also programs known as <b>pop under ads</b>, which display windows behind your web browser window. As a user is surfing the web and visiting various websites, new windows may suddenly (<em>and without user initiation</em>) open and display advertisements and promotions.<!--more--></p>

<p><a href="http://harkuchh.com/what-are-pop-ups-or-what-are-the-pop-up-ads/what-are-pop-up-ads/" rel="attachment wp-att-8100"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-8100" alt="what are pop up ads" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/what-are-pop-up-ads.jpeg" width="348" height="341" /></a></p>

<p><span style="color: #ff0000;"><strong>Pop-Ups</strong> are NOT security risks</span>. They can NOT carry Spy Bots, Viruses, or Trojans. The reason they may be blocked is that, if they are designed to open automatically, they can be annoying nuisances!</p>

<h1>Major Concerns of PopUps</h1>


<ul>
    <li>A screen flooded with pop-ups may make navigating the web stressful and difficult.</li>
    <li>At times, they may look like browsers of normal web pages and can cause confusion to the users. A pop-up may not be even related to the site itself, thus annoying the user with its irrelevance to the site and its obstruction to the browsing experience.</li>
    <li>Some pop-ups contain inappropriate or even pornographic content, which you may not like to watch.</li>
    <li>Some pop-ups appear as a result in the site being reloaded, causing loss of information for the users.</li>
</ul>


<h1><b>How to Block Popup Ads </b></h1>


<p>Ads pop up can be a tremendous annoyance, but there are ways to deal with them. Your best bet would be to close the window and not interact with those <b>popups</b>. The <b>best way to prevent from Popup ads</b> is don&rsquo;t connect to internet without enabling firewall and Anti-virus software. Increase the security settings in the browser so that Activex controls won&rsquo;t install automatically and these <b>free classifieds</b> won’t come up to your screen.</p>

<p>Default browser of Microsoft Windows <code>Internet Explorer</code> is configured to <b>block all pop-up ads</b> by default. If you don’t like the blocker warning or its associated beep, you can control the <b>pop-up blocker’s</b> settings. Also, any good Anti-virus package can be a great tool for avoiding pop-ups.</p>

<p>For bloggers pop up advertising can be proved as a great source of income from their blog, but we recommend you to don’t go for it, people hates it and most probably you too.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
