<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: NEW TECHNOLOGY | harkuchh]]></title>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/blog/categories/new-technology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://harkuchh.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-01-29T01:21:45+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://harkuchh.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[harkuchh]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do not Believe on Websites like GetwebsiteWorth.com]]></title>
    <link href="http://harkuchh.com/why-i-dont-believe-on-websites-like-getwebsiteworth/"/>
    <updated>2013-01-15T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://harkuchh.com/why-i-dont-believe-on-websites-like-getwebsiteworth</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">There are more than enough websites over internet who tells the a website’s worth, their income, page views, daily traffic, Ads revenues etc and well known example of this type of websites is <strong>Getwebsiteworth.com</strong>, This is a site who tells worth of websites, by tracing some stats of a website.<!--more--></span></p>

<p><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">I’m very sure that, You Guys have also checked your website worth on some websites like this many time and became happy after knowing the worth of your website, but the thing I’m going to tell you through this post will make your a lil bit sad for sure.</span></p>

<p><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">All these kind of websites who shows estimated cost of a website are non-Trustable, I mean don’t trust on any of them, now you may surely wanted to ask <code>but why I don’t believe on Getwebsiteworth ?</code> right ! oh yeah I’m sure you wanted to ask this, so here are the points..</span></p>

<div style="height: 440px; width: 600px; float: left; background: #F0F0F0;">
<ul>
    <li><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">All these websites who tell value of a website are also a particular website and they want traffic on their site same like we want on our website, and for this they make people fool.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
    <li><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">These websites trace some data of our website from internet which are easily available for anyone like Alexa ranking and search engine health of our website.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
    <li><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">After fetching these data from internet they estimate worth of our website by following some Algorithms.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
    <li><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">The worth is calculated by taking the average of ranking, SEO properties, search engine visibility etc.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
    <li><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">On the basis of those records, they produce fake calculated worth and other result like Pageviews and ads revenues.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
    <li><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">Even after they show clearly fake information &amp; result on their sites, people go heavily crowded to these sites on regular interval for checking whether worth of their site increased or not, they feel happy to see their website’s worth but they are unaware of the fact that, they have been tricked and these website making people nothing more than fool and they don’t want any occasion like April fool for this.</span></li>
</ul>
</div>


<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p><em style="color: #000000; font-family: georgia;"><strong>Note</strong> </em><span style="color: #000000; font-family: georgia;">: I’m not talking about Getwebsiteworth.com only instead I’m talking about all those websites who shows worth of a website.</span></p>

<p><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">I know still many people not ready to believe on me and  my words, no problem it’s human tendency to not believe on true things they love to be sticked with those things which make them smile no matter those things are genuine or not, but no worries I have a proof.</span></p>

<p><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">If you are also one of those category people then in next few lines you will start believing on me, here is the proof why I’m telling you to not believe on Getwebsiteworth.com or any of this type of website.</span></p>

<h4><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;"><strong>First of all see this picture..</strong></span></h4>


<p>[caption id=&ldquo;attachment_6011&rdquo; align=&ldquo;aligncenter&rdquo; width=&ldquo;479&rdquo;]<a href="http://harkuchh.com/why-i-dont-believe-on-websites-like-getwebsiteworth/is-getwebsiteworth-com-a-trustable-site-no/" rel="attachment wp-att-6011"><img class="size-full wp-image-6011" title="is Getwebsiteworth.com a trustable site, No !" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/01/is-Getwebsiteworth.com-a-trustable-site-No-.jpg" width="479" height="441" /></a> snapshot taken last week from <strong>Getwebsiteworth</strong>[/caption]</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">This is great, isn’t it. According to this record my website Harkuchh.Com having 46,608 daily pageviews this is kind of joke for me you know why, because actual daily pageviews of my website is average 6-8K&hellip; Wait wait don’t laugh yet I’ve one joke to crack here which make you laugh harder, according to Getwebsteworth my Daily Ads Revenue is $196 :D and you know what, Harkuchh.Com’s actual daily ads revenues is less than $10 till today. Hehehehe&hellip;.. <a href="http://harkuchh.com/google-is-a-girl-i-can-prove-it/biggrin/" rel="attachment wp-att-5324"><img title="Kamina Hansi" alt="" src="http://harkuchh.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/biggrin.gif" width="16" height="16" /></a></span></p>

<p><span style="font-family: georgia; color: #000000;">Now see the difference where is $196 and where it stands on $10, now I think I don’t need to explain it anymore, you guys are smart and most probably having your own brain inside your skull (tell me if you don’t :P ) so now you are going to believe on these kind of stuff  in future ! comment if you liked it.</span></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
